Who is a self-taught software engineer, game developer and entrepreneur most widely known as the co-creator of Endless Ages, a first person shooter MMOG combined with elements of role playing; thus making it the world's first MMOFPSRPG (massively-multplayer-online-first-person-shooter-role-playing-game), as it was heralded in its day?
Aaron Boucher    Thomas Peterffy    Jeff Raikes    Bruce Ableson

Who is an English television presenter, journalist and Watford FC support?
Adam Leventhal     Kingsley Uyi Idehen    Ken Arnold    Daniel Robbins

Who is an American software designer and programmer. Widely recognized as the “Father of Visual Basic," Cooper is also known for his books on About Face 3: The Essentials of Interaction Design and The Inmates Are Running the Asylum: Why High-Tech Products Drive Us Crazy and How to Restore the Sanity?
Alan Cooper    Alan Kay    Vern Paxson    Marc Andreessen

Who is one of the initiators of the agile movement in software development, helping write the Manifesto for Agile Software Development in 2001, the agile PM Declaration of Interdependence in 2005, and co-founding the [http://icagile.com International Consortium for Agile] in 2009 (with Ahmed Sidky and Ash Rofail)?
Alistair Cockburn    Aaron Boucher    Brian Eddy    Robert Fourer

Who is an American TV host, acclaimed fisherman, and web entrepreneur.  He is the founder and owner of Sound Strategies, Inc a leading NY based web services provider specializing in search engine optimization?
Andy LoCascio    David Maynard    Jim Gettys    Brian Eddy

Who is a software developer best known for her work with Drupal, a free and open source content management system and content management framework?
Angela Byron    Dave Hyatt    Ken Schwaber    Robert Abbott 

Who is an American  interface designer. He is the son of human-computer interface expert Jef Raskin?
Aza Raskin    Ronald Dale Harris    Chris Roberts     Gary Martin 

Who is a computer scientist and software researcher.  He retired from IBM's Thomas J?
Barry Leiba    Aaron Swartz    Mark Jason Dominus    William Clinger 

Who is a Taiwanese-born American and Canadian computer programmer and entrepreneur?
Ben Chiu    Ilya Zhitomirskiy    Deepen Shah    Michael Holve

Who is an author and Senior Technical Evangelist for Adobe Systems, particularly ColdFusion and Flex, and the owner of EmTek Systems?
Ben Forta    Molly Holzschlag    Mike Filsaime    Scott Seebass

Who is a co-founder (with ex-wife Mena Trott) of Six Apart, creator of Movable Type and TypePad?
Benjamin Trott    Jim Kent    Stu Moment    Doug Bell

Who is an American business magnate, investor, programmer, inventor and philanthropist?
Bill Gates    Alan Kay    Danese Cooper    Wayne Chang

Who is an American computer scientist.  Joy co-founded Sun Microsystems in 1982 along with Vinod Khosla, Scott McNealy and Andreas von Bechtolsheim, and served as chief scientist at the company until 2003. He played an integral role in the early development of BSD UNIX while a graduate student at Berkeley, and he is the original author of the vi text editor?
Bill Joy    Jeremy Sagan    Biz Stone    Donald Knuth

Who is an American software engineer best known for creating and maintaining Tux Paint, an open source bitmap graphics editor for children?
Bill Kendrick    Eric Haines    John Draper    Tom Lane 

Who is a computer programmer, owner of Wholly Genes Software, and creator of The Master Genealogist, genealogy software?
Bob Velke    Jeff Sutherland    Lois Haibt    Brendan Eich

Who is an American programmer. He is best known as the creator of LiveJournal and is the author of a variety of free software projects such as memcached and OpenID?
Brad Fitzpatrick    Bill Kendrick    Tim Stryker    Deepen Shah

Who is an American computer programmer, best known as the author of the peer-to-peer (P2P) BitTorrent protocol, as well as the first file sharing program to use the protocol, also known as BitTorrent?
Bram Cohen    Bill Joy    Grace Hopper    Christopher Abad

Who is an inventor and founder of several network technology companies whose well known products include PIX Firewall, the first stateful-inspection firewall and Cisco Systems first load-balancer, LocalDirector?
Brantley Coile    Ward Cunningham    Alistair Cockburn    Bill Gates

Who is an American computer programmer and creator of the JavaScript scripting language?
Brendan Eich    Dominic Giampaolo    Thomas Peterffy    Donald Knuth

Who is the publisher and editor of The Perl Review, a magazine devoted to Perl and co-author of several books on Perl including Learning Perl and Intermediate Perl?
Brian d foy    Larry Kaplan    Daniel Kottke    Elliot Koffman

Who is an American computer programmer and designer. He works at Midway Games, and his completed designs include several of the most popular and influential pinball machines of the 1990s, including Attack From Mars, Medieval Madness?
Brian Eddy    Rodnay Zaks    Gordon Eubanks    Ben Chiu

Who is an American computer programmer and website developer?
Bruce Ableson    Aza Raskin    Michael Deering    Brantley Coile

Who is Board Chair of the International Society for Inconsistency Robustness. He has been a Visiting Professor at Stanford University and the University of Keio?
Carl Hewitt    Lois Haibt    Lukas Biewald    Larry Wall

Who is a Democratic member of the Fairfax County Board of Supervisors; representing the Hunter Mill district, which includes the town of Reston?
Cathy Hudgins    Kingsley Uyi Idehen    Alan Kay    Pito Salas

Who is a Professor of Software Engineering at Florida Institute of Technology, and the Director of Florida Tech's Center for Software Testing Education & Research (CSTER) since 2004.  He is perhaps best known outside academia as an advocate of software usability and software testing?
Cem Kaner    Eric Allman    Shawn Bayern    Larry Kaplan

Who is a Hungarian-American computer software executive who, as head of Microsoft's application software group, oversaw the creation of Microsoft's flagship Office suite of applications?
Charles Simonyi    Jeff Atwood    Thomas Peterffy    Delon Dotson

Who is an American software developer, best known as the primary author of the LLVM project and related projects, such as the clang compiler?
Chris Lattner    Narendra Rocherolle    Gordon Eubanks    Owen Mock

Who is an American hacker, museum curator, artist, network engineer and programmer. He is best known for his qualitative analysis of specialization stratification in the underground economies related to computer crime?
Christopher Abad    Samy Kamkar    Narendra Rocherolle    Eric Allman

Who is a software developer, game programmer, entrepreneur, and the founder of Bethesda Softworks?
Christopher Weaver    Qi Lu    Jon Phillips    Shawn Bayern

Who is also applied to intervals, chords, notes, musical styles, and kinds of harmony?
Chromatic     Ward Cunningham    Mark Kilgard    Richard Brodie 

Who is a programmer from Columbus, Ohio also known as the Dead Body Guy. He has gained fame playing dead people in film and television?
Chuck Lamb    Aaron Boucher    Andrew Koenig     Joseph Primiani

Who is an entrepreneur and software designer. An inventor of Heatmaps, trading and risk management systems used by institutional traders, and a news analysis methods for quantitative securities trading?
Cormac Kinney    Lois Haibt    Ilya Zhitomirskiy    Aaron Swartz

Who is an American game programme?
Corrinne Yu    Earl Isaac    Trung Dung    Andy Kessler 

Who is a programmer and original author of the Apache Struts framework for building web applications?
Craig McClanahan    Owen Mock    Bruce Ableson    Dominic Giampaolo

Who is a software developer, user interface designer, writer, and podcaster?
Dan Benjamin    Andy Kessler     Brad Fitzpatrick    William Clinger 

Who is an American programmer, computer scientist, and an advocate of open source software?
Danese Cooper    Eric Haines    Tim Paterson    DJ Delorie

Who is a U.S. computer engineer and one of the earliest employees of Apple Inc?
Daniel Kottke    Matthew Dillon    Chuck Lamb    Molly Holzschlag

Who is a computer programmer and consultant best known as the founder and former chief architect of the Gentoo Linux project?
Daniel Robbins    Michael Morrison     Robert Iannucci    Bill Gates

Who is a computer programmer, technology consultant, and an award-winning author of over three dozen books and hundreds of magazine articles on computer-related topics?
Danny Goodman    Warren Gish    Jeff De Luca    Joe Hewitt 

Who is an American software engineer, designer and developer of several operating systems including RSX-11M, VMS and VAXELN at Digital Equipment Corporation and Windows NT at Microsoft?
Dave Cutler    Paul Irish    Jeff Raikes    Shawn Bayern

Who is an American software developer employed by Apple Inc. (since July 15, 2002), where he is part of the development team responsible for the Safari web browser and WebKit framework?
Dave Hyatt    Tom Proulx    Joseph Primiani    Vern Paxson

Who is a computer programmer and game programmer who has spent his career working at various companies in the San Francisco Bay Area?
David Maynard    Dick Smith     Andy LoCascio    Gordon Eubanks

Who is an American author, computer programmer, and pro-animal activist?
David Rolsky    Larry Wall    Stormy Peters    Jon Phillips

Who is an American journalist and columnist for CBSNews.com.  He specializes in computer security and privacy issues?
Declan McCullagh    Ron Jeffries    Larry Wall    Michael Morrison 

Who is an American softwis architect, philanthropist,  businessperson, and entrepreneur known as the co-creator of buzzd, FanBridge?
Deepen Shah    Mike Filsaime    Stepan Pachikov    Robert Iannucci

Who is a technologist and businessman who has worked in several businesses, including Netscape Communications and MP3.com?
Delon Dotson    Mark Davis     Eric Haines    John Warnock

Who is an American software developer. He initiated and maintains the DJGPP project, a port of the GNU C/C++ compiler and tools suite, targeted for PCs running MS-DOS or DOS terminals under Microsoft Windows?
DJ Delorie    Ilya Zhitomirskiy    Donald Knuth    Michael Holve

Who is a software developer who helped develop the Be File System for the Be Operating System (BeOS) and currently works at Apple Inc?
Dominic Giampaolo    Brad Fitzpatrick    Henry Burkhardt III    Ian Murdock

Who is a computer scientist and Professor Emeritus at Stanford University?
Donald Knuth    Elliot Koffman    Chuck Lamb    Matthew Dillon

Who is an advocate and creator of open-source search technology. He originated Lucene and, with Mike Cafarella, Nutch, both open-source search technology projects which are now managed through the Apache Software Foundation?
Doug Cutting    Nick Gerakines    Brad Fitzpatrick    Michael Holve

Who is a professor of computer science at State University of New York at Oswego, where he specializes in concurrent programming and the design of concurrent data structures?
Doug Lea    Scott Seebass    Chromatic     Sol Katz

Who is an American computer programmer and entrepreneur who is best known for his ongoing involvement in the development of the JavaScript language, for having popularized the data format JSON (JavaScript Object Notation), and for developing various JavaScript related tools such as JSLint and JSMin?
Douglas Crockford    Alistair Cockburn    Aaron Swartz    Betty Holberton

Who is an ACM Fellow, an IEEE Fellow (since 2003), and an AT&T Fellow at Bell Labs for research in software metrics and testing as well as elected to the National Academy of Engineering?
Elaine Weyuker    Cormac Kinney    David Rolsky    Mark Kilgard

Who is the co-founder of FORTH, Inc. and is a leading expert in the Forth programming language?
Elizabeth Rather    Bruce Ableson    Ross Cohen    Chuck Lamb

Who is a noted computer scientist and educationist?
Elliot Koffman    Darin Adler    Paul Allen    Ward Cunningham

Who is an American computer programmer who  developed sendmail and its precursor delivermail in the late 1970s and early 1980s at UC Berkeley?
Eric Allman    Matthew Dillon    Chris Roberts     Mark Davis 

Who is an American software engineer, and is an expert in computer graphics, specifically image rendering?
Eric Haines    Russ Nelson    Michael Holve    Cathy Hudgins

Who is a software developer and writer.  He is the author of  on the Business of Software (2006), a collection of essays from his blog and the "Business of Software" column for the Microsoft Developer Network?
Eric Sink    Andy LoCascio    Doug Bell    Carl Hewitt

Who is an American software developer and computer technical writer?
Erick Tejkowski    Chuck Forsberg    Sol Katz    Chuck Lamb

Who is the Chairman and CEO of SnapLogic, an enterprise application and data integration software development company that helps organizations connect business applications and Web services?
Gaurav Dhillon    Mark Davis     Jonathan Alexander    Ben Forta

Who is the creator of the Newspeak programming language, a software engineer at Google and a member of the Dart (programming language) team in Aarhus?
Gilad Bracha    Mark Kilgard    Gaurav Dhillon    Greg Skibiski

Who is an American microcomputer industry pioneer who worked with Gary Kildall in the early days of Digital Research?
Gordon Eubanks    Robert Abbott     Steven Snyder    Brian d foy

Who is an American computer engineer and entrepreneur. He is known in the free software community due to his work on HAL, GNOME, Metacity, GConf, and D-BUS?
Havoc Pennington    Andy Kessler     Alan Cooper    Jon Mittelhauser

Who is the founder of the Debian distribution and Progeny Linux Systems, a commercial Linux company?
Ian Murdock    Michael Deering    DJ Delorie    Dick Smith 

Who is an American web developer and businessman widely known as the creator of Twitter and as the founder and CEO of Square, a mobile payments company?
Jack Dorsey    Andrew Fluegelman    Mark Davis     Corrinne Yu

Who is a computer programmer, writer, musician, and game designer. He publishes most of his software under the GNU GPL or into the public domain, and charges for the iPhone ports of his games?
Jason Rohrer    Stepan Pachikov    Alan Kay    Robert Abbott 

Who is a Bangladeshi German American internet entrepreneur. He is best known for being the  co-founder of the popular video sharing website YouTube?
Jawed Karim    Daniel Weinreb    Andrew Fluegelman    Peter Norton

Who is a San Francisco-based author, computer scientist, software executive and entrepreneur of French descent, noted for his active role in mobile computing standardization efforts, and profiled for his participation in the web 2.0 movement and ecosystem?
Jean Sini    Robby Garner    Owen Mock    Chromatic 

Who is an American software developer, author, blogger, and entrepreneur. He is mainly known for the programming blog Coding Horror, and as the co-founder of the question-and-answer website Stack Overflow and the Stack Exchange Network?
Jeff Atwood    Justin Lewis     Bob Velke    Steven McGeady

Who is a software developer, most notable for leading the team that developed the ZFS file system?
Jeff Bonwick    Roger Powell     Bill Kendrick    Pat Villani

Who is a global information technology strategist and an author in the field of software development methodology?
Jeff De Luca    Mark Pilgrim     Shawn Fanning    Kelley Deal

Who is the chief executive officer of the Bill & Melinda Gates Foundation?
Jeff Raikes    Gordon Lyon    Monte Davidoff    Jon Mittelhauser

Who is one of the inventors of the Scrum software development process. Together with Ken Schwaber, he created Scrum as a formal process at OOPSLA'95. They have extended and enhanced Scrum at many software companies and IT organizations?
Jeff Sutherland    Gaurav Dhillon    Bruce Carver    Mark Davis 

Who is an American entrepreneur, computer scientist and software developer?
Jeff Wellemeyer    Ross Cohen    Steve Wozniak    Chuck Lamb

Who is an American technology entrepreneur and Arizona millionaire who is considered to be the pioneer of hispanic Internet in the United States?
Jeffrey Peterson    David Maynard    Jean Bartik    Betty Holberton

Who is the inventor of Jabber/XMPP technologies and was the primary developer of jabberd 1.0, the first XMPP server?
Jeremie Miller    Jeff Sutherland    Stephen Warshall    Alistair Cockburn

Who is an American computer programmer. He is the founder of Sagan Technology and author of Metro: an audio, MIDI and video sequencer for Apple Macintosh computers?
Jeremy Sagan    Brian d foy    Robert Fourer    Wayne Chang

Who is an American computer programmer at Alcatel-Lucent Bell Labs, USA. Until January 2009, he was the Vice President of Softwis at the One Laptop per Child project, working on the software for the OLPC XO-1. He is one of the original developers of the X Window System at MIT and worked on it again with X.Org, where he served on the board of directors?
Jim Gettys    Phil Katz    Nick Gerakines    Molly Holzschlag

Who is an American jazz guitarist, composer and arranger?
Jim Hall     Larry Wall    Brantley Coile    Brantley Coile

Who is an American software engineer and author of books in the field of software development methodology?
Jim Highsmith    Ron Jeffries    Brantley Coile    Christopher Weaver

Who is an American research scientist and computer programmer?
Jim Kent    Gordon Lyon    Alan Kotok    Stephen Warshall

Who is the designer of the NCR Corporation version of the p-code machine which is a kind of Stack machine popular in the 1970s as the preferred way to implement new computing architectures and languages such as Pascal and BCPL?
Joel McCormack    Matthew Haughey    Jon Phillips    Earl Isaac

Who is a software engineer and writer. He is the author of Joel on Software, a blog on software development?
Joel Spolsky    DJ Delorie    Scott Meyers    Sol Katz

Who is an American computer programmer and former phone phreak?
John Draper    Brendan Eich    Chris Roberts     Gordon Eubanks

Who is a US computer scientist, director and entrepreneu?
John Mashey    Stormy Peters    Kelley Deal    Donald Knuth

Who is an American computer scientist best known as the co-founder with Charles Geschke of Adobe Systems Inc., the graphics and publishing software company?
John Warnock    Biz Stone    Bill Gates    Craig McClanahan

Who is considered a founding father of the web browse?
Jon Mittelhauser    Shawn Fanning    Mitchell Waite    Deepen Shah

Who is an open source developer, artist, designer, writer, educator, lecturer, and curator with 12+ years of experience creating communities and working within computing culture?
Jon Phillips    Paul Haeberli    Shawn Bayern    Chris Lattner

Who is an American sex offender and a former fugitive who was added to the FBI's Top Ten Most Wanted Fugitives list on September 7, 2007.  Schillaci is the 488th fugitive to be placed on the list?
Jon Schillaci    Russ Nelson    Richard Green     Larry McVoy

Who is an American Internet entrepreneur and designer best known as the founder of [http://www.thebackplane.com Backplane] and Cortex?
Joseph Primiani    Jeff De Luca    Jeremy Sagan    Shawn Bayern

Who is a software engineer, formerly employed at Google, and a technology author?
Joshua Bloch    DJ Delorie    Stepan Pachikov    Alan Kotok

Who is an American musician. The identical twin sister of Kim Deal, she is the lead guitarist of The Breeders, besides having a solo career?
Kelley Deal    Nathaniel Borenstein    Ronald Dale Harris    Tom Van Vleck

Who is an American computer programmer well known as one of the developers of the 1980s dungeon-crawling video game Rogue, for his contributions to the original Berkeley (BSD) distribution of Unix, for his books and articles about C and C++ (e.g?
Ken Arnold    Bill Kendrick    Mark Jason Dominus    Kelley Deal

Who is a software developer, product manager and industry consultant.  Ken worked with Jeff Sutherland to formulate the initial versions of the Scrum development process and to present Scrum as a formal process at OOPSLA'95. They have extended and enhanced Scrum at many software companies and IT organizations?
Ken Schwaber    Earl Isaac    Michael Deering    Larry McVoy

Who is an American pioneer of computer science?
Ken Thompson    Rodnay Zaks    Pat Villani    Andrew Fluegelman

Who is an American entrepreneur and software engineer best known as the co‑founder and CEO of Instagram?
Kevin Systrom    Ward Christensen    Joel McCormack    Elizabeth Rather

Who is Founder, President, and CEO of OpenLink Software, a privately held company founded in 1992.  Born in Manchester, England in 1965, of Nigerian heritage, Idehen was raised in both Great Britain and Nigeria?
Kingsley Uyi Idehen    Mark Davis     Mark Crispin    Jon Phillips

Who is an American video game designer and programmer. He initially worked at Atari and was responsible for a lot of their sales?
Larry Kaplan    Paul Haeberli    Steve Wozniak    Elizabeth Rather

Who is the CEO of BitMover, the company that makes BitKeeper, a version control system that was used from February 2002 to early 2005 to manage the source code of the Linux kernel?
Larry McVoy    Scott Meyers    Mike Lesk    Monte Davidoff

Who is a computer programmer and author, most widely known for his creation of the Perl programming language in 198?
Larry Wall    Joel McCormack    Mark Jason Dominus    Martin Roesch

Who is an American theoretical computer scientist and professor of computer science and molecular biology at the University of Southern California?
Leonard Adleman    Rodnay Zaks    Chris Lattner    Samy Kamkar

Who is an American computer scientist, and is perhaps most famous for being a member of the ten-person team at IBM that developed FORTRAN, the first successful high level programming language?
Lois Haibt    Elizabeth Rather    Mark Zuckerberg    Dave Hyatt

Who is an American attorney, and Deputy General Counsel at the Wikimedia Foundation. Previously he was an attorney at Greenberg Traurig and Mozilla, where he worked on the revision of the Mozilla Public License (MPL)?
Luis Villa    Mark Davis     Jon Schillaci    Brendan Eich

Who is an entrepreneur living in San Francisco, California. Biewald is CEO of CrowdFlower (formerly Dolores Labs) — an Internet company that breaks large digital projects into small tasks and distributes them to workers around the world — which he co-founded in December 2007 with Chris Van Pelt?
Lukas Biewald    William Clinger     Kevin Systrom    Richard Wallace 

Who is an American entrepreneur, investor, software engineer, and multi-millionaire?
Marc Andreessen    Wayne Chang    Jim Hall     Ward Cunningham

Who is a Northern Irish professional snooker player. He won the World Amateur Championship in 2004. The following year he entered the Main Tour and took only three seasons to reach the elite top 16. Entering the 2010/2011 season, he was ranked 1?
Mark Allen     Ken Arnold    Michael Hawley    Declan McCullagh

Who is the author of Higher-Order Perl: Transforming Programs with Programs which was published in 2005 by Morgan Kaufmann?
Mark Jason Dominus    Ronald Dale Harris    Roger Powell     Alistair Cockburn

Who is a graphics software engineer working at Nvidi?
Mark Kilgard    Thomas Peterffy    Ken Schwaber    Warren Gish

Who is an American game programmer and the founder, principal technologist, and majority owner of Terminal Reality?
Mark Randel    Jim Hall     DJ Delorie    Ward Cunningham

Who is an American computer programmer and Internet entrepreneur?
Mark Zuckerberg    Death of Kevin Flanagan    Tom Proulx    DJ Delorie

Who is responsible for the technical direction and product development efforts?
Martin Roesch    Lois Haibt    Paul Haeberli    Eric Sink

Who is a computer scientist living in Berkeley, California. He is best known for his contributions to FreeBSD and for starting the DragonFly BSD project?
Matthew Dillon    Joseph Primiani    Shawn Fanning    Dan Benjamin

Who is an American programmer, web designer, and  best known as the founder of the community weblog MetaFilter, where he is known as mathowie?
Matthew Haughey    Paul Allen    Tom Proulx    Vern Paxson

Who is a computer scientist, a former chief engineer for Sun Microsystems in Mountain View, California, and a widely recognized expert on artificial intelligence, computer vision, 3D graphics hardware/software, very-large-scale integration (VLSI) design and virtual reality?
Michael Deering    Gordon Eubanks    Pradeep Tapadiya    Warren Gish

Who is an educator, artist and researcher working in the field of digital media?
Michael Hawley    Douglas Crockford    Chris Lattner    Cormac Kinney

Who is an American author, photographer, programmer and systems administrator?
Michael Holve    Stormy Peters    Nick Gerakines    Jason Rohrer

Who is the president and project lead of Castaway Entertainment, a company formed out of former Blizzard North employees in 2003. He is also responsible for programming on Diablo II and the development of the Battle.net game server network?
Michael Scandizzo    Bill Kendrick    Ben Chiu    Adam Leventhal 

Who is an American author, software developer, personal coach, social media expert and business consultant who specializes in Internet Marketing?
Mike Filsaime    Rodnay Zaks    Darin Adler    Elliot Koffman

Who is a computer scientis?
Mike Lesk    Mark Zuckerberg    Ben Chiu    Gordon Lyon

Who is an American computer programmer and author of programming books. His first book "Projects in Sight, Sound and Sensation" was published in 1974. He did a physics degree at Sonoma State University during 1971–197?
Mitchell Waite    Doug Bell    Daniel Weinreb    Ron Jeffries

Who is a US author, lecturer and advocate for the Open Web. She has written or co-authored over 35 books on web design and open standards, including The Zen of CSS Design: Visual Enlightenment for the Web (co-authored with Dave Shea) and Transcending CSS: The Fine Art of Web Design with Andy Clarke?
Molly Holzschlag    Mike Filsaime    Barry Leiba    Danese Cooper

Who is an American computer programmer.  He graduated from Nicolet High School in Glendale, Wisconsin in 1974.  He went on to Harvard University, where he majored in applied mathematics, the department at Harvard that, at the time, included computer science?
Monte Davidoff    Larry Wall    Bill Gates    Eric Sink

Who is an American entrepreneur, designer, and software enginee?
Narendra Rocherolle    Owen Mock    Bob Scheifler    Shawn Fanning

Who is an American computer scientis?
Nathaniel Borenstein    Ben Chiu    Ken Schwaber    Rich Skrenta

Who is an American author, speaker  and software engineer. He is a contributor to a number of notable open source Erlang projects on GitHub and is the author of the book Facebook Application Developmen?
Nick Gerakines    Aaron Boucher    Jean Bartik    Ward Cunningham

Who is an American computer programmer and inventor. He is the founder and chief executive officer of Quest Visual Inc?
Otavio Good    Bram Cohen    Ken Schwaber    Larry McVoy

Who is an American inventor, investor and philanthropist, best known as the co-founder, with Bill Gates, of Microsoft Corporation?
Paul Allen    Eric Allman    Monte Davidoff    Mark Randel

Who is an American computer programmer and entrepreneur. He was the creator and lead developer of Gmail?
Paul Buchheit    Shawn Fanning    Betty Holberton    Scott Werndorfer

Who is an American computer graphics programmer and researche?
Paul Haeberli    Brian Eddy    Mark Jason Dominus    Biz Stone

Who is an American front-end web developer, and developer advocate for Google Chrome. He is also recognized as an expert in cutting edge Web Technologies like HTML5 and CSS?
Paul Irish    Wayne Bell     Elliot Koffman    Mark Harris 

Who is an American programmer, software publisher, author, and philanthropist?
Peter Norton    Ben Chiu    Larry Wall    Michael Morrison 

Who is an American computer scientist, best known for creating pioneering computer software?
Peter Samson    Robert Abbott     Alan Kay    Jon Phillips

Who is a Curacaoan-American Cambridge, Massachusetts-based software developer. While working with the Lotus Advanced Technology Group in 1986,  invented a next-generation spreadsheet concept which was released by Lotus in 1989 as Lotus Improv?
Pito Salas    Gary Martin     Jonathan Alexander    Jon Mittelhauser

Who is a computer programmer and Silicon Valley entrepreneur who created the search engine blekko?
Rich Skrenta    Narendra Rocherolle    Ross Cohen    Alan Kay

Who is an English footballer who plays for Crawley Town as a striker?
Richard Brodie     Adam Leventhal     Joe Hewitt     Jim Kent

Who is a natural language programmer and software developer. He won the 1998 and 1999 Loebner Prize Contests with the program called Albert One?
Robby Garner    Jim Kent    Richard Brodie     Jim Gettys

Who is an American game inventor, sometimes referred to by fans as "The Official Grand Old Man of Card Games"?
Robert Abbott     Cathy Hudgins    Bob Velke    Shawn Bayern

Who is a prominent scientist working in the area of operational research and management science?
Robert Fourer    Robert Tappan Morris    Jon Phillips    Ken Thompson

Who is a computer scientist. His areas of expertise include multiprocessing and embedded systems?
Robert Iannucci    Gary Kildall    Ric Weiland    Doug Lea

Who is an American computer scientist, best known for creating the Morris Worm in 1988, considered the first computer worm on the Internet—and subsequently becoming the first person convicted under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act?
Robert Tappan Morris    David Ungar    Jeremy Sagan    Kelley Deal

Who is one of the 3 founders of the Extreme Programming (XP) software development methodology circa 1996, along with Kent Beck and Ward Cunningham?
Ron Jeffries    Martin Roesch    Richard Wallace     Joseph Primiani

Who is a computer programmer who worked for the Nevada Gaming Control Board in the early 1990s and was responsible for finding flaws and gaffes in software that runs computerized casino games?
Ronald Dale Harris    Alistair Cockburn    Wayne Bell     Virgil Griffith

Who is the cofounder of BitTorrent Inc along with brother Bram Cohen, where among other things he was involved in the Codeville project?
Ross Cohen    Alan Kay    Joe Hewitt     Greg Skibiski

Who is an American computer programmer. He was a founding board member of the Open Source Initiative and briefly served as its president in 200?
Russ Nelson    Dominic Giampaolo    Samuel Genensky    Declan McCullagh

Who is a security researcher, possibly best known for creating the Evercookie and the MySpace worm Samy (XSS), as well as his discovery that the Apple iPhone, Google Android and Microsoft Windows Phone mobile devices transmit GPS and Wi-Fi information to their parent companies?
Samy Kamkar    Bill Joy    Havoc Pennington    Brian d foy

Who is a corporate vice president in the Microsoft Developer Division. He is best known for his work on ASP.NET, which he and colleague Mark Anders developed while at Microsoft?
Scott Guthrie    John Mashey    Shawn Fanning    Earl Isaac

Who is an American author and software consultant, specializing in the C++ computer programming language?
Scott Meyers    Jeremy Sagan    Martin Roesch    Nathaniel Borenstein

Who is the co-founder and head developer of Cerulean Studios, a company responsible for creating Trillian, a popular instant messaging client?
Scott Werndorfer    Dave Hyatt    Elizabeth Rather    Narendra Rocherolle

Who is an American law professor.  Before his legal career, he created several widely used computer-software systems and wrote several widely cited books on computer programming?
Shawn Bayern    Brantley Coile    Narendra Rocherolle    Bob Velke

Who is an American computer programmer, serial entrepreneur, and angel investor?
Shawn Fanning    Mark Pilgrim     Roger Powell     Wayne Chang

Who is the co-founder of ParaGraph Intl., Parascript, Evernote Corp?
Stepan Pachikov    Chris Lattner    Angela Byron    Stu Moment

Who is an American inventor, computer engineer and programmer who co-founded Apple Computer (now Apple Inc.) with Steve Jobs and Ronald Wayne?
Steve Wozniak    Trung Dung    Paul Buchheit    Jim Kent

Who is a former Intel executive best known as a witness in the Microsoft antitrust trial.  His notes contained colorful quotes by Microsoft executives threatening to "cut off Netscape's air supply" and Bill Gates' guess that "this anti-trust thing will blow over"?
Steven McGeady    Jason Rohrer    Christopher Weaver    Bruce Carver

Who is a notable figure in high technology management.  He was an early employee of Microsoft where he was Microsoft's first business unit general manager, leading the Development Tool Business?
Steven Snyder    Robert Tappan Morris    Scott Meyers    Aaron Boucher

Who is an information technology industry analyst and prominent free and open source software (FOSS) advocate, promoting business use of FOSS?
Stormy Peters    LaFarr Stuart    Qi Lu    Cathy Hudgins

Who is a software developer and pilot.  Along with Bruce Artwick, he created the subLOGIC Corporation while he was at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign?
Stu Moment    Michael Scandizzo    Chris Roberts     Bruce Carver

Who is a Hungarian-born American entrepreneur. He is the founder and head of Interactive Brokers (Nasdaq: IBKR) and played a key role in founding the Boston Options Exchange?
Thomas Peterffy    Charles Simonyi    Dave Hyatt    Gary Martin 

Who is an American computer programmer, best known as the original author of MS-DOS, the most widely used personal computer operating system in the 1980s?
Tim Paterson    Doug Lea    Carl Hewitt    David Ungar

Who is an American computer programmer and entrepreneur. He was a co-founder of Intuit and a pioneer of usability testing in the 1980s?
Tom Proulx    Rich Skrenta    Brendan Eich    Lukas Biewald

Who is an American computer software enginee?
Tom Van Vleck    Brad Fitzpatrick    Aaron Swartz    Silas Warner

Who is a Vietnamese-American businessman. His life story has been profiled in many leading publications including Forbes, Financial Times, The Wall Street Journal and San Francisco Chronicle, as well as in Dan Rather's book The American Dream?
Trung Dung    Michael Deering    Chris Lattner    Ward Christensen

Who is a Professor of Computer Science at the University of California, Berkeley. He also works as an Internet researcher based at the International Computer Science Institute in Berkeley, California?
Vern Paxson    Mark Harris     Daniel Kottke    Mark Zuckerberg

Who is an American hacker, known for his involvement in a 2003 lawsuit with Blackboard Inc?
Virgil Griffith    Ronald Dale Harris    Brad Fitzpatrick    David Maynard

Who is an American computer programmer who developed the first wiki?
Ward Cunningham    Scott Werndorfer    Joe Hewitt     Silas Warner

Who is an American entrepreneur. He is best known for founding Crashlytics that, in a little over a year, was acquired by Twitter for over $100 million in 2013, creating i2hub, a popular filesharing network, and his lawsuit against the Winklevoss brothers, famously depicted in The Social Network movie?
Wayne Chang    Qi Lu    Trung Dung    Bruce Carver

Who is an American computer scientist and entrepreneur best known for his innovations in Internet, entertainment, telecommunications, virtual workforce, and energy efficiency technologies?
Wendell Brown    Ilya Zhitomirskiy    Bram Cohen    Shawn Fanning

Who is a Macintosh software developer, best known for co-founding and heading The Omni Group in 1991, where he did consulting work and developed software for the NeXTSTEP operating system, Rhapsody and later Mac OS X?
Wil Shipley    Ken Schwaber    Andrew Fluegelman    Paul Allen

