What is the Association for Computing Machinery's Special Interest Group on programming language?
ACM SIGPLAN Programming Languages Software Award    Calgary Challenge    Turing Award    Presburger Award

What is an annual award that honors people or an organization "for developing a software system that has had a lasting influence, reflected in contributions to concepts, in commercial acceptance, or both"?
ACM Software System Award    Jon Postel    Fulkerson Prize    Knuth Prize

What is a class of data compression algorithms that allows the exact original data to be reconstructed from the compressed data?
Calgary Challenge    Knuth Prize    Machtey Award    EATCS Award

What is a computer program designed to simulate an intelligent conversation with one or more human users via auditory or textual methods, primarily for engaging in small talk?
Chatterbox Challenge    Gerard Salton Award    EATCS Award    SIGCOMM Award

What is a group of researchers honored by SIGCHI, the Special Interest Group in Computer–Human Interaction of the Association for Computing Machinery?
CHI Academy    Chatterbox Challenge    Loebner Prize    Lovelace Medal

What is an academic conference in the field of theoretical computer science?
Danny Lewin Best Student Paper Award    Knuth Prize    Pirelli Internetional Award    Hutter Prize

What is an international award sponsored by the Digital Preservation Coalition?
Digital Preservation Award    Lovelace Medal    Dijkstra Prize    Gödel Prize

What is an international organization with a European focus, founded in 1972. Its aim is to facilitate the exchange of ideas and results among theoretical computer scientists as well as to stimulate cooperation between the theoretical and the practical community in computer science?
EATCS Award    Gordon Bell Prize    Knuth Prize    White Camel award

What area of discrete mathematics is sponsored jointly by the Mathematical Programming Society (MPS)  and the American Mathematical Society (AMS)?
Fulkerson Prize    EATCS Award    IJCAI Award for Research Excellence    Pirelli Internetional Award

What is presented by the Association for Computing Machinery (ACM) Special Interest Group on Information Retrieval (SIGIR) every three years to an individual who has made "significant, sustained and continuing contributions to research in information retrieval"?
Gerard Salton Award    Gerard Salton Award    Jon Postel    Lovelace Medal

What is a prize for outstanding papers in theoretical computer science, named after Kurt Gödel and awarded jointly by the European Association for Theoretical Computer Science (EATCS) and the Association for Computing Machinery Special Interest Group on Algorithms and Computation Theory (ACM SIGACT)?
Gödel Prize    Tsutomu Kanai Award    Konrad Zuse Medal    Gödel Prize

What is an award presented by the Association for Computing Machinery each year in conjunction with the SC Conference series (formerly known as the Supercomputing Conference)?
Gordon Bell Prize    Gerard Salton Award    SIGCOMM Award    Nevanlinna Prize

What is a cash prize funded by Marcus Hutter which rewards data compression improvements on a specific 100 MB English text file?
Hutter Prize    Gerard Salton Award    Dijkstra Prize    Ken Kennedy Award

What is a biannual award given at the IJCAI conference to researcher in artificial intelligence as a recognition of excellence of their career?
IJCAI Award for Research Excellence    John von Neumann Theory Prize    White Camel award    Turing Award

What is a prize for outstanding contributions to the foundations of computer science, named after Donald E?
Knuth Prize    Paris Kanellakis Award    Lovelace Medal    Digital Preservation Award

What is the highest award of the Gesellschaft für Informatik (the German Computer Science Society), given every two years to one or sometimes two leading German computer scientists?
Konrad Zuse Medal    Chatterbox Challenge    Grace Murray Hopper Award    Grace Murray Hopper Award

What is an annual competition in artificial intelligence that awards prizes to the chatterbot considered by the judges to be the most human-like?
Loebner Prize    Loebner Prize    Gerard Salton Award    Machtey Award

What is a theoretical computer science prize given awarded for  outstanding papers in the area of multivariate algorithmics?
Nerode Prize    White Camel award    Sidney Fernbach Award    Ken Kennedy Award

What is awarded once every 4 years at the International Congress of Mathematicians, for outstanding contributions in Mathematical Aspects of Information Sciences includin?
Nevanlinna Prize    Nerode Prize    Sloan Fellowship    Herbrand Award

What is awarded each year by the European Association for Theoretical Computer Science (EATCS) to "a young scientist for outstanding contributions in theoretical computer science, documented by a published paper or a series of published papers." The award is named after Mojzesz Presburger who accomplished his path-breaking work on decidability of the theory of addition (which today is called Presburger arithmetic) as a student in 192?
Presburger Award    Seymour Cray Computer Engineering Award    Grace Murray Hopper Award    ACM SIGPLAN Programming Languages Software Award

What is an award given by the IEEE Computer Society, to recognize significant and innovative contributions in the field of high-performance computing?
Seymour Cray Computer Engineering Award    EATCS Award    Konrad Zuse Medal    Loebner Prize

What is awarded annually by the Alfred P. Sloan Foundation since 1955 to "provide support and recognition to early-career scientists and scholars"?
Sloan Fellowship    Gödel Prize    Knuth Prize    CHI Academy

What is a software engineering award given in memory of Wayne Stevens. The international  was created to recognize outstanding contributions to the literature or practice of methods for softwis and systems development?
Stevens Award    Turing Award    Fulkerson Prize    Sidney Fernbach Award

What is an annual award for outstanding contributions to the field of information retrieval and is presented in memory of Dr Tony Kent, a past Fellow of the Institute of Information Scientists (IIS), who died in 1997. Tony Kent made a major contribution to the development of information science and information services both in the UK and internationally, particularly in the field of chemistry?
Tony Kent Strix award    Knuth Prize    Presburger Award    SIGCOMM Award

What is an annual prize given by the Association for Computing Machinery (ACM) to "an individual selected for contributions of a technical nature made to the computing community"?
Turing Award    Gordon Bell Prize    Calgary Challenge    Pirelli Internetional Award

What is given to important contributors to the Perl Programming Language community?
White Camel award    Tsutomu Kanai Award    Nerode Prize    Danny Lewin Best Student Paper Award

