What is an iconic series of robotic pets designed and manufactured by Sony?
AIBO    FlyTech Dragonfly    RoboSapien    Robopet

What is a modified mini-fridge that catapults beer to the desired drinker by use of a keyless remote system?
Beer Launching Fridge    Tux Droid    Tux Droid    Sony Rolly

What is a robot built primarily with Lego Mindstorms and a Samsung Galaxy S2 for solving a Rubik's Cube?
CubeStormer II    Robopanda    Robopanda    CubeStormer II

What is, as the name indicates, a robot that is not made for utilitarian use, as in production or domestic services, but for the sole subjective pleasure of the human it serves, usually the owner or his housemates, guests or clients?
Entertainment robot    FlyTech Dragonfly    Milton Bradley Playmate    Hexbug

What is a female humanoid robot that WowWee announced at CES in January 2008. It can respond to sight, sound, and touch and can be programmed with a sequence of movements?
FemiSapien    Spykee    RS Media    PaPeRo

What is WowWee's entry into remote-controlled flying toy industry. The Dragonfly has been incorrectly billed as the world's first commercially available RC ornithopter (flapping wing aircraft)?
FlyTech Dragonfly    Robopet    Entertainment robot    Kota the triceratops

What is an electronic robotic toy resembling a hamster or owl-like creature which went through a period of being a "must-have" toy following its launch in the holiday season of 1998, with continual sales until 2000. Over 40 million Furbies were sold during the three years of its original production, with 1.8 million sold in 1998, and 14 million in 1999. Its speaking capabilities were translated into 24 languages?
Furby    Entertainment robot    Sarcoman    Entertainment robot

What is a robotic dog produced by the Korean company Dasarobot of Dasatec?
Genibo    Genibo    CubeStormer II    WowWee Alive Chimpanzee

What is an undertaking by Canadian inventor Jaimie Mantzel to construct a large 6-legged robot?
Giant Robot Project    FemiSapien    Pleo    Giant Robot Project

What is a brand of toy automatons developed and distributed by Innovation First.   was inspired by BEAM robotics, and uses many elements of it?
Hexbug    Nabaztag    Pekoppa    Hexbug

What is a robot dog toy designed and manufactured by Sega Toys, marketed by Hasbro in the United States?
IDog    Giant Robot Project    FlyTech Dragonfly    RoboSapien

What is an animatronic toy dinosaur made by Hasbro and Playskool. It is modeled after a triceratops, and intended for children aged 3 to ?
Kota the triceratops    Robosapien v2    Robosapien v2    FlyTech Dragonfly

What are transforming robotic dinosaurs.   is owned by Mike West and Transaurus is owned by Rick and Sheri Dorritie?
Megasaurus    Push the Talking Trash Can    AIBO    Robopanda

What is a personal robot developed by Japanese firm NEC Corporation?
PaPeRo    Roboboa    Zhu Zhu Pets    FlyTech Dragonfly

What is a battery-powered plastic plant, manufactured by Sega, which reacts with nodding movements when being spoken to?
Pekoppa    RoboSapien    Robosapien v2    Tux Droid

What is the largest order in the fungal class Dothideomycetes.  By some estimates it contains 23 families, 332 genera and more than 4700 species?
Pleo    Pleo    Hexbug    Milton Bradley Playmate

What is a radio-controlled robot, created by Daniel Deutsch, which makes daily rounds throughout Tomorrowland inside the Magic Kingdom theme park at Walt Disney World in Orlando, Florida; Disneyland and Disney California Adventure Park park in Anaheim, California, Hong Kong Disneyland park as well as Disneyland Paris outside Paris, France and Tokyo Disneyland in Japan?
Push the Talking Trash Can    Tux Droid    WowWee Alive Chimpanzee    Roboquad

What is a robotic snake produced by WowWee. s has 4 angled body sections, allowing  to coil by rotating adjacent sections?
Roboboa    Roboquad    Robosaurus    Nabaztag

What is a robotic interactive companion produced by WowWee. The  uses interchangeable cartridges that contain personalities, stories and songs, and is controlled directly by touch and sound sensors?
Robopanda    Robopet    Furby    Entertainment robot

What is a robotic dog produced by WowWee that is based on the biomorphic work of Mark W. Tilden?
Robopet    RS Media    Spykee    Genibo

What is one of the 5 robots that WowWee announced at CES in January 2007. It is a 4-legged robot that somewhat resembles a spider and a dog?
Roboquad    Push the Talking Trash Can    FlyTech Dragonfly    Beer Launching Fridge

What is a robotic toy invented by Mark Tilden and distributed by Wow Wee Toys International. It is the successor to the RoboSapien robot and uses motion technology based on realistic biomechanics that give it fluid and natural movements?
Roboraptor    IDog    CubeStormer II    CubeStormer II

What is a toy-like biomorphic robot designed by Mark Tilden and produced by WowWee toys. The  is preprogrammed with moves, and also can be controlled by an infrared remote control included with the toy, or by either a personal computer equipped with an infrared transmitter or an infrared transmitter-equipped PDA?
RoboSapien    FemiSapien    IDog    Pekoppa

What is the second generation of Mark Tilden's Robosapien robot. It is nearly twice the size of the original robot, standing around  tall?
Robosapien v2    Robopet    Roboboa    Pleo

What is a transforming dinosaur robot created by inventor Doug Malewicki in 1989 and is now owned and operated by Monster Robots, Inc?
Robosaurus    Entertainment robot    Roboraptor    RoboSapien

What is another product in WowWee's line of biomorphic robots, based on a walking system designed by Mark Tilden?
RS Media    Megasaurus    RoboSapien    Spykee

What is an entertainment robot remotely controlled by a human operator (For example, an appropriately trained comedian)?
Sarcoman    Megasaurus    RS Media    RS Media

What is an egg-shaped digital robotic music player made by Sony, combining music functions with robotic dancing?
Sony Rolly    Pleo    Sony Rolly    Genibo

What is a robotic toy made by Erector/Meccano. It contains a USB webcam, microphone and speakers. Controlled by computer locally or over the internet, the owner can move the robot to various locations within range of the local router, take pictures and video, listen to surroundings with the on-board microphone and play sounds/music or various built-in recordings (Robot laugh, laser guns, etc.) through the speaker?
Spykee    FlyTech Dragonfly    Roboreptile    Genibo

What is a Linux wireless Tux mascot (210mm x 180mm x 140mm - with lowered wings) with a programmable interface, allowing it to announce events by its gestures and by ALSA driven sound?
Tux Droid    Sony Rolly    Entertainment robot    Roboreptile

What is produced by WowWee Alive, a division of WowWee Ltd. The animatronic Chimpanzee is the first in WowWee Alive's product line?
WowWee Alive Chimpanzee    FemiSapien    Beer Launching Fridge    Sarcoman

What is an American line of plush robotic hamster toys, created by Cepia LLC in 2009. They were a craze during the 2009 Christmas season holidays?
Zhu Zhu Pets    FemiSapien    PaPeRo    Roboraptor

