What is a film directed by Henry King starring John Hodiak and Gene Tierney. The film was adapted from the novel by John Hersey, which won the Pulitzer Prize in 1945. In his 1945 review of the film, Bosley Crowther wrote, "..?
A Bell for Adano     The Shocking Miss Pilgrim     Ladies in Love     The Three Musketeers 

What is an 1889 novel by American humorist and writer Mark Twain?
A Connecticut Yankee     The Littlest Rebel     Grand Canary     The Snake Pit 

What is a silent film. The film was controversial because of the sequences of what was regarded as superfluous nudity by the main character, Nydia, played by Australian swimming star Annette Kellerman?
A Daughter of the Gods    Song of the Islands     Call Her Savage     The Beautiful Blonde from Bashful Bend 

What is any object or structure that creates a barrier or obstacle to control, block passage or force the flow of traffic in the desired direction?
Barricade     Song of the Islands     Call Her Savage     The Snake Pit 

What is a town square in the West End of London, England, in the City of Westminster. It was originally laid out in the mid 18th century by architect William Kent?
Berkeley Square     Tess of the Storm Country     Heidi     The Shocking Miss Pilgrim 

What is a Pre-Code drama film directed by John Francis Dillon and starring Clara Bow?
Call Her Savage     Crash Dive     Barricade     The Lights of New York 

What is a procession or parade on horseback, or a mass trail ride by a company of riders.  The focus of a cavalcade is participation rather than display; often, the participants do not wear costumes or ride in formation?
Cavalcade     Under Your Spell     Wing and a Prayer     The Cowboy and The Countess 

What is the fifth novel in the Charlie Chan series by Earl Derr Bigger?
Charlie Chan Carries On     Street Angel     Tail Spin     Dragonwyck 

What is a song co-written by David Bowie and Iggy Pop during their years in Berlin, first appearing on Pop's album The Idiot (1977)?
China Girl     Cameo Kirby     My Gal Sal     Man Trouble 

What is a 1945 Technicolor musical film starring Betty Grable, directed by George Seaton, and released by 20th Century Fox?
Diamond Horseshoe     Pilgrimage     The Black Swan     High Society Blues 

What is a small natural indentation in the flesh on a part of the human body, most notably in the cheek or on the chin?
Dimples     Captain January     This Above All     Yankee Senor 

What is a wicked or rebellious angel. The term is found neither in the Hebrew Bible nor the Deuterocanonical Books nor the New Testament?
Fallen Angel     Second Honeymoon     This Above All     Under Your Spell 

What is a point of entry or exi?
Gateway     Fifty Roads to Town     King of Burlesque     The Magnificent Dope 

What is the second most populous island of the Canary Islands, a Spanish archipelago, with a population of 838,397 which constitutes approximately 40% of the population of the archipelago?
Grand Canary     A Bell for Adano     Love Is News     Cleopatra 

What issued on that label's Tamla Records subsidiary label (T54073)?
Happy Landing     The Dolly Sisters     Sunny Side Up     The Littlest Rebel 

What is a Swiss work of fiction, originally published in two parts as Heidi's years of learning and travel () and makes use of what she has learned?
Heidi     The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes     Ramona     My Darling Clementine 

What is a film starring Janet Gaynor and Charles Farrell. The movie was written by Howard J?
High Society Blues     The Snake Pit     Little Miss Broadway     Green Grass of Wyoming 

What is an American professional wrestler. Bynum is best known for her stint in Total Nonstop Action Wrestling under the name Sojournor Bolt (or "Sojo Bolt" for short)?
Josette     That Wonderful Urge     Diamond Horseshoe     Miracle on 34th Street 

What is a romantic comedy film directed by Edward H. Griffith and starring Janet Gaynor, Constance Bennett and Loretta Young?
Ladies in Love     Captain from Castile     The Lights of New York     Gateway 

What are the laurel family, that includes the "True Laurel" and its closest relatives. The family comprises over 3000 species of flowering plants in over 50 genera world-wide?
Laura     The Pied Piper     Pilgrimage     East Lynne 

What is an American musical film. The only known footage to survive is a 12-minute fragment from the final reel in Multicolor at UCLA Film and Television Archive?
Married in Hollywood     A Daughter of the Gods    Liliom     Heidi 

What is a 1947 Christmas film written and directed by George Seaton and based on a story by Valentine Davies?
Miracle on 34th Street     The Beautiful Blonde from Bashful Bend     Love Is News     Dragonwyck 

What is a 20th Century Fox musical starring Rita Hayworth and Victor Mature. The film is a biopic of 1890s composer and songwriter Paul Dresser and singer Sally Elliot?
My Gal Sal     China Girl     Sunrise     To the Shores of Tripoli 

What is a 1965 war film starring Frank Sinatra, Clint Walker, Tatsuya Mihashi, Tommy Sands and Brad Dexter?
None But the Brave     Delicious     The Black Swan     One in a Million 

What is a journey or search of  moral or spiritual significance. Typically, it is a journey to a shrine or other location of importance to a person's beliefs and faith, although sometimes it can be a metaphorical journey into someone's own beliefs?
Pilgrimage     The Cowboy and The Countess     Guadalcanal Diary     The Joy Girl 

What is a model whose mass-produced pictures see wide appeal as popular culture?
Pin Up Girl     Captain January     Guadalcanal Diary     Miracle on 34th Street 

What is an annual competitive and recreational gathering of a U.S. state's population, usually held in late summer or early fall?
State Fair     Happy Landing     Stowaway     A Connecticut Yankee 

What is a person who secretly boards a vehicle, such as an aircraft, bus, ship, cargo truck or train, to travel without paying and without being detected?
Stowaway     The Joy Girl     Wake Up and Dream     Crash Dive 

What is a seaport city (population ca. 497,000) in north-eastern Egypt, located on the north coast of the Gulf of (a branch of the Red Sea), near the southern terminus of the Canal, having the same boundaries as governorate?
Suez     Anna and the King of Siam     The Littlest Rebel     Footlight Serenade 

What is the instant at which the upper edge of the Sun appears over the eastern horizon in the morning?
Sunrise     Midnight     Miracle on 34th Street     That Lady in Ermine 

What is the common name for Cygnus atratus, an Australasian waterfow?
The Black Swan     In Old Chicago     None But the Brave     State Fair 

What areas from the end of World War II in 1945 until the end of the Cold War in 1991. The term symbolized efforts by the Soviet Union to block itself and its dependent and central European allies off from open contact with the west and non-communist areas?
The Iron Curtain     Berkeley Square     Happy Days     The Cowboy and The Countess 

What is an iconic literary term (currently transitioning into an archaic reference) originating in the early Victorian culture (1825–35) when horses still powered most machinery, excepting windmills and stationary steam engines, the term was common and popular in both British and North American literary articles?
The Iron Horse     Fifty Roads to Town     Barricade     Song of the Islands 

What is an American silent comedy film starring Olive Borden, and based on the novel of the same name by May Edginton?
The Joy Girl     Springtime in the Rockies     Sunny Side Up     The Lights of New York 

What is a 1942 comedy film. As a publicity stunt, a down-on-his-luck success school operator searches for the least promising man in America to take his course?
The Magnificent Dope     A Message to Garcia     Judge Priest     The Black Swan 

What is the subject of a legend concerning the departure or death of a great number of children from the town of Hamelin (Hameln), Lower Saxony, Germany, in the Middle Ages?
The Pied Piper     The Magnificent Dope     A Letter to Three Wives     The Song of Bernadette 

What is a novel by Alexandre Dumas, first serialized in March–July 1844. Set in the 17th century, it recounts the adventures of a young man named d'Artagnan after he leaves home to travel to Paris, to join the Musketeers of the Guard?
The Three Musketeers     Midnight     A Letter to Three Wives     Wing and a Prayer 

What is a novel by Eric Knight. It was adapted into an Academy Award winning movie in 194?
This Above All     The Iron Horse     In Old Arizona     Springtime in the Rockies 

What is the seventh episode of the sixth season of the fantasy television show Buffy the Vampire Slayer (1997–2003) and the only one in the series performed as a musical?
Under Your Spell     Delicious     Hearts in Dixie     Tess of the Storm Country 

What is a swirling body of water produced by the meeting of opposing currents. The vast majority of whirlpools are not very powerful?
Whirlpool     High Society Blues     The Iron Curtain     Mother Wore Tights 

What is a black-and-white 1944 war film about the heroic crew of an American carrier in the desperate early days of World War II in the Pacific theater, directed by Henry Hathaway and starring Dana Andrews and Don Ameche?
Wing and a Prayer     The Story of Alexander Graham Bell     Bright Eyes     Stowaway 

