What is the state of experiencing humorous and entertaining events or situations, and is associated with enjoyment, happiness, laughter and pleasure?
 Amusements    Pirates Cove     Aquatica Florida    Riverside Amusement Park 

What is a Filipino comics creator, writer and illustrato?
Adventure Kingdom     Riverside Amusement Park     Chankanaab Park    Valle Fantastico

What is a Mexican zoo park that was established in 1972 by Captain Carlos Camacho Espíritu. It is located about  from the city of Puebla?
Africam Safari    Dry Town Water Park    Thunder Road     Parque de Diversiones

What is a chain of water parks owned and operated by SeaWorld Parks & Entertainment. Aquatica parks are operating in Orlando, Florida and San Antonio, Texas, with a third location set to open in Chula Vista, California in 201?
Aquatica Florida    Old Town     Xcaret Park    Riverfront Park 

What is a chain of water parks owned and operated by SeaWorld Parks & Entertainment. Aquatica parks are operating in Orlando, Florida and San Antonio, Texas, with a third location set to open in Chula Vista, California in 201?
Aquatica San Antonio    Riverfront Park     Aquatica San Antonio    Full Blast 

What is located on U.S. Route 22 West in Scotch Plains, New Jersey?
Bowcraft Amusement Park     Amusements    Adventure Kingdom      Amusements

What is a water park operated by the city of Palmdale, California, opened in 2006. It is located on the grounds of the Palmdale Oasis Park & Recreation Center in the southeast portion of the city?
Dry Town Water Park    Islands of Adventure    Africam Safari    Full Blast 

What is a forest under, or containing, enchantments. Such forests are described in the oldest folklore from regions where forests are common, and occur throughout the centuries to modern works of fantasy?
Enchanted Forest     Historic Bushkill Park    Scandia Amusements    Adventureland 

What issues, reopened May 23, 2009, under the Freestyle brand,  and closed yet again after its 2009 season?
Freestyle Music Park    Big Splash     Storyland     Old Town 

What is a small family amusement park located in Angola, Indiana, USA. Although it was small in comparison to parks in neighboring states, such as Cedar Point and Michigan's Adventure, it remained one of the largest parks in the region?
Fun Spot     Big Splash     Pyrite Rapids Water Park    Belmont Park 

What is located in Northeastern Pennsylvania just outside of the city of Easton. It is a small amusement park, generally geared toward younger audiences?
Historic Bushkill Park    Big Splash     Turtle Farm    Adventure Island 

What is a theme park located in Orlando, Florida?
Islands of Adventure    Enchanted Island     Enchanted Forest     Dry Town Water Park

What is a  ski resort located in Ludlow, Vermont. Before becoming a popular ski resort destination, Ludlow was originally a mill town, and was the home of a General Electric plant until 1977. The resort experienced 600,000 skier visits in 2009. Parents Magazine rated it the Top US Family Snow Resort?
Okemo Mountain    Thunder Road     Big Splash     Adventureland 

What is an amusement park located in San José, Costa Rica?
Parque de Diversiones    Wonderland Park     Parque de Diversiones    Full Blast 

What is a board game designed by Paul Randles and Daniel Stahl, and published in Europe in 2002 by Amigo Spiele and in the United States in 2003 by Days of Wonder?
Pirates Cove     Turtle Farm    Aquatica San Antonio    Village Vacances Valcartier 

What is a chain of Scandinavian-themed family amusement centers in California, including three locations: Scandia Fun Center in Sacramento, Scandia Family Fun Center in Victorville, and Scandia Amusement Park in Ontario?
Scandia Amusements    Pyrite Rapids Water Park    Centreville Amusement Park at Toronto Islands    Dry Town Water Park

What is the practice of raising turtles and tortoises of various species commercially. Raised animals are sold for use as gourmet food, traditional medicine ingredients, or as pets?
Turtle Farm    Storyland     Big Splash     Centreville Amusement Park at Toronto Islands

What is a privately owned and operated theme park, resort and self-described ecotourism development located in the Riviera Maya, a portion of the Caribbean coastline of Mexico's state of Quintana Roo that has been designated as a zone for tourism development?
Xcaret Park    Ontario Place     Castle Park     Belmont Park 

