What is a logic puzzle game developed by Teyon for the Nintendo DSiWare. It is available in the Nintendo DSi Shop for 500 Nintendo DSi Points?
1001 Crystal Mazes Collection    Lonpos    THOG problem    MU puzzle

What is a logic puzzle which on first inspection seems to have insufficient information to solve, but which rewards those who persist and examine the puzzle critically?
Ages of Three Children puzzle    Logic maze    MindTrap    Heyawake

What is a binary-determination puzzle that was originally developed by Quadratic Games for the iPhone platform?
Atsumari     Sokoban    Str8ts    Isolate 

What is the capital of the Republic of Iraq, as well as the coterminous Baghdad Province. The population of Baghdad as of 2011 is approximately 7,216,040, making it the largest city in Iraq, the second largest city in the Arab World (after Cairo, Egypt), and the second largest city in Western Asia (after Tehran, Iran)?
Bag     Heyawake    Super Swap    Stained Glass 

What is a large armored warship with a main battery consisting of heavy caliber guns. During the late 19th and early 20th centuries the battleship was the most powerful type of warship, and a fleet of battleships was vital for any nation which desired to maintain command of the sea?
Battleship     Induction puzzles    Balance puzzle    Futoshiki

What is a logic puzzle that deals with four people, a bridge and a torch?
Bridge and torch problem    Trigon puzzle    Shikaku    Light Up

What is a logic puzzl?
Buchstabensalat     Bag     Four glasses puzzle    Ages of Three Children puzzle

What is an old code-breaking paper and pencil game for two players, predating the similar commercially marketed board game Mastermind?
Bulls and cows    Sudoku    THOG problem    1001 Crystal Mazes Collection

What is a single-player variation on the classic board game Clue, where a player is given a series of clues and must deduce where in the mansion each suspect should be and who is the killer?
Clue Suspects    Mutilated chessboard problem    Keisuke     Bulls and cows

What is a game that incorporates the popular Japanese number slotting game Sudoku with crossword puzzles?
Crosswordoku    Atsumari     KenKen    Truel

What is a type of logic puzzle published by many publishers.  Other published titles for the puzzle include Allied Occupation?
Fillomino    Sokoban    Logic maze    Nurikabe

What is a logic puzzle first publicised by Martin Gardner in his "Mathematical Games" column in the February 1979 edition of Scientific American?
Four glasses puzzle    Logic puzzle    Monkey and banana problem    Kuromasu

What is a binary-determination logic puzzl?
Goishi Hiroi    Super Swap    Train shunting puzzle    Keisuke 

What is a binary-determination logic puzzle published by Nikol?
Gokigen Naname    Survo puzzle    Kakuro    Logic puzzle

What is a type of logic puzzle published by Nikoli?
Hashiwokakero    Ages of Three Children puzzle    Light Up    Sudoku

What is a binary-determination logic puzzle published by Nikoli?
Heyawake    Lasertank    Lights Out     Slitherlink

What is a logic puzzle game invented by Dr. Gyora Benedek, an Israeli mathematician?
Hidato    Missionaries and cannibals problem    River crossing puzzle    Nonogram

What is a type of logic puzzle published by Nikoli?
Hitori    Heyawake    Four glasses puzzle    Light Up

What is a binary-determination logic puzzle published by Nikol?
Hotaru Beam    Goishi Hiroi    Gokigen Naname    Lights Out 

What are logic puzzles which are solved via the application of the principle of induction?
Induction puzzles    Takuzu    1001 Crystal Mazes Collection    Ripple Effect 

What is a type of logic puzzle published by Nikol?
Inshi no heya    Nikoli    Missionaries and cannibals problem    Navigrid

What is a French logic puzzle and a word puzzle on grid created in 2006 and inspired by Picross?
Izukirudo    Atsumari     Light Up    Mutilated chessboard problem

What is a kind of logic puzzle that is often referred to as a mathematical transliteration of the crossword?
Kakuro    Missing dollar riddle    Yajilin    Zebra Puzzle

What are trademarked names for a style of arithmetic and logic puzzle invented in 2004 by Japanese math teacher Tetsuya Miyamoto, who intends the puzzles to be an instruction-free method of training the brain?
KenKen    Nurikabe    1001 Crystal Mazes Collection    Truel

What is a puzzle that combines elements of sudoku and kakuro?
Killer sudoku    Fillomino    Mutilated chessboard problem    Light Up

What is a type of logic puzzl?
Knights and Knaves    Light Up    Goishi Hiroi    Str8ts

What is a binary-determination logic puzzle published by Nikoli. As of 2005, one book consisting entirely of  puzzles has been published by Nikoli?
Kuromasu    Ages of Three Children puzzle    Heyawake    Kuromasu

What is a computer puzzle game requiring logical thinking to solve a variety of levels?
Lasertank    Wason selection task    Lights Out     Knights and Knaves

What is a binary-determination logic puzzle published by Nikoli?
Light Up    Balance puzzle    Wason selection task    Train shunting puzzle

What is a binary determination puzzle published by Nikol?
LITS    The Hardest Logic Puzzle Ever    Lonpos    Wason selection task

What are logic puzzles with all the aspects of a tour puzzle that fall outside of the scope of a typical maze?
Logic maze    Nonogram    Knights and Knaves    Ages of Three Children puzzle

What is a puzzle deriving from the mathematics field of deductio?
Logic puzzle    Fillomino    Ages of Three Children puzzle    Robot Rescue

What is a type of logic puzzle designed and published by Nikoli?
Masyu    Mastermind     Ripple Effect     Light Up

What is a series of lateral thinking puzzle games played by two individuals or teams. Invented in Canada, it is the main product of   Games, Inc., who license the game for manufacture by various companies including Outset Media, Blue Opal, the Great American Puzzle Factory, Pressman Toy Corporation, Spears Games and Winning Moves?
MindTrap    Hidato    Goishi Hiroi    Keisuke 

What is a famous toy problem in artificial intelligence, particularly in logic programming and planning?
Monkey and banana problem    Goishi Hiroi    Logic puzzle    1001 Crystal Mazes Collection

What is a puzzle stated by Douglas Hofstadter and found in Gödel, Escher, Bach. As stated, it is an example of a Post canonical system and can be reformulated as a string rewriting system?
MU puzzle    Bridge and torch problem    Yajilin    MU puzzle

What is a tiling puzzle proposed by philosopher Max Black in his book Critical Thinking (1946)?
Mutilated chessboard problem    Hashiwokakero    Str8ts    MindTrap

What is a logic-based number-placement puzzle. The puzzler is provided with a set of movements which must be used to move between the numbers 1 to 9 in order starting with the number 1. A solved grid will contain each of the numbers 1 to 9. The puzzle setter provides a partially completed grid?
Navigrid    Wason selection task    Missing dollar riddle    Gokigen Naname

What is a Japanese publisher that specializes in games and, especially, logic puzzles?
Nikoli    Lasertank    Hotaru Beam    Futoshiki

What are picture logic puzzles in which cells in a grid must be colored or left blank according to numbers at the side of the grid to reveal a hidden picture?
Nonogram    Bridge and torch problem    Lasertank    Ripple Effect 

What is a type of logic puzzle involving finding paths to connect numbers in a gri?
Numberlink    Zebra Puzzle    Monkey and banana problem    Theseus and the Minotaur

What is a binary determination puzzle named for an invisible wall in Japanese folklore that blocks roads and delays foot travel?
Nurikabe    Goishi Hiroi    MU puzzle    Isolate 

What is a situation where, like the ever expanding ripples across water when an object is dropped into it, an effect from an initial state can be followed outwards incrementally?
Ripple Effect     Logic maze    Bag     Wason selection task

What is a type of transport puzzle in which the object is to carry items from one river bank to another?
River crossing puzzle    Sokoban    The Hardest Logic Puzzle Ever    Kakuro

What is a puzzle game developed by Teyon for the Nintendo DSi. It is available for download at the Nintendo DSi Shop for 200 Nintendo DSi Points?
Robot Rescue    Atsumari     Verbal arithmetic    Missionaries and cannibals problem

What is a village in County Offaly, Ireland.  It lies at the junction of the R491 regional road between Cloughjordan and Roscrea where it is joined by the R492.  According to the 2006 census the population is 591 persons?
Shinro    Takuzu    Goishi Hiroi    Super Swap

What is a logic puzzle developed by publisher Nikoli?
Slitherlink    Ripple Effect     Missing dollar riddle    Crosswordoku

What is a logic-based number-placement puzzle, invented by Jeff Widderich in 2008. It is distinct from, but shares some properties and rules with Sudoku?
Str8ts    Monkey and banana problem    Str8ts    Mastermind 

What is a logic-based, combinatorial number-placement puzzle. The objective is to fill a 9×9 grid with digits so that each column, each row, and each of the nine 3×3 sub-grids that compose the grid (also called "boxes", "blocks", "regions", or "sub-squares") contains all of the digits from 1 to 9. The puzzle setter provides a partially completed grid, which typically has a unique solution?
Sudoku    Bulls and cows    1001 Crystal Mazes Collection    Train shunting puzzle

What is an action puzzle game developed by Teyon for the Nintendo DSiWare. It is available in the Nintendo DSi Shop for 500 Nintendo DSi Points?
Super Swap    Shikaku    Mutilated chessboard problem    Monkey and banana problem

What is a kind of logic puzzle presented (in April 2006) and studied by Seppo Mustone?
Survo puzzle    MU puzzle    Stained Glass     Shinro

What is a logic-based number placement puzzle. The objective is to fill a (usually 10×10) grid with 1s and 0s, where there is an equal number of 1s and 0s in each row and column and no more than two of either number adjacent to each other?
Takuzu    Missionaries and cannibals problem    Hashiwokakero    Ripple Effect 

What is a hexagonal tile-based abstract game invented by Mike McManaway from New Zealand.  Each of the 56 different tiles in the set contains three lines, going from one edge of the tile to another?
Tantrix    The Hardest Logic Puzzle Ever    Killer sudoku    Izukirudo

What is a type of logic puzzle designed and published by Nikoli. The puzzle is based on Japanese tatami mats?
Tatamibari    Numberlink    Lasertank    Tetsuya Miyamoto

What is a logic puzzle invented by American philosopher and logician George Boolos and published in The Harvard Review of Philosophy in 1996. A translation in Italian was published earlier in the newspaper La Repubblica, under the title L'indovinello più difficile del mondo?
The Hardest Logic Puzzle Ever    Buchstabensalat     MindTrap    Bag 

What is a type of logic maze designed by Robert Abbott. In this maze, the player acts as Theseus, the legendary king of Athens who is attempting to escape the Labyrinth?
Theseus and the Minotaur    Four glasses puzzle    Induction puzzles    Mutilated chessboard problem

What is one of Peter Wason's logic puzzles, constructed to show some of the weaknesses in human thinking?
THOG problem    Buchstabensalat     Inshi no heya    Isolate 

What is a type of transport puzzle?
Train shunting puzzle    Tetsuya Miyamoto    Goishi Hiroi    Buchstabensalat 

What are logic puzzles created by Alan Fraser-Dackers for Trigon Puzzles Ltd and are published on their own website and by Dell Magazines?
Trigon puzzle    Tatamibari    Truel    TuxMathScrabble

What is a neologism for a duel among three opponents, in which players can fire at one another in an attempt to eliminate them while surviving themselves?
Truel    Nurikabe    Wason selection task    Verbal arithmetic

What is a math version of the classic word game Scrabble (Trademark of Hasbro) which challenges kids to construct compound equations and to consider multiple abstract possibilities?
TuxMathScrabble    Atsumari     Hitori    LITS

What is a type of mathematical game consisting of a mathematical equation among unknown numbers, whose digits are represented by letters?
Verbal arithmetic    Battleship     Clue Suspects    Isolate 

What is a logic puzzle devised by Peter Cathcart Wason in 1966. It is one of the most famous tasks in the study of deductive reasoning?
Wason selection task    Logic puzzle    Kakuro    Logic puzzle

What is a type of logic puzzle published by Nikoli.  It has been published in English under the name Arrow Ring, such as in the 2005 U.S?
Yajilin    Nikoli    MindTrap    Keisuke 

What is a well-known logic puzzle. It is often called Einstein's Puzzle or Einstein's Riddle because it is said to have been invented by Albert Einstein as a boy; it is sometimes claimed that only 2% of the population can solve it?
Zebra Puzzle    Hitori    Logic puzzle    Navigrid

