What is application software that records and processes accounting transactions within functional modules such as accounts payable, accounts receivable, payroll, and trial balance?
Accounting software    Genomics    Graphical user interface    Music

What is a service provided by ground-based controllers who direct aircraft on the ground and through controlled airspace?
Air traffic control    Trade    Numerical Analysis    Automatic Teller Machine

What is part of the so-called passenger service systems (PSS), which is applications supporting the direct contact with the passenger?
Airline reservations    Embedded system    Architecture    Air traffic control

What is the discovery and communication of meaningful patterns in data. Especially valuable in areas rich with recorded information, analytics relies on the simultaneous application of statistics, computer programming and operations research to quantify performance?
Analytics    Reverse auctions     Numerical Analysis    Drill

What is both the process and product of planning, designing, and construction?
Architecture    Trade    Air traffic control    Cheque

What is a process of buying and selling goods or services by offering them up for bid, taking bids, and then selling the item to the highest bidder?
Auctions     Instant messaging    Loader     Accounting software

What is embedded software with legally mandated safety and reliability concerns used in avionics?
Avionics software    Manufacturing    Medical software    Automatic Teller Machine

What is a financial institution and a financial intermediary that accepts deposits and channels those deposits into lending activities, either directly by loaning or indirectly through capital markets?
Banking    Loader     Management Information Systems    Management Information Systems

What is a financial market where participants can issue new debt, known as the primary market, or buy and sell debt securities, known as the Secondary market, usually in the form of bonds?
Bond market    Presentation program    Distributed control system    Architecture

What is any software or set of computer programs that are used by business users to perform various business functions?
Business software    Music sequencers    Medical software    Telemetry

What are the components that a telephone operator or telco uses to run its business operations towards customer?
Business Support Systems    Special effects for video and film    Distributed control system    Sea lane

What is the use of computer systems to assist in the creation, modification, analysis, or optimization of a design?
CAD    Banking    Business software    Avionics software

What is the whole system of an economy that constitutes an environment for business. The system includes legal, economic, political, social, cultural and technological systems that are in operation in any country?
Commerce    Telephony    Sea lane    Speech processing

What is a compiler that tries to minimize or maximize some attributes of an executable computer program?
Compiler optimization    Contact managers    Drill    Simulation

What is a computer program (or set of programs) that transforms source code written in a programming language (the source language) into another computer language (the target language, often having a binary form known as object code)?
Compilers    Management Information Systems    Loader     Telemetry

What is a block of arbitrary information, or resource for storing information, which is available to a computer program and is usually based on some kind of durable storage?
Computer file    Air traffic control    Spatial Visualization Ability    Instant messaging

What is a method where multiple tasks, also known as processes, are performed during the same period of time?
Computer multitasking    Sea lane    Credit cards    Network Management

What is a type of telecommunications network between data processing nodes for the purpose of data communications?
Computer network    Optical character recognition    Distributed control system    Genomics

What is a computer program, run on a single computer, or a network of computers, that attempts to simulate an abstract model of a particular system?
Computer simulation    Credit cards    Office suites    Computer file

What is a payment card issued to users as a system of payment. It allows the cardholder to pay for goods and services based on the holder's promise to pay for them?
Credit cards    Computer graphics    Accounting software    Laboratory information system

What is the practice and study of techniques for secure communication in the presence of third parties (called adversaries)?
Cryptography    Video games    Telemetry    Airline reservations

What is a hierarchical distributed naming system for computers, services, or any resource connected to the Internet or a private network?
Domain Name System    Computer graphics    Operating systems    Special effects for video and film

What is a tool fitted with a cutting tool attachment or driving tool attachment, usually a drill bit or driver bit, used for drilling holes in various materials or fastening various materials together with the use of fasteners?
Drill    Sciences    Genomics    Web server

What is the process of selecting and preparing written, visual, audible, and film media used to convey information through the processes of correction, condensation, organization, and other modifications performed with an intention of producing a correct, consistent, accurate, and complete work?
Editing    Contact managers    Animation    Animation

What is a category of software tools for designing electronic systems such as printed circuit boards and integrated circuits?
Electronic Design Automation    Accounting software    Spatial Visualization Ability    Interpreter 

What is a term encompassing several different types of voting, embracing both electronic means of casting a vote and electronic means of counting votes?
Electronic voting    Data mining closely related to database    Cheque    Video games

What is a computer system  designed for specific control functions within a larger system, often with real-time computing constraints?
Embedded system    Presentation program    Compilers    HVAC

What is the application of scientific, economic, social, and practical knowledge, in order to design, build, and maintain structures, machines, devices, systems, materials and processes?
Engineering    Engineering    MUD    Auctions 

What is the study of how people allocate their assets over time under conditions of certainty and uncertainty?
Finance    Manufacturing    Analytics    Drill

What is a central financial exchange where people can trade standardized futures contracts; that is, a contract to buy specific quantities of a commodity or financial instrument at a specified price with delivery set at a specified time in the future?
Futures market    Contact managers    Music sequencers    Office suites

What is a video gaming website that provides news, reviews, previews, downloads, and other information on certain video games?
Games    Spreadsheets    Cryptography    Business Support Systems

What is a discipline in genetics that applies recombinant DNA, DNA sequencing methods, and bioinformatics to sequence, assemble, and analyze the function and structure of genomes (the complete set of DNA within a single cell of an organism)?
Genomics    Operations Support System    Parsers    Logistics

What is a type of user interface that allows users to interact with electronic devices using images rather than text commands?
Graphical user interface    Computer simulation    Air traffic control    Speech processing

What is the ability of a computer to receive and interpret intelligible handwritten input from sources such as paper documents, photographs, touch-screens and other devices?
Handwriting recognition    Numerical Analysis    Futures market    Computer simulation

What is the technology of indoor and automotive environmental comfort?
HVAC    Engineering    Contact managers    Special effects for video and film

What is a form of communication over the Internet that offers quick transmission of text-based messages from sender to receiver?
Instant messaging    Reverse auctions     Training    Special effects for video and film

What is the facilitating of oral or sign-language communication, either simultaneously or consecutively, between users of different languages?
Interpreter     Medical software    Video games    Business Support Systems

What is a software-based laboratory and information management system that offers a set of key features that support a modern laboratory's operations?
Laboratory information system    Drill    Speech processing    Automatic Teller Machine

What is a computer program that takes one or more object files generated by a compiler and combines them into a single executable program?
Linker     Sciences    Compiler optimization    Engineering

What is the management of the flow of resources between the point of origin and the point of destination in order to meet some requirements, for example, of customers or corporations?
Logistics    Embedded system    CAD    Loader 

What is the production of goods for use or sale using labor and machines, tools, chemical and biological processing, or formulation?
Manufacturing    Finance    Reverse auctions     Presentation program

What is a multiplayer real-time virtual world, usually text-based?
MUD    Compiler optimization    World wide web    Distributed control system

What is an art form whose medium is sound and silence. Its common elements are pitch (which governs melody and harmony), rhythm (and its associated concepts tempo, meter, and articulation), dynamics, and the sonic qualities of timbre and texture?
Music    Computer graphics    Special effects for video and film    Banking

What is a device or application software that can record, edit, or play back music, by handling note and performance information in several forms, typically MIDI or CV/Gate, and possibly audio and automation data for DAWs and plug-ins?
Music sequencers    Knowledge management    Poker    Operating systems

What is a combination of hardwis and software used to monitor and administer a computer network or networks?
Network management system    Handwriting recognition    Knowledge management    Sound effects

What is a collection of software that  manages computer hardware resources and provides common services for computer programs?
Operating systems    Data mining closely related to database    Engineering    Data mining closely related to database

What are computer systems used by telecommunications service providers?
Operations Support System    Electronic voting    Cheque    Compiler optimization

What is the mechanical or electronic conversion of scanned images of handwritten, typewritten or printed text into machine-encoded text?
Optical character recognition    Genomics    Web server    Training

What is a family of card games involving betting and individualistic play whereby the winner is determined by the ranks and combinations of their cards, some of which remain hidden until the end of the game?
Poker    Sciences    Loader     Electronic voting

What is a computer software package used to display information, normally in the form of a slide show?
Presentation program    Credit cards    Business Support Systems    Credit cards

What is a system of digital message formats and rules for exchanging those messages in or between computing systems and in telecommunications?
Protocol     Sea lane    Telephony    Telephony

What is a type of auction in which the roles of buyer and seller are reversed. In an ordinary auction (also known as a forward auction), buyers compete to obtain a good or service by offering increasingly higher prices?
Reverse auctions     Computer multitasking    Numerical Analysis    Contact managers

What is the branch of technology that deals with the design, construction, operation, and application of robots, as well as computer systems for their control, sensory feedback, and information processing?
Robotics    Music sequencers    Video games    Computer graphics

What is a device that forwards data packets between computer networks, creating an overlay internetwork?
Router     Testing    Cheque    Auctions 

What is a systematic enterprise that builds and organizes knowledge in the form of testable explanations and predictions about the universe?
Sciences    Element Management System    Embedded system    Word processors

What is a regularly used route for ocean-going and Great Lakes vessels. In the time of sailing ships they were not only determined by the distribution of land masses but also the prevailing winds, whose discovery was crucial for the success of long voyages?
Sea lane    Communication    Traffic Control    Genomics

What is the imitation of the operation of a real-world process or system over time. The act of simulating something first requires that a model be developed; this model represents the key characteristics or behaviors of the selected physical or abstract system or process?
Simulation    Sound effects    Business software    Logistics

What is artificially created or enhanced sounds, or sound processes used to emphasize artistic or other content of films, television shows, live performance, animation, video games, music, or other media?
Sound effects    Handwriting recognition    Auctions     Data mining closely related to database

What is the study of speech signals and the processing methods of these signals. The signals are usually processed in a digital representation, so speech processing can be regarded as a special case of digital signal processing, applied to speech signal?
Speech processing    Air traffic control    Optical character recognition    Web browser

What is an interactive computer application program for organization and analysis of data in tabular form?
Spreadsheets    Genomics    CAD    Stock market

What is a public entity (a loose network of economic transactions, not a physical facility or discrete entity) for the trading of company stock (shares) and derivatives at an agreed price; these are securities listed on a stock exchange as well as those only traded privately?
Stock market    Business software    Analytics    Bar code scanners

What is the management of a network of interconnected businesses involved in the provision of product and service packages required by the end customers in a supply chain?
Supply chain management    Computer file    Auctions     Robotics

What is the highly automated communications process by which measurements are made and other data collected at remote or inaccessible points and transmitted to receiving equipment for monitoring?
Telemetry    Analytics    Router     Computer file

What is the transfer of ownership of goods   and services from one person or entity to another by getting something in exchange from the buyer?
Trade    Spreadsheets    Medical software    Music sequencers

What is the acquisition of knowledge, skills, and competencies as a result of the teaching of vocational or practical skills and knowledge that relate to specific useful competencies?
Training    Robotics    Distributed control system    Special effects for video and film

What is an electronic game that involves human interaction with a user interface to generate visual feedback on a video device?
Video games    Music    Telephony    Network Management

What is a softwis application for retrieving, presenting and traversing information resources on the World Wide Web?
Web browser    Contact managers    HVAC    Accounting software

What is a computer application used for the production (including composition, editing, formatting and possibly printing) of any sort of printable material?
Word processors    Supply chain management    Web server    Stock market

What is a system of interlinked hypertext documents accessed via the Internet?
World wide web    Parsers    Sciences    Embedded system

