Who is one of the original developers of the Mosaic browser. He cofounded and was a partner at Netscape Communications Corporation?
Aleksandar Totic    Kim Man Lui    Manny Lehman     Diomidis Spinellis

Who is an American  programming language designer, software engineer, and inventor?
Anthony James Barr    Robert Adamson     Thomas Dickey    Jan Dietz

Who is an American software engineer most notable for his contributions to the MySQL database?
Baron Schwartz    Victor Basili    Robert Adamson     Glenda Schroeder

Who is an American software engineer, TRW Emeritus Professor of Software Engineering at the Computer Science Department of the University of Southern California, and known for his many contributions to software engineering?
Barry Boehm    Brian Randell    Joe Celko    Stewart Stevenson

Who is a softwis architect, designer, and imagery expert.  As of 2010, he is the architect of Bing Maps and Bing Mobile?
Blaise Agüera y Arcas    Gary Robinson    Thomas Biskup    Steve McConnell

Who is a computer scientist and Ph.D. of mathematical biology known mostly for his work in software engineering (specifically software reuse), software componentry, and the Objective-C programming language?
Brad Cox    Zvonko Vranesic    Samir Arora    Cris Kobryn

Who is a British computer scientist, and Emeritus Professor at the School of Computing Science, Newcastle University, U.K?
Brian Randell    James Ready    Gary Robinson    Edward Saatchi

Who is a French software engineer and a software technology author. He is the co-author of two books and the creator of the TestNG Java testing framework?
Cédric Beust    Grady Ward    Jim Highsmith    James Ready

Who is an American computer scientist, who spent his entire career as an industrial researcher rather than in academia?
Charles Bachman    Gilad Bracha    Samir Arora    Robert Adamson 

Who is an American electronics engineer and software engineer who was a co-founder of Silicon Graphics, a major graphics workstation manufacturer?
Charles Kuta    Cody Brocious    Gary Robinson    Jan Dietz

Who is an American software engineer best known for his work on PyMusiqu?
Cody Brocious    Duncan Suttles    Thomas Knoll    László Bélády

Who is a Canadian computer scientist specializing in Iterative and incremental development, Agile software development, Object-oriented analysis, Object-oriented design, and agile modeling?
Craig Larman    Chris Oliver     Bruce Artwick    Jonathan Bowen

Who is an American technologist, system architect and entrepreneur who specializes in advanced softwis and systems development?
Cris Kobryn    James Rumbaugh    Harold Lawson    Brian Randell

Who is a Canadian early pioneer of software engineering, who developed the concept of information hiding in modular programming, which is an important element of object-oriented programming today?
David Parnas    Ib Holm Sørensen    Tom Gilb    Eric Traut

Who is a computer scientist and advisor in information technology. Born to Anima and Pramod Kumar Mukhopadhyay, he grew up in Calcutta?
Debajyoti Mukhopadhyay    Philippe Kruchten    Martyn Thomas    Cédric Beust

Who is an American software engineer, consultant, and trainer at the Software Engineering Institute (SEI)?
Donald Firesmith    Tom DeMarco    Samir Arora    Sjaak Brinkkemper

Who is an African-American businesswoman, entrepreneur, and philanthropist.  She was the founder and chief executive officer (CEO) of Freshwater Software from 1996 to 2001.  Prior to Freshwater Software, she was a senior engineering manager at Apple Computer who helped to coordinate the development of the Newton personal digital assistant (PDA)?
Donna Auguste    Charles Bachman    Jim Jagielski    Baron Schwartz

Who is an American software engineer and former actor best remembered as Kurt von Trapp in The Sound of Music?
Duane Chase    Tarun Anand    Terry Halpin    Brian Randell

Who is an International Grandmaster of chess who was the strongest Canadian player between the eras of Abe Yanofsky and Kevin Spraggett?
Duncan Suttles    Junio Hamano    Poorni    Stewart Stevenson

Who is an entrepreneur and co-founder of NationalField, a software company that creates enterprise-based private social networks?
Edward Saatchi    Junio Hamano    Eric Traut    Diomidis Spinellis

Who is an American software engineer and software emulation pioneer.  Traut graduated from Stanford University in 1992.  From 1993 to 1995 he worked for Apple Computer, creating a Mac 68K emulator to be used in PowerPC-based Macintoshes?
Eric Traut    Robert Carr     Sally Shlaer    Blaise Agüera y Arcas

Who is an information systems researcher and was the first UK Professor of Information Systems?
Frank Land    Thomas Biskup    Anthony James Barr    Diomidis Spinellis

Who is a software engineer and computer scientist, best known for managing the development of IBM's System/360 family of computers and the OS/360 software support package, then later writing candidly about the process in his seminal book The Mythical Man-Month?
Fred Brooks    Philippe Kruchten    Tom Gruber    Steve McConnell

Who is a Welsh Software engineer best known for having built [http://www.techcompanypay.com TechCompanyPay] with features in TechCrunch, Wired, and Business Insider?
Gareth Paul Jones    Jacques Bonjawo    Jeff Offutt    Paul Tyma

Who is an American software engineer notable for his mathematical algorithms to fight spa?
Gary Robinson    Gilad Bracha    Ivar Jacobson    Donald Firesmith

Who is the creator of the Newspeak programming language, a software engineer at Google and a member of the Dart (programming language) team in Aarhus?
Gilad Bracha    Steve McConnell    Software engineer    Gareth Paul Jones

Who is an American software engineer who implemented the first shell for the Multics operating system (a predecessor to the Unix shell) at MIT?
Glenda Schroeder    Harri Porten    Diomidis Spinellis    Glenda Schroeder

Who is an American software engineer. Booch is best known for developing the Unified Modeling Language with Ivar Jacobson and James Rumbaugh?
Grady Booch    Scott Ambler    Gareth Paul Jones    Terry Halpin

Who is an American software engineer, lexicographer, and Internet activist who has featured prominently in the Scientology versus the Internet controversy?
Grady Ward    Baron Schwartz    Jeff Offutt    Harri Porten

Who is a software engineer, computer architect and systems engineer. Lawson is credited with the 1964 invention of the pointer?
Harold Lawson    Martyn Thomas    Stevens Award    David Parnas

Who is  a software engineer. Porten, a KDE developer and former Trolltech employee, is the CEO of Froglogic, a consultancy company related to Qt development?
Harri Porten    James Rumbaugh    Charles Bachman    Glenda Schroeder

Who is a Swedish computer scientist, known as major contributor to UML, Objectory, RUP and aspect-oriented software development?
Ivar Jacobson    Gilad Bracha    Kent Beck    Joe Celko

Who is a software engineer, an author and a columnist  in the application of technology to sustainable development?
Jacques Bonjawo    Yugo Nakamura    Dick Smith     Software engineering professionalism

Who is an American computer scientist and object-oriented methodologist who is best known for his work in creating the Object Modeling Technique (OMT) and the Unified Modeling Language (UML)?
James Rumbaugh    Grady Booch    Jim Jagielski    James Ready

Who is a Dutch computer scientist, and former Professor of Information Systems Design at Delft University of Technology?
Jan Dietz    Tarun Anand    Sally Shlaer    Tom DeMarco

Who is a professor of Software Engineering at George Mason University. His primary interests are Software Testing and Analysis, Web Software Engineering, and  Software evolution and Change-impact Analysis?
Jeff Offutt    Jim Jagielski    Cody Brocious    Barry Boehm

Who is an American software engineer working for IBM since 1987. He is currently  the Chief Technology Officer of WebSphere, a business unit within IBM Software Group (SWG?
Jerry Cuomo    David Parnas    Stevens Award    Junio Hamano

Who is an American software engineer and author of books in the field of software development methodology?
Jim Highsmith    Stevens Award    Anthony James Barr    Brad Cox

Who is an American software engineer, who specialises in web and open source technologies?
Jim Jagielski    Manny Lehman     Wayne Stevens    Gilad Bracha

Who is an American relational database expert from Austin, Texas. He has participated on the ANSI X3H2 Database Standards Committee, and helped write the SQL-89 and SQL-92 standards?
Joe Celko    Jan Dietz    Jeff Offutt    David Parnas

Who is a British computer scientist. He is Chairman of Museophile Limited, an Emeritus Professor at London South Bank University where he has headed the Centre for Applied Formal Methods, Formerly he was a Visiting Professor at the University of Westminster and at King's College London and a visiting academic at University College London?
Jonathan Bowen    Sjaak Brinkkemper    Ib Holm Sørensen    Aleksandar Totic

Who is a software engineer, formerly employed at Google, and a technology author?
Joshua Bloch    Joe Celko    Software engineering demographics    László Bélády

Who is an American software engineer, consultant, and trainer in the areas of software development, management and process improvement?
Karl Wiegers    Watts Humphrey    Software engineer    Brian Randell

Who is an American software engineer and the creator of the Extreme Programming and Test Driven Development software development methodologies, also named agile software development?
Kent Beck    Edward Saatchi    Tom Gruber    Watts Humphrey

Who is an author of software engineering, and financial speculation books?
Kim Man Lui    Eric Traut    Alex Verrijn Stuart    Gary Robinson

Who is an American software engineer and professor in the Center for Exact Sciences and Engineering at the University of Madeira Portugal, who is considered one of the pioneers of computing?
Larry Constantine    Glenda Schroeder    Charles Kuta    Samir Arora

Who is a Hungarian computer scientist notable for devising the Bélády's Min theoretical memory caching algorithm in 1966 while working at IBM Research?
László Bélády    Wayne Stevens    Chris Oliver     David Crowe 

Who is a British executive and software engineer who serves as corporate vice president in the Microsoft Skype Division?
Mark Gillett    Philippe Kruchten    Anthony James Barr    Baron Schwartz

Who is a British independent consultant and software engineer?
Martyn Thomas    Gareth Paul Jones    Harold Lawson    Duane Chase

Who is a Nepalese computer programmer credited with helping to usher in information technology in Nepal?
Muni Sakya    Pierre De Muelenaere    Robert Carr     Samir Arora

Who is an American inventor, software engineer, author, actor, and entrepreneur?
Paul Tyma    Software engineer    Grady Ward    Chris Oliver 

Who is a Canadian software engineer, and Professor of Software Engineering at University of British Columbia in Vancouver, Canada, known as Director of Process Development (RUP) at Rational Software, and developer of the 4+1 Architectural View Model?
Philippe Kruchten    Kim Man Lui    Thomas Biskup    Donald Firesmith

Who is a Belgian entrepreneur and scientist. In 1987, after he received its Ph.D?
Pierre De Muelenaere    Zvonko Vranesic    Gary Robinson    Baron Schwartz

Who is a VJ, Actress and Software Engineer from Tamil Nadu?
Poorni    Harold Lawson    Anthony James Barr    James Rumbaugh

Who is best known as the founder, CEO and Chairman of the web design company NetObjects, Inc?
Samir Arora    Thomas Knoll    Cédric Beust    Martyn Thomas

Who is a Canadian software engineer, consultant and author, currently Senior Consulting Partner at  + Associates?
Scott Ambler    Tom Gilb    Mark Gillett    Ib Holm Sørensen

Who is a software engineer at Google, where he worked on Google Talk and is currently working on Google Maps?
Sean Egan    Stevens Award    Karl Wiegers    David Parnas

Who is a Dutch computer scientist, and Full Professor of organisation and information at the Department of Information and Computing Sciences of Utrecht University?
Sjaak Brinkkemper    Debajyoti Mukhopadhyay    Diomidis Spinellis    Murali Chemuturi

Who is a practitioner of software engineering. s apply the principles of engineering to the design, development, maintaining, testing, and evaluation of the softwis and systems that make computers or anything containing software work?
Software engineer    Craig Larman    Junio Hamano    Samir Arora

Who is a movement to make software engineering a profession, with aspects such as degree and certification programs, professional associations, professional ethics, and government licensing?
Software engineering professionalism    Victor Basili    Robert Carr     Zvonko Vranesic

Who is an author of many software engineering textbooks including Code Complete, Rapid Development, and Software Estimation?
Steve McConnell    Paul Tyma    Frank Land    Zvonko Vranesic

Who is a software engineering award given in memory of Wayne Stevens. The international  was created to recognize outstanding contributions to the literature or practice of methods for softwis and systems development?
Stevens Award    Kent Beck    Jonathan Bowen    Edward Saatchi

Who is a Scottish politician who became a Member of the Scottish Parliament in 200?
Stewart Stevenson    Tom Gruber    Donna Auguste    Tom Gilb

Who is an Indian information technology entrepreneur, software engineer and the co-founder of The Perfect Future?
Tarun Anand    Jeromy Carriere    Diomidis Spinellis    Jim Jagielski

Who is an Australian computer scientist who is known for his formalization of the Object Role Modeling notation?
Terry Halpin    Philippe Kruchten    Thomas Dickey    Duane Chase

Who is a German software engineer and computer scientist. He is the creator and developer of Ancient Domains of Mystery, a popular computer roleplaying game?
Thomas Biskup    Jim Highsmith    Paul Tyma    Donald Firesmith

Who is a free software developer of several widely-used programs and libraries related to text terminals and terminal emulators?
Thomas Dickey    Steve McConnell    Chris Oliver     Samir Arora

Who is an American software engineer best known (with his brother John Knoll) for initiating the development of Adobe Photoshop?
Thomas Knoll    Stevens Award    Craig Larman    Software engineer

Who is an American software engineer, author, teacher and speaker on software engineering topics?
Tom DeMarco    Sean Egan    Larry Constantine    Joe Celko

Who is an American systems engineer, consultant, and author, known for the development of software metric, software inspection, and evolutionary processes?
Tom Gilb    Karl Wiegers    Stewart Stevenson    Jacques Bonjawo

Who is an American computer scientist, inventor, and entrepreneur with a focus on systems for knowledge sharing and collective intelligence?
Tom Gruber    Zvonko Vranesic    Terry Halpin    Brad Cox

Who is an American computer software enginee?
Tom Van Vleck    Jeromy Carriere    Dick Smith     Software engineering professionalism

Who is an Emeritus Professor at the Department of Computer Science and the Institute for Advanced Computer Studies, both at University of Maryland?
Victor Basili    Martyn Thomas    Gareth Paul Jones    Brian Randell

Who is considered one of Japan's leading web designers. Yugo studied engineering, architecture and landscape design?
Yugo Nakamura    Chris Oliver     Jeff Offutt    Murali Chemuturi

Who is a Croatian–Canadian International Master of chess, and an International Master of Correspondence Chess?
Zvonko Vranesic    Jerry Cuomo    Brian Randell    Pierre De Muelenaere

