What is a model based systems engineering software platform used for a range of activities including building and operating real-time simulation-based lab test facilities for hardware-in-the-loop simulation purposes?
ADvantage Framework    Software architectural model    Model View ViewModel    Federated Portal Network

What is a microcrystalline variety of silica, chiefly chalcedony, characterised by its fineness of grain and brightness of color?
AGATE     OOHDM    Semantic architecture    Open Service Interface Definitions

What is a blueprint for softwis agents and intelligent control systems, depicting the arrangement of components?
Agent architecture    Messaging Open Service Interface Definition    Multitenancy    Software architecture analysis method

What is an O.K.I. specification which supports the creation, retrieval and deletion of Agent and Groups?
Agent Open Service Interface Definition    Functional software architecture    Mibe architecture    Situational application

What is the use of a software domain model where the business logic is implemented outside the domain objects?
Anemic domain model    SIGMDSE    Principle of good enough    Repository Open Service Interface Definition

What is a mechanism (similar to a process in an operating system) used within the Common Language Infrastructure (CLI) to isolate executed softwis applications from one another so that they do not affect each other?
Application domain    Application service architecture    Architecture framework    Software analysis pattern

What is an emerging discipline within IT that involves a top down approach to monitoring, controlling, securing, and optimizing applications in transit?
Application service architecture    Software architecture    Public interface    IDEAS Group

What is a standard design in the field of softwis architecture. The concept of an architectural pattern has a broader scope than the concept of design pattern?
Architectural pattern    Authentication Open Service Interface Definition    Presenter First    Synchrony abstraction

What are the system engineering community, the software engineering community and the enterprise modelling and engineering communi?
Architecture description language    Technical debt    Software architecture recovery    EMML 

What is arid when it is characterized by a severe lack of available water, to the extent of hindering or preventing the growth and development of plant and animal life?
ARID    Open architecture    Reference architecture    Software analysis pattern

What is making individual software components, such as speech synthesizers, interoperable with other components, such as common sense knowledgebases, in order to create larger, broader and more capable A.I?
Artificial intelligence systems integration    Node graph architecture    Open Service Interface Definitions    CPPSERV

What is an O.K.I. specification which supports creating, organizing, administrating, evaluating, storing and retrieving assessment information?
Assessment Open Service Interface Definition    Connection broker    Monolithic application    Transparency 

What is an O.K.I. specification which supports invoking an authentication process?
Authentication Open Service Interface Definition    Filing Open Service Interface Definition    SIGMDSE    Task computing

What is an O.K.I. specification which provides the means to define who is authorized to do what, when?
Authorization Open Service Interface Definition    Coupling     MODELISAR    BORO method

What is an open and standardized automotive softwis architecture, jointly developed by automobile manufacturers, suppliers and tool developers?
AUTOSAR    Colony Framework    Synthetic Environment for Analysis and Simulations    ADvantage Framework

What is a compositional .NET MVC framework with concepts from REST and AOP. Bistro modifies the traditional concepts of MVC by breaking down a single HTTP request into a series of aspects, each processed by a separate controller?
Bistro Framework    Messaging Open Service Interface Definition    OpenPipeline    Software framework

What is an artificial intelligence application based on the blackboard architectural model, where a common knowledge base, the "blackboard", is iteratively updated by a diverse group of specialist knowledge sources, starting with a problem specification and ending with a solution?
Blackboard system    IDEAS Group    Darwin     Software architect

What is an approach to developing ontological or semantic models for large complex operational applications that consists of a top ontology and a process for constructing the ontology?
BORO method    Solution architecture    Graphical user interface    MVC4WPF

What is the set of classes that represent objects in the business model being implemented?
Business domain    Interface metaphor    Occasionally connected computing    Demonolithicized application

What is a non-technical term generally used to describe the functional algorithms that handle information exchange between a database and a user interface?
Business logic    Architecture tradeoff analysis method    Common Component Architecture    Artificial intelligence systems integration

What is an open source plugin framework specification. Implementations of the specification offer a runtime component model, that allows for plugins to be installed, started, stopped, updated and uninstalled without requiring the application container to be stopped?
Colony Framework    Evocb    ARID    Authorization Open Service Interface Definition

What is a standard for Component-based software engineering used in high-performance (also known as scientific) computing?
Common Component Architecture    Solution architecture    Node graph architecture    Bistro Framework

What are the most common layers in a logical multilayered architecture for an information system with an object-oriented desig?
Common layers in an information system logical architecture    Knowledge Discovery Metamodel    Scaffold     Software framework

What is an addition to Microsoft's .NET Framework for creating complex user interfaces made of loosely coupled components?
Composite UI Application Block    Business logic    Wright     Mashup 

What is a technique by which classes may achieve polymorphic behavior and code reuse by containing other classes that implement the desired functionality instead of through inheritance?
Composition over inheritance    Office controller    Functional design    Enterprise service bus

What is a device used to connect two shafts together at their ends for the purpose of transmitting power?
Coupling     Open architecture    Scheduling Open Service Interface Definition    Task computing

What is an O.K.I. specification which supports the creation and management of a course catalog (CourseCatalog)?
CourseManagement Open Service Interface Definition    Presenter First    Demonolithicized application    Naked objects

What is C++ Servlet Engine. It provides Servlet-like API to C++ programmers. This allows them to write small, extremely efficient web applications, with an ease that was only available to Java programmers?
CPPSERV    Software architect    Model View ViewModel    Solution architecture

What is the result of breaking a monolithic application into small manageable pieces the deliver the same or superior business results?
Demonolithicized application    Rich Internet application    Transparency     Logging Open Service Interface Definition

What is a software design pattern that allows removing hard-coded dependencies and making it possible to change them, whether at run-time or compile-time?
Dependency injection    Transparency     Synchrony abstraction    PureMVC

What is an interface metaphor which is a set of unifying concepts used by graphical user interfaces to help users more easily interact with the computer?
Desktop metaphor    Desktop metaphor    Digital nervous system    Office controller

What is an O.K.I. specification which supports creating and populating dictionaries of tag-value pairs?
Dictionary Open Service Interface Definition    Scheduling Open Service Interface Definition    Interface metaphor    Smart client

What is a phrase, popularly associated with Bill Gates of Microsoft, used to describe a vision for how the IT infrastructure of an enterprise could be analogous to the autonomic nervous system of a biological organism?
Digital nervous system    Scheduling Open Service Interface Definition    Integrated data management    IDEAS Group

What is a small column of liquid, bounded completely or almost completely by free surfaces?
Droplets     Composition over inheritance    Extensibility    Functional software architecture

What is an XML markup language for creating enterprise mashups, which are softwis applications that consume and mash data from variety of sources, often performing logical or mathematical operations as well as presenting data?
Enterprise Mashup Markup Language    Dependency injection    Blackboard system    Business logic

What is a distributed object system that is constructed on top of publish/subscribe event systems. This design decision implies modeling method calls as events and subscriptions over the underlying messaging middleware?
Evocb    Presentation logic    Runahead solution    SAP Enterprise Architecture Framework

What is a framework for remote content sharing between enterprise portal?
Federated Portal Network    Web application    Application Mediation    Simulated reality

What is an O.K.I. specificatio?
Filing Open Service Interface Definition    Model View ViewModel    Filing Open Service Interface Definition    Library Oriented Architecture

What is a paradigm used to simplify the design of hardwis and software devices such as computer softwis and increasingly, 3D models?
Functional design    Shared nothing architecture    Application service architecture    Architecture tradeoff analysis method

What is a piece of  mineral, which, in cut and polished form, is used to make jewelry or other adornments?
Gemstone     Implicit invocation    Wright     Filing Open Service Interface Definition

What is a development environment and an application server for Web Applications. It is characterized by strict separation of data storage, processing and user interface development?
GNUstepWeb    Common layers in an information system logical architecture    Model View ViewModel    BORO method

What is an Open Knowledge Initiative specification. OSIDs are programmatic interfaces which comprise a Service Oriented Architecture for designing and building reusable and interoperable software?
Grading Open Service Interface Definition    Wright     Pipe and filter architecture    Scheduling Open Service Interface Definition

What is a type of user interface that allows users to interact with electronic devices using images rather than text commands?
Graphical user interface    Model View ViewModel    Software architecture analysis method    Naked objects

What is an Open Knowledge Initiative specification. OSIDs are programmatic interfaces which comprise a Service Oriented Architecture for designing and building reusable and interoperable software?
Hierarchy Open Service Interface Definition    Logging Open Service Interface Definition    ARID    PureMVC

What is the International Defence Enterprise Architecture Specification for exchange Group?
IDEAS Group    BORO method    CPPSERV    Digital nervous system

What is an IEEE Standard  for describing the architecture of a software-intensive system, also known as softwis architecture?
IEEE 1471    Multimodal Architecture and Interfaces    Extensibility    Solution architecture

What is a term used by some authors for a style of softwis architecture in which a system is structured around event handling, using a form of callback?
Implicit invocation    Functional design    Subsumption architecture    Software blueprint

What is a tools approach to facilitate data management and improve performance?
Integrated data management    Public interface    Library Oriented Architecture    Architecture description language

What is a software development firm that was created in 2002. The company is a systems integrator and solutions provider for knowledge management, automation and plant process management and decision support applications?
Integration Objects    Architectural pattern    Web API    IBM PureQuery

What is a set of user interface visuals, actions and procedures that exploit specific knowledge that users already have of other domains?
Interface metaphor    Open Service Interface Definitions    Coupling     SAP Enterprise Architecture Framework

What is publicly available specification from the Object Management Group (OMG)?
Knowledge Discovery Metamodel    Authorization Open Service Interface Definition    Workflow Open Service Interface Definition    Functional software architecture

What is an O.K.I. specification which supports a means of reading and writing log files?
Logging Open Service Interface Definition    Software architecture recovery    Smart client    Situational application

What is a web application and mobile app that provides a free automatic video editing service for amateurs?
Magisto    ARID    Rich client platform    Multitenancy

What is an O.K.I. specification which provides a means of sending, subscribing and receiving messages?
Messaging Open Service Interface Definition    Common modeling infrastructure    Software architecture recovery    Open Service Interface Definitions

What is the section of a database or other data holding structure that is designated to hold data that will act as source code or metadata?
Metatable    Interface metaphor    Smart client    OOHDM

What is a behavior-based robot architecture developed at [http://www.airlab.elet.polimi.it/ Artificial Intelligence and Robotics Lab] of Politecnico di Milano by Fabio La Daga and [http://home.dei.polimi.it/bonarini/index.html Andrea Bonarini] in 1998. MIBE architecture is based on the idea of animat and derived from subsumption architecture, formerly developed by Rodney Brooks and colleagues at MIT in 198?
Mibe architecture    Demonolithicized application    Digital nervous system    Common Component Architecture

What are two commonly used design models, referred to as  and Model ?
Model 1    Principle of good enough    Inversion of control    Software framework

What is a complex design pattern used in the design of Java Web applications which separates the display of content from the logic used to obtain and manipulate the content?
Model 2    Common layers in an information system logical architecture    Software architectural model    Software architecture description

What is an architectural pattern used in software engineering that originated from Microsoft as a specialization of the presentation model design pattern introduced by Martin Fowler?
Model View ViewModel    Technical debt    OpenPipeline    Functional software architecture

What is an ITEA 2 (Information Technology for European Advancement) European project aiming to improve the design of systems and of embedded software in vehicles?
MODELISAR    Workflow Open Service Interface Definition    Agent Open Service Interface Definition    Demonolithicized application

What is an architectural pattern used in software engineering that came about as an enhancement to the MVVM design pattern?
Multiuse Model View    Enterprise Mashup Markup Language    Software architecture analysis method    Presenter First

What is an open-source, extensible, automated code pattern developed at Information Control Corporation for Windows Presentation Foundation (WPF) development based on the Model-View-Controller (MVC) and Presentation-Abstraction-Control (PAC) patterns?
MVC4WPF    Common Component Architecture    Evocb    Model 2

What is an architectural pattern used in software engineerin?
Naked objects    Node graph architecture    Pipe and filter architecture    Workflow Open Service Interface Definition

What is a type of software design which builds around modular node components which can be connected to form a graph?
Node graph architecture    UIMA    BORO method    Architecture description language

What is a term used in computing for an architecture or framework which permits running some aspects of a web application when not connected to the Internet?
Occasionally connected computing    Common modeling infrastructure    Business logic    Dictionary Open Service Interface Definition

What is a method for the development of Web application?
OOHDM    EFx Factory    Architectural pattern    EMML 

What is a type of computer architecture or softwis architecture that is designed to make adding, upgrading and swapping components easy?
Open architecture    Monolithic application    Common modeling infrastructure    Public interface

What are programmatic interface specifications describing services?
Open Service Interface Definitions    Integrated data management    Common layers in an information system logical architecture    MODELISAR

What is open source software for crawling, parsing, analyzing and routing documents. It is intended to tie together otherwise incomplete solutions for enterprise search and document processing?
OpenPipeline    CPPSERV    Shared nothing architecture    GNUstepWeb

What is the ability to send a payload (the document or request object sent to a Service) without regard to what protocol might be configured?
Payload abstraction    Logging Open Service Interface Definition    Software architect    QP 

What is a software development approach that combines the ideas of the model–view–presenter (MVP) design pattern, test-driven development, and Feature-driven development?
Presenter First    Simulated reality    Scheduling Open Service Interface Definition    Software architect

What is a rule for softwis and systems design?
Principle of good enough    ARID    Authentication Open Service Interface Definition    Implicit invocation

What is the logical point at which independent software entities interact. The entities may interact with each other within a single computer, across a network, or across a variety of other topologies?
Public interface    Payload abstraction    Droplets     SAP Enterprise Architecture Framework

What is a framework for creating applications based upon the well-established Model-View-Controller design pattern?
PureMVC    Federated Portal Network    Open Service Interface Definitions    Business domain

What is an English professional football club, based in White City, London?
QP     Application Mediation    SIGMDSE    Software Architecture styles and patterns

What is an O.K.I. specification which defines the storing and retrieving of digital content, referred to as Assets?
Repository Open Service Interface Definition    Workflow Open Service Interface Definition    Rich client platform    Blackboard system

What is a style of softwis architecture for distributed systems such as the World Wide Web?
Representational state transfer    Wright     Functional design    Software Architecture styles and patterns

What is a programmer tool that makes it easier to integrate independent software components, where most of the data processing occurs on the client side?
Rich client platform    Multitier architecture    Inversion of control    Enterprise Mashup Markup Language

What is a Web application that has many of the characteristics of desktop application software, typically delivered by way of a site-specific browser, a browser plug-in, an independent sandbox, extensive use of JavaScript, or a virtual machine?
Rich Internet application    Functional design    ARID    Messaging Open Service Interface Definition

What is a methodology and toolset primarily to support the effective adoption of SOA?
SAP Enterprise Architecture Framework    Authentication Open Service Interface Definition    Messaging Open Service Interface Definition    Droplets 

What is a temporary structure used to support people and material in the construction or repair of buildings and other large structures?
Scaffold     Logging Open Service Interface Definition    Integration Objects    Architecture framework

What is an O.K.I. specification. OSIDs are programmatic interfaces which comprise a Service Oriented Architecture for designing and building reusable and interoperable software?
Scheduling Open Service Interface Definition    Debugging patterns    Semantic architecture    Solution architecture

What is a novel concept in softwis architecture which envisions enabling the architecture community to unambiguously capture, catalog, communicate, preserve, and interoperably exchange semantics of their architectures, thus making architecture descriptions true assets?
Semantic architecture    Shared disk architecture    Solution architecture    Blackboard system

What is the hypothesis that reality could be simulated—for example by computer simulation—to a degree indistinguishable from "true" reality, and may in fact be such a simulation?
Simulated reality    Application server    Situational application    Grading Open Service Interface Definition

What is "good enough" software created for a narrow group of users with a unique set of needs?
Situational application    UIMA    Metatable    Open Service Interface Definitions

What is a term describing an application environment whic?
Smart client    Assessment Open Service Interface Definition    Digital nervous system    Common modeling infrastructure

What is a computer programmer who makes high-level design choices and dictates technical standards, including software coding standards, tools, and platforms?
Software architect    Naked objects    Task computing    Dictionary Open Service Interface Definition

What is a method used in softwis architecture to evaluate a system architecture?
Software architecture analysis method    Darwin     Common modeling infrastructure    Library Oriented Architecture

What is a set of methods for the extraction of architectural information from lower level representations of a software system, such as source code?
Software architecture recovery    Dictionary Open Service Interface Definition    Model 1    UIMA

What is a general, reusable solution to a commonly occurring problem in softwis architecture within a given context?
Software Architecture styles and patterns    Occasionally connected computing    Naked objects    Multimodal Architecture and Interfaces

What is a reactive robot architecture heavily associated with behavior-based robotics?
Subsumption architecture    Principle of good enough    Model 2    Payload abstraction

What is a collection of open source software released by Sun Microsystems for developing web applications that run on Java EE application servers?
Sun Web Developer Pack    Payload abstraction    Occasionally connected computing    Messaging Open Service Interface Definition

What is the proposed ability to generically call a Service/Operati?
Synchrony abstraction    Rich Internet application    Demonolithicized application    Pipe and filter architecture

What is currently being used by Homeland Security and the US Defense Department to simulate crises on the US mainland?
Synthetic Environment for Analysis and Simulations    Multilayered architecture    Technical debt    Software Architecture styles and patterns

What is the conceptual model that defines the structure, behavior, and more views of a system?
Systems architecture    AJAX Service Bus    SIGMDSE    Node graph architecture

What is a computatiοn to fill the gap between tasks (what user wants to be done), and services (functionalities that is available to the user)?
Task computing    Synthetic Environment for Analysis and Simulations    Connascence     Business domain

What is a neologistic metaphor referring to the eventual consequences of poor or evolving softwis architecture and software development within a codebase?
Technical debt    Office controller    Software analysis pattern    Scaffold 

What is to date the only industry standard for content analytics?
UIMA    Sun Web Developer Pack    Application Mediation    Software Architecture styles and patterns

What is used to refer to both a server-side API upon a web server as well as client-side API within a web browser?
Web API    MVC4WPF    Pipe and filter architecture    Task computing

What is an application that is accessed by users over a network such as the Internet or an intranet?
Web application    Functional software architecture    Bistro Framework    Multimodal Architecture and Interfaces

What is the component of a web server that interacts with Java servlets?
Web container    Knowledge Discovery Metamodel    Multilayered architecture    Payload abstraction

What is an O.K.I. specification which provides the means to define a Process composed of Steps?
Workflow Open Service Interface Definition    Smart client    Architectural pattern    Repository Open Service Interface Definition

