What is a film directed by Henry King starring John Hodiak and Gene Tierney. The film was adapted from the novel by John Hersey, which won the Pulitzer Prize in 1945. In his 1945 review of the film, Bosley Crowther wrote, "..?
A Bell for Adano     The Little Princess     The Luck of the Irish     Charlie Chan in Paris 

WhatConnecticut Yankee or may refer t?
A Connecticut Yankee     Delicious     The Song of Bernadette     Orchestra Wives 

What is a silent film. The film was controversial because of the sequences of what was regarded as superfluous nudity by the main character, Nydia, played by Australian swimming star Annette Kellerman?
A Daughter of the Gods    That Lady in Ermine     Josette     Ladies in Love 

Whatis a 1949 American romantic drama film which tells the story of a woman who mails a letter to three women, telling them she has left town with the husband of one of them?
A Letter to Three Wives     Tail Spin     Circus Cowboy     Tales of Manhattan 

Whatis a best-selling inspirational essay written in 1899 by Elbert Hubbard that has been made into two motion pictures?
A Message to Garcia     Tess of the Storm Country     To the Shores of Tripoli     Wake Up and Live 

Whatis a 1945 film, the first film directed by Greek-American director Elia Kazan, starring James Dunn (who won the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor), Dorothy McGuire, Joan Blondell, and Peggy Ann Garner  (who won the Academy Juvenile Award)?
A Tree Grows in Brooklyn     Street Angel     Circus Cowboy     Just Imagine 

Whatmay refer t?
A Walk in the Sun     Charlie Chan in Shanghai     That Wonderful Urge     High Society Blues 

Whatmay refer t?
Anna and the King of Siam     Happy Landing     Miracle on 34th Street     Diamond Horseshoe 

What is any object or structure that creates a barrier or obstacle to control, block passage or force the flow of traffic in the desired direction?
Barricade     The Eve of St Mark     Anna and the King of Siam     Girl Trouble 

What is a town square in the West End of London, England, in the City of Westminster. It was originally laid out in the mid 18th century by architect William Kent?
Berkeley Square     That Lady in Ermine     Music Is Magic     Tail Spin 

Whatmay refer t?
Bottoms Up     Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm     Sins of Man     Stowaway 

Whatis an American indie rock band founded by singer-songwriter and guitarist Conor Oberst. It consists of Oberst, multi-instrumentalist and producer Mike Mogis, trumpet and piano player Nate Walcott, and a rotating lineup of collaborators drawn primarily from Omaha's indie music scene?
Bright Eyes     Orchestra Wives     Orchestra Wives     Little Miss Broadway 

What is a Pre-Code drama film directed by John Francis Dillon and starring Clara Bow?
Call Her Savage     Judge Priest     Greenwich Village     Love Under Fire 

Whatis a 1923 American silent drama film directed by John Ford and featured Jean Arthur in her onscreen debut?
Cameo Kirby     Ramona     Coney Island     The Shocking Miss Pilgrim 

Whatis a historical adventure film released by 20th Century Fox in 1947.  Directed by Henry King, the Technicolor film starred Tyrone Power, Jean Peters, and Cesar Romero?
Captain from Castile     Fox Movietone Follies of 1929     The Iron Curtain     The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes 

Whatmay refer t?
Captain January     Suez     The Three Musketeers     The Magnificent Dope 

What is a procession or parade on horseback, or a mass trail ride by a company of riders.  The focus of a cavalcade is participation rather than display; often, the participants do not wear costumes or ride in formation?
Cavalcade     Gateway     My Darling Clementine     Heidi 

What is the fifth novel in the Charlie Chan series by Earl Derr Bigger?
Charlie Chan Carries On     Coney Island     That Lady in Ermine     Love Under Fire 

Whatis the seventh film produced by Fox with Warner Oland as Charlie Cha?
Charlie Chan in Paris     A Letter to Three Wives     Nightmare Alley     Jane Eyre 

Whatis the ninth Charlie Chan film produced by Fox with the title character played by Warner Oland?
Charlie Chan in Shanghai     Thunder Birds     Just Imagine     The Luck of the Irish 

Whatis a 1930 American musical film directed by Sidney Lanfield. The film starred Arthur Lake, Dixie Lee and Olga Baclanova and a 23-year old John Wayne had a minor uncredited role?
Cheer Up and Smile     Guadalcanal Diary     A Bell for Adano     The Shocking Miss Pilgrim 

Whatis a 1949 American comedy film directed by George Seaton. The screenplay by Seaton and Valentine Davies is based on the 1944 play of the same title by Julius J?
Chicken Every Sunday     Sunny Side Up     Charlie Chan in Paris     New Movietone Follies of 1930 

What is a song co-written by David Bowie and Iggy Pop during their years in Berlin, first appearing on Pop's album The Idiot (1977)?
China Girl     A Walk in the Sun     Coney Island     Just Imagine 

Whathistory as Cleopatra, was the last pharaoh of Ancient Egypt?
Cleopatra     On the Avenue     Happy Days     The Rains Came 

Whatis a peninsula and beach on the Atlantic Ocean in southern Brooklyn, New York City, New York, United States?
Coney Island     Under Your Spell     Orchestra Wives     Prince of Foxes 

Whatis a World War II film in Technicolor released in 1943. It was directed by Archie Mayo, written by Jo Swerling and W.R?
Crash Dive     Man Trouble     Berkeley Square     Street Angel 

Whatmay refer t?
Delicious     Madness of Youth     Captain January     Chicken Every Sunday 

What is a 1945 Technicolor musical film starring Betty Grable, directed by George Seaton, and released by 20th Century Fox?
Diamond Horseshoe     Kiss of Death     Married in Hollywood     Wing and a Prayer 

What are a small natural indentation in the flesh on a part of the human body, most notably in the cheek or on the chin?
Dimples     Judge Priest     Laura     The Three Musketeers 

Whatmay refer t?
Dragonwyck     Fig Leaves     None But the Brave     A Letter to Three Wives 

Whatis an English sensation novel of 1861 by Ellen Wood. was a Victorian bestseller?
East Lynne     Berkeley Square     Man Trouble     The Snake Pit 

What is a wicked or rebellious angel. The term is found neither in the Hebrew Bible nor the Deuterocanonical Books nor the New Testament?
Fallen Angel     Regeneration     Guadalcanal Diary     Coney Island 

Whatis a 1926 silent comedy film directed by Howard Hawks, released by Fox Film Corporation, and starring George O'Brien?
Fig Leaves     Yankee Senor     Orchestra Wives     Stowaway 

Whatis a 1942 musical comedy film directed by Gregory Ratoff, starring  Betty Grable, John Payne and Victor Matu?
Footlight Serenade     Fig Leaves     Song of the Islands     That Wonderful Urge 

Whatis a 1944 film starring Kay Francis, Carole Landis, Martha Raye, and Mitzi Mayfair as themselves, re-enacting their USO tour of Europe and North Africa during World War II?
Four Jills in a Jeep     Manila Calling     Tess of the Storm Country     Dragonwyck 

What(also known as Movietone Follies of 1929 and The William Fox Movietone Follies of 1929) was a black-and-white and color American musical film released by Fox Film Corporation?
Fox Movietone Follies of 1929     Man Trouble     Fifty Roads to Town     Crash Dive 

What is a point of entry or exi?
Gateway     The Poor Little Rich Girl     Pin Up Girl     Man Trouble 

Whatmay refer t?
Girl Trouble     Street Angel     Midnight     Guadalcanal Diary 

What is the second most populous island of the Canary Islands, a Spanish archipelago, with a population of 838,397 which constitutes approximately 40% of the population of the archipelago?
Grand Canary     Sunrise     The Snake Pit     None But the Brave 

Whatis a 1948 film starring Peggy Cummins and Charles Coburn. The film is based on the third book in the popular, "My Friend Flicka" trilogy, written by Mary O'Hara?
Green Grass of Wyoming     The Snake Pit     Hearts in Dixie     Sunrise 

WhatGreenwich Villag?
Greenwich Village     Rendezvous 24     The Joy Girl     Sins of Man 

Whatmay refer t?
Guadalcanal Diary     Jesse James     Married in Hollywood     The Littlest Rebel 

Whatis an American television sitcom that aired first-run from January 15, 1974 to September 24, 1984 on ABC?
Happy Days     Wilson     In Old Chicago     Girl Trouble 

Whator Happyland may refer t?
Happy Land     Kiss of Death     Man Trouble     New Movietone Follies of 1930 

What issued on that label's Tamla Records subsidiary label (T54073)?
Happy Landing     A Connecticut Yankee     Fifty Roads to Town     Madness of Youth 

What(1929) was one of the first all-"talkie", big-studio production to boast a predominantly African-American cast?
Hearts in Dixie     Kiss of Death     To the Shores of Tripoli     The Beautiful Blonde from Bashful Bend 

Whatis a 1978 American comedy film directed by Warren Beatty and Buck Henry. It is the second film adaptation of Harry Segall's stageplay of the same name, preceded by Here Comes Mr?
Heaven Can Wait     The Eve of St Mark     Thunder Birds     Dimples 

Whatis a Swiss work of fiction, published in two parts as (1) Heidi's years of learning and travel () and (2) makes use of what she has learned?
Heidi     That Wonderful Urge     Jane Eyre     When My Baby Smiles at Me 

What is a film starring Janet Gaynor and Charles Farrell. The movie was written by Howard J?
High Society Blues     Pin Up Girl     Judge Priest     Whirlpool 

Whatis a 1939 American film featuring Alice Faye as a young performer making her way in the early days of Hollywood, from slapstick silent pictures through the transition from silent to sound?
Hollywood Cavalcade     Rendezvous 24     The Snake Pit     King of Burlesque 

Whatis a 1929 American Western film directed by Irving Cummings and Raoul Walsh, nominated for five Academy Awards, including Best Picture?
In Old Arizona     Sins of Man     Cavalcade     Fig Leaves 

Whatis a 1937 American drama film directed by Henry King.  The screenplay by Sonya Levien and Lamar Trotti was based on the Niven Busch story, "We the O'Learys."  The film is a fictionalized account about the Great Chicago Fire of 1871 and stars Alice Brady as Mrs?
In Old Chicago     When My Baby Smiles at Me     Second Fiddle     The Littlest Rebel 

Whatlished as Jane Eyre: An Autobiography) is a novel by English writer Charlotte Brontë?
Jane Eyre     Captain from Castile     Captain from Castile     Fox Movietone Follies of 1929 

WhatMissouri and the most famous member of the James-Younger Gang?
Jesse James     Jane Eyre     Midnight     The Pied Piper 

What is an American professional wrestler. Bynum is best known for her stint in Total Nonstop Action Wrestling under the name Sojournor Bolt (or "Sojo Bolt" for short)?
Josette     The Three Musketeers     Married in Hollywood     Captain January 

Whatis a 1934 American comedy film. The film was based on humorist Irvin S. Cobb's character Judge Priest?
Judge Priest     Under the Yoke     Stowaway     Gateway 

Whatis a 1930 science fiction musical comedy directed by David Butler. The film is probably best known for its art direction and special effects in its portrayal of New York City in an imagined 198?
Just Imagine     The Littlest Rebel     Happy Land     Under Your Spell 

Whatis a 1936 musical film about a former burlesque producer played by Warner Baxter who moves into a legitimate theatre does very well, until he marries a socialite?
King of Burlesque     The Cowboy and The Countess     Captain from Castile     Just Imagine 

Whatmay refer t?
Kiss of Death     My Gal Sal     The Pied Piper     Madness of Youth 

What is a romantic comedy film directed by Edward H. Griffith and starring Janet Gaynor, Constance Bennett and Loretta Young?
Ladies in Love     State Fair     The Iron Horse     Cameo Kirby 

What are the laurel family, that includes the "True Laurel" and its closest relatives. The family comprises over 3000 species of flowering plants in over 50 genera world-wide?
Laura     The Poor Little Rich Girl     Josette     Married in Hollywood 

Whatis a 1909 play by the Hungarian playwright Ferenc Molnár. It was very famous in its own right during the early to mid-20th century, but is best known today as the basis for the Rodgers and Hammerstein musical Carousel?
Liliom     The Pied Piper     The Big Trail     In Old Arizona 

Whatis a 1938 American musical film directed by Irving Cummings.  The screenplay was written by Harry Tugend and Jack Yellen?
Little Miss Broadway     Greenwich Village     A Tree Grows in Brooklyn     Regeneration 

Whatis a 1937 romantic film starring Tyrone Power, Loretta Young, and Don Ameche.  The movie was directed by Tay Garnett and was the first film for which Power had top billing?
Love Is News     Rings on Her Fingers     Happy Land     The Littlest Rebel 

Whatis a 1992 romantic comedy starring Jack Nicholson and Ellen Barkin. It was directed by Bob Rafelson, and written by Carole Eastman, who together had been responsible for 1970's Five Easy Pieces?
Man Trouble     My Darling Clementine     Little Miss Broadway     Man Trouble 

Whatis a 1942 American wartime drama film starring Lloyd Nolan and Carole Landi?
Manila Calling     Heidi     The Lights of New York     The Song of Bernadette 

What is an American musical film. The only known footage to survive is a 12-minute fragment from the final reel in Multicolor at UCLA Film and Television Archive?
Married in Hollywood     The Pied Piper     Second Fiddle     Sunrise 

Whatis  the transition time period from one day to the next: the moment when the date changes. In the Roman time system, midnight was halfway between sunset and sunrise, varying according to the seasons?
Midnight     Tales of Manhattan     The Big Trail     Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm 

What is a 1947 Christmas film written and directed by George Seaton and based on a story by Valentine Davies?
Miracle on 34th Street     Madness of Youth     The Pied Piper     A Connecticut Yankee 

Whatis a 1947 musical film starring Betty Grable and Dan Dailey as married vaudeville performers, directed by Walter Lang?
Mother Wore Tights     The Littlest Rebel     Manila Calling     The Big Trail 

Whatis a 1935 Fox musical film directed by George Marshall. The movie stars Alice Faye and Bebe Daniels and is based on a play by Jesse Lasky Jr?
Music Is Magic     King of Burlesque     Liliom     Guadalcanal Diary 

Whatis a 1946 western movie. It was directed by John Ford and based on the book of the same name by Stuart Lake?
My Darling Clementine     Circus Cowboy     Music Is Magic     Captain from Castile 

What is a 20th Century Fox musical starring Rita Hayworth and Victor Mature. The film is a biopic of 1890s composer and songwriter Paul Dresser and singer Sally Elliot?
My Gal Sal     King of Burlesque     A Walk in the Sun     Sunrise 

Whatis a 1930 American musical film released by Fox Film Corporation, directed by Benjamin Stoloff?
New Movietone Follies of 1930     The Big Noise     Springtime in the Rockies     Sins of Man 

Whatis a novel by William Lindsay Gresham. It is a study of the lowest depths of showbiz and its sleazy inhabitants- the dark, shadowy world of a second rate carnival filled with hustlers, scheming grifters, and Machiavellian femme fatales?
Nightmare Alley     Springtime in the Rockies     Fig Leaves     Yankee Senor 

What is a 1965 war film starring Frank Sinatra, Clint Walker, Tatsuya Mihashi, Tommy Sands and Brad Dexter?
None But the Brave     Cavalcade     Green Grass of Wyoming     State Fair 

Whatis a 1937 American musical film directed by Roy Del Ruth and starring Dick Powell, Madeleine Carroll, Alice Faye George Barbier, and The Ritz Brothers?
On the Avenue     Thunder Birds     Crash Dive     A Tree Grows in Brooklyn 

Whatmay refer t?
One in a Million     Orchestra Wives     The Joy Girl     Delicious 

Whatis a 1942 American musical film by 20th Century Fox starring Ann Rutherford, George Montgomery, and Glenn Miller?
Orchestra Wives     Just Imagine     China Girl     Rose of Washington Square 

What is a journey or search of  moral or spiritual significance. Typically, it is a journey to a shrine or other location of importance to a person's beliefs and faith, although sometimes it can be a metaphorical journey into someone's own beliefs?
Pilgrimage     The Shocking Miss Pilgrim     Laura     The Song of Bernadette 

What is a model whose mass-produced pictures see wide appeal as popular culture?
Pin Up Girl     High Society Blues     Love Is News     Prince of Foxes 

Whatis a novel of historical fiction by Samuel Shellabarger, following the adventures of the fictional Andrea Orsini, a captain in the service of Cesare Borgia during his conquest of the Romagna?
Prince of Foxes     The Little Princess     Fallen Angel     The Rains Came 

Whatis an 1884 American novel written by Helen Hunt Jackson.  Set in Southern California after the Mexican-American War, it portrays the life of a mixed-race Scots-Native American orphan girl, who suffers racial discrimination and hardship?
Ramona     Orchestra Wives     Hollywood Cavalcade     To the Shores of Tripoli 

Whatis a classic American  1903 children's novel by Kate Douglas Wiggin that tells the story of Rebecca Rowena Randall and her two stern aunts in the village of Riverboro, Maine?
Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm     In Old Chicago     To the Shores of Tripoli     The Dolly Sisters 

Whatis a classic American  1903 children's novel by Kate Douglas Wiggin that tells the story of Rebecca Rowena Randall and her two stern aunts in the village of Riverboro, Maine?
Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm     Diamond Horseshoe     Cavalcade     Wake Up and Live 

Whator regenerative may refer t?
Regeneration     Berkeley Square     Barricade     None But the Brave 

Whatis a 1942 screwball comedy film starring Henry Fonda and Gene Tierney. A poor man gets mistaken for a millionaire and is swindled out of his life savings?
Rings on Her Fingers     Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm     High Society Blues     Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm 

Whatis a 1939 American musical drama film. Set in 1920s New York City, it focuses on singer Rose Sargent and her turbulent relationship with con artist Barton DeWitt Clinton, whose criminal activities threaten her professional success in the Ziegfeld Follies?
Rose of Washington Square     High Society Blues     The Three Musketeers     Guadalcanal Diary 

Whatis a term that refers to something that plays a secondary role in support of something that plays a more major or leading role?
Second Fiddle     Tess of the Storm Country     The Littlest Rebel     Rose of Washington Square 

Whatrefers to a romantic vacation for a married couple, taken some time after their honeymoon?
Second Honeymoon     Cavalcade     The Black Swan     Hollywood Cavalcade 

Whator 7th Heaven may refer t?
Seventh Heaven     Midnight     My Gal Sal     Second Honeymoon 

Whatis a 1942 musical comedy film starring Betty Grable and Victor Mature. It was directed by Walter Lang and released through 20th Century Fox?
Song of the Islands     The Iron Horse     Laura     Fallen Angel 

Whatis a Technicolor musical comedy film released by Twentieth Century Fox in 1942. A Betty Grable vehicle, with support from John Payne, Carmen Miranda, Cesar Romero, Charlotte Greenwood, and Edward Everett Horton?
Springtime in the Rockies     Bottoms Up     The Lights of New York     A Daughter of the Gods

What is an annual competitive and recreational gathering of a U.S. state's population, usually held in late summer or early fall?
State Fair     Charlie Chan in Paris     Pin Up Girl     Thunder Birds 

What is an annual competitive and recreational gathering of a U.S. state's population, usually held in late summer or early fall?
State Fair     That Wonderful Urge     Prince of Foxes     Four Jills in a Jeep 

What is a person who secretly boards a vehicle, such as an aircraft, bus, ship, cargo truck or train, to travel without paying and without being detected?
Stowaway     Gateway     Jane Eyre     Sunrise 

Whatmay refer t?
Street Angel     Fifty Roads to Town     Heaven Can Wait     Cameo Kirby 

What is a seaport city (population ca. 497,000) in north-eastern Egypt, located on the north coast of the Gulf of (a branch of the Red Sea), near the southern terminus of the Canal, having the same boundaries as governorate?
Suez     Cameo Kirby     Happy Land     Call Her Savage 

WhatSunny side up may refer t?
Sunny Side Up     Happy Landing     A Bell for Adano     None But the Brave 

What is the instant at which the upper edge of the Sun appears over the eastern horizon in the morning?
Sunrise     Greenwich Village     Charlie Chan Carries On     Jesse James 

Whatis a 1939 aviation film starring Alice Faye, Constance Bennett, Nancy Kelly, Joan Davis, Charles Farrell, and Jane Wyman?
Tail Spin     Girl Trouble     Love Under Fire     Ramona 

Whatis a 1942 American anthology film directed by Julien Duvivier. Thirteen writers, including Ben Hecht, Alan Campbell, Ferenc Molnár, Samuel Hoffenstein, and Donald Ogden Stewart worked on the six stories in this film?
Tales of Manhattan     Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm     The Shocking Miss Pilgrim     Liliom 

Whatmay refer t?
Tess of the Storm Country     China Girl     Judge Priest     Suez 

Whatis a 1948 American musical film directed by Ernst Lubitsch. The screenplay by Samson Raphaelson is based on the operetta Die Frau im Hermelin by Rudolph Schanzer and Ernst Welisch?
That Lady in Ermine     The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes     Wing and a Prayer     Footlight Serenade 

Whatis a 1948 20th Century Fox screwball comedy film, directed by Robert Sinclair and starring Tyrone Power and Gene Tierney?
That Wonderful Urge     My Gal Sal     Manila Calling     The Cowboy and The Countess 

Whatis a collection of twelve stories by Arthur Conan Doyle, featuring his famous detective and illustrated by Sidney Paget?
The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes     Springtime in the Rockies     Rendezvous 24     High Society Blues 

Whatis a 1949 romantic comedy Western film starring Betty Grable and featuring Cesar Romero and Rudy Vallee?
The Beautiful Blonde from Bashful Bend     A Walk in the Sun     Manila Calling     Midnight 

Whatis a 1944 comedy film starring Stan Laurel and Oliver Hardy. It was produced by Sol M. Wurtzel and directed by Mal St.Clair?
The Big Noise     Thin Ice     The Shocking Miss Pilgrim     Love Under Fire 

Whatis a 1930 lavish early widescreen movie shot on location across the American West starring John Wayne in his first leading role and directed by Raoul Walsh?
The Big Trail     Gateway     Judge Priest     East Lynne 

What is the common name for Cygnus atratus, an Australasian waterfow?
The Black Swan     Orchestra Wives     Mother Wore Tights     Laura 

Whatis a 1945 American biographical film about the Dolly Sisters, identical twins who became famous as entertainers on Broadway and in Europe in the early years of the twentieth century?
The Dolly Sisters     Suez     The Eve of St Mark     Sunrise 

Whatis a 1942 play by Maxwell Anderson set during World War II. It later became a 1944 film by 20th Century Fox that featured some of the same actors who repeated their roles in the film?
The Eve of St Mark     Sins of Man     The Magnificent Dope     Charlie Chan in Paris 

What areas from the end of World War II in 1945 until the end of the Cold War in 1991. The term symbolized efforts by the Soviet Union to block itself and its dependent and central European allies off from open contact with the west and non-communist areas?
The Iron Curtain     In Old Chicago     China Girl     Suez 

What is an iconic literary term (currently transitioning into an archaic reference) originating in the early Victorian culture (1825–35) when horses still powered most machinery, excepting windmills and stationary steam engines, the term was common and popular in both British and North American literary articles?
The Iron Horse     The Keys of the Kingdom     Cavalcade     Whirlpool 

What is an American silent comedy film starring Olive Borden, and based on the novel of the same name by May Edginton?
The Joy Girl     A Connecticut Yankee     Miracle on 34th Street     High Society Blues 

Whatis a 1941 novel by A. J. Cronin. Spanning six decades, it tells the story of Father Francis Chisholm, an unconventional Scottish Catholic priest who struggles to establish a mission in China?
The Keys of the Kingdom     The Luck of the Irish     Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm     The Little Princess 

Whatis a 1935 American comedy drama film directed by David Butler.  The screenplay by William M?
The Little Colonel     Happy Land     Springtime in the Rockies     King of Burlesque 

WhatLittle Princess may refer t?
The Little Princess     Diamond Horseshoe     Footlight Serenade     Springtime in the Rockies 

Whatis a 1935 American dramatic film directed by David Butler.  The screenplay by Edwin J?
The Littlest Rebel     The Song of Bernadette     Hollywood Cavalcade     Pilgrimage 

Whatmay refer t?
The Luck of the Irish     Charlie Chan in Shanghai     Heidi     My Darling Clementine 

What is a 1942 comedy film. As a publicity stunt, a down-on-his-luck success school operator searches for the least promising man in America to take his course?
The Magnificent Dope     Fallen Angel     Rendezvous 24     The Snake Pit 

What is the subject of a legend concerning the departure or death of a great number of children from the town of Hamelin (Hameln), Lower Saxony, Germany, in the Middle Ages?
The Pied Piper     Green Grass of Wyoming     Anna and the King of Siam     Dimples 

Whatis a 1917 American comedy-drama film directed by Maurice Tourneur. Adapted by Frances Marion from the 1913 play by Eleanor Gates?
The Poor Little Rich Girl     None But the Brave     The Pied Piper     Rendezvous 24 

Whatis a novel by Louis Bromfield, published in 1937, as well as the 1939 20th Century Fox film version which followed it?
The Rains Came     Springtime in the Rockies     Happy Days     Man Trouble 

Whatis a 1947 American musical comedy film written and directed by George Seaton, starring Betty Grable and Dick Haymes?
The Shocking Miss Pilgrim     Song of the Islands     Fig Leaves     In Old Chicago 

Whatis a 1948 American drama film directed by Anatole Litvak. The film tells the story of a woman who finds herself in an insane asylum and cannot remember how she got there, and stars Olivia de Havilland, Mark Stevens, Leo Genn, Celeste Holm, Beulah Bondi, and Lee Patrick?
The Snake Pit     My Darling Clementine     The Story of Alexander Graham Bell     Kiss of Death 

Whatis a 1943 drama film which tells the true story of Saint Bernadette Soubirous, who from February to July 1858 in Lourdes, France, reported eighteen visions of the Blessed Virgin Mary?
The Song of Bernadette     Captain January     Kiss of Death     The Iron Horse 

Whatis a somewhat fictionalized 1939 biographical film of the famous inventor?
The Story of Alexander Graham Bell     Jesse James     Four Jills in a Jeep     The Little Princess 

What is a novel by Alexandre Dumas, first serialized in March–July 1844. Set in the 17th century, it recounts the adventures of a young man named d'Artagnan after he leaves home to travel to Paris, to join the Musketeers of the Guard?
The Three Musketeers     A Daughter of the Gods    My Darling Clementine     Pilgrimage 

Whatmay refer t?
Thin Ice     Anna and the King of Siam     The Beautiful Blonde from Bashful Bend     My Gal Sal 

What is a novel by Eric Knight. It was adapted into an Academy Award winning movie in 194?
This Above All     Pin Up Girl     Fifty Roads to Town     The Keys of the Kingdom 

WhatThunderbird or Thunderbirds may refer t?
Thunder Birds     Delicious     Regeneration     My Darling Clementine 

Whatis a 1942 American Technicolor film starring John Payne, Maureen O'Hara, Randolph Scott, Nancy Kelly and Minor Watson?
To the Shores of Tripoli     Call Her Savage     That Wonderful Urge     Little Miss Broadway 

What]is a novel by Ivan Vazov written in 1888. It depicts the Ottoman rule of Bulgaria and is the most famous piece of classic Bulgarian literature?
Under the Yoke     Cheer Up and Smile     Hearts in Dixie     Tales of Manhattan 

What is the seventh episode of the sixth season of the fantasy television show Buffy the Vampire Slayer (1997–2003) and the only one in the series performed as a musical?
Under Your Spell     Fig Leaves     Song of the Islands     Jane Eyre 

Whatis a musical revue with a book by John Hastings Turner and music and lyrics by Cole Porter and others?
Wake Up and Dream     Under the Yoke     On the Avenue     A Connecticut Yankee 

Whatis a 1937 Fox musical film directed by Sidney Lanfield and produced by Darryl F. Zanuck?
Wake Up and Live     Happy Land     Just Imagine     Love Under Fire 

Whatis the name of a popular song with music by Bill Munro with words by Andrew B?
When My Baby Smiles at Me     China Girl     A Message to Garcia     This Above All 

What is a swirling body of water produced by the meeting of opposing currents. The vast majority of whirlpools are not very powerful?
Whirlpool     Sunrise     The Luck of the Irish     Jane Eyre 

Whatmay refer t?
Wilson     Barricade     Gateway     One in a Million 

What is a black-and-white 1944 war film about the heroic crew of an American carrier in the desperate early days of World War II in the Pacific theater, directed by Henry Hathaway and starring Dana Andrews and Don Ameche?
Wing and a Prayer     Sins of Man     Miracle on 34th Street     Charlie Chan Carries On 

