What is a form of locomotion or movement in which an organism or non-living (e.g., robotic) mechanical system propels itself through the air along a ballistic trajectory?
 Jumping    Speedball     International fronton    Snow kiting

What is a form of horse racing (primarily conducted in Ireland, the United Kingdom, Canada, United States, Australia and France) and derives its name from early races in which orientation of the course was by reference to a church steeple, jumping fences and ditches and generally traversing the many intervening obstacles in the countryside?
 Steeplechase    Fourball    Aerobic Gymnastics    Chinese Checkers

What is the main armament of the ?
16 Inch    Cue sports    Zui Quan    Bumper pool

What is an EP by the rock band Genesis. It was released in 1982. Its three songs were recorded during the Abacab sessions?
3x3     Aquakart    Pickup truck racing    Roller hockey

What is a mechanical puzzle, a 5×5×5 version of the Rubik's Cube.  It has qualities in common with both the original 3×3×3 Rubik's Cube and the 4×4×4 Rubik's Revenge, and knowing how to solve either can help when working on the 5×5×5 cube?
5x5x5    Dog sports    Red rover    Rugby league sevens

What is the controlled descent down a rock face using a rope. Climbers use this technique when a cliff or slope is too steep and/or dangerous to descend without protection?
Abseiling    Croquet    Korfball    Gaelic football

What is a combination of two or more endurance disciplines, including orienteering (if an orienteering map is used) and/or navigation (when non-orienteering maps are used), cross-country running, mountain biking, paddling and climbing and related rope skills?
Adventure racing    Ski jumping    Practical shooting    Metallic silhouette

What is the practice of flying maneuvers involving aircraft attitudes that are not used in normal flight?
Aerobatics    Basketball    Vintage racing    Reining

What is the ability to perform continuously complex and high-intensity movement patterns to music—which originates from traditional aerobics—with a high degree of perfectly executed elements of difficulty?
Aerobic Gymnastics    High jump    Wireball	    Xingyiquan

What is a form of inline skating executed on specially designed inline skates with focus on grinding and spins?
Aggressive inline skating    Spongee    Combine racing    Hurling

What is a game for two competing players trying to score points in the opposing player's goa?
Air hockey    Trick shot competition    Longboarding    Geocaching

What is a motorsport that involves airplanes competing over a fixed course, with the winner either returning the shortest time, the one to complete it with the most points, or to come closest to a previously estimated time?
Air racing    Shinty    Shotgun start    Land Kiteboarding

What is a sport   or recreational activity in which participants eliminate opponents by hitting each other with spherical non-metallic pellets launched via replica firearms?
Airsoft    Intercrosse    Mob football    Swing boarding

What is the sport of sliding down snow-covered hills on skis with fixed-heel bindings. It is also commonly known as downhill skiing, although that also incorporates different styles?
Alpine skiing    Artistic roller skating    Toss juggling    Color guard 

What is a mixed-gender, non-contact version of rugby union and is a variant of the sport Tag Rugby?
American flag rugby    Sea kayaking    Swedish football     Volata

What is a team sport. It is played by two teams, eleven players to a side, who advance an oval ball  over a rectangular field that is 120 yards long by 53.3 yards wide and has goalposts at both ends?
American football    Roller derby    Arena football    Sport fishing

What is a sport in which players use their hands to hit a small rubber ball against a wall so that it bounces off in such a way that their opponent cannot return it?
American handball    Dodgeball    Disc golf    Backpacking 

What is a method of fishing by means of an "angle" (fish hook). The hook is usually attached to a fishing line and the line is often attached to a fishing rod?
Angling    Lawn bowls    Noodling    Practical shooting

What is the art, practice, or skill of propelling arrows with the use of a bow, from Latin arcus. Historically, archery has been used for hunting and combat, while in modern times, its main use is that of a recreational activity?
Archery    Caid     Desert racing    Ice Climbing

What is a variety of gridiron football played by the Arena Football League (AFL). It is a proprietary game, the rights to which are owned by Gridiron Enterprises, and is played indoors on a smaller field than American or Canadian outdoor football, resulting in a faster and higher-scoring game?
Arena football    English billiards    Wolf hunting    Toss juggling

What is a type of wrestling (a combat sport) with two participants. Each participant places one arm (either the right or left, but both must be the same) on a surface with their elbows bent and touching the surface, and they grip each other's hand?
Arm Wrestling    International fronton    F1 Powerboat Racing    Wheelchair rugby league

What is a form of competitive indoor cycling in which athletes perform tricks (called exercises) for points on specialized, fixed-gear bikes in a format similar to ballet or gymnastics?
Artistic cycling    Aquathlon     Pradal Serey    Horizontal bar

What is a discipline of gymnastics where gymnasts perform short routines (ranging from approximately 30 to 90 seconds) on different apparatus, with less time for vaulting (see lists below)?
Artistic gymnastics    Speedball     Tang Soo Do    Sack race

What is a shot played on a billiards table (most often a pool table, though snooker tables is also used), which seems unlikely or impossible or requires significant skill?
Artistic pool    Wood chopping    Ribbon     Boule lyonnaise

What is a sport similar to figure skating but where contestants run on roller skates instead of ice skates?
Artistic roller skating    Aquathlon     Bodyboarding    Camping 

What is a sport played between two teams of typically eleven players, though other variations in player numbers such as 5 and 7 is also played, with a spherical ball?
Association football    Pencak Silat    Aerobatics     Legends car racing

What is marketed as AFL, after the Australian Football League, the only fully professional  league) is a sport played between two teams of 18 players on the field on either an Australian Football ground, a modified cricket field or similar sized sports venue?
Australian football    Sambo     Freediving    Triple jump

What is a sport where players hit a ball against one or more wall?
Australian handball    Kitesurfing    Fistball    Formula Student

What is a sport where players hit a ball against one or more wall?
Australian Handball    Indoor short track    Skysurfing    Trap shooting

What is a sport which was started in Australia during World War II when U.S. soldiers wanted to play a form of football against the Australians?
Austus    Fastnet     Eton Fives    Ninjutsu

What is a motorsport involving the racing of automobiles for competition?
Auto Race    Wireball	    Rope     5x5x5

What is the biggest form of amateur motor racing in Britain. It takes place at venues throughout England, Wales, Scotland, Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland?
Autograss    Rec footy    Samoa Rules    Rugby football

What is a version of medieval football played in Scotland, perhaps most notably in Orkney and the Scottish Borders, around Christmas and New Year?
Ba game    Truck racing    Hurling    Campdrafting

What is one of the oldest board games for two players. The playing pieces are moved according to the roll of dice, and players win by removing all of their pieces from the board?
Backgammon    Test cricket		 	    Bobrun cycling    Boccia

What is one of the four swimming styles regulated by FINA, and the only regulated style swum on the back?
Backstroke    Harpastum    Drag racing    Tapball

What is a billiards-derived indoor table game, the object of which is to get a number of balls (set at nine in the 19th century) past wooden pins (which act as obstacles) into holes?
Bagatelle    Alpine skiing    Eton field game    Rugby football

What is one of the three main Chinese martial arts of the Wudang school, the other two being Taijiquan and Xingyiquan?
Baguazhang    Western Pleasure    Mesoamerican ballgame    Fricket 

What is an artistic gymnastics apparatus, as well as the event performed using the apparatus?
Balance beam     Bartitsu    Go     Bicycle Motocross or BMX

What is the overarching title of a large array of carom billiards games generally played with two  and a third, red , on a -covered, 5 foot × 10 foot, less table that is divided by  on the cloth into marked regions called ?
Balkline and straight rail    Speed pool    Rugby league    Harpastum

What is a round, usually spherical but sometimes ovoid, object with various uses. It is used in ball games, where the play of the game follows the state of the ball as it is hit, kicked or thrown by players?
Ball     Military Service Rifle    Australian handball    Ice Racing

What is a sport native to India. It is a racket game, played with a yellow ball made of wool, on a court of fixed dimensions (12 by 24 metres) divided by a net?
Ball badminton    Calisthenics    Royaking    Sport stacking

What is a team sport and a variation of the sport of ice hockey and a specific variation of the game of street hockey?
Ball hockey    Trick shot competition    Matball    Roller hockey 

What is a defensive style of thaing focusing on animal-based techniques. The earliest meanings of the word were self-discipline, self-development and self-improvement?
Bando    Downhill mountain biking    Snowshoeing    Trailer racing

What is a defensive style of thaing focusing on animal-based techniques. The earliest meanings of the word were self-discipline, self-development and self-improvement?
Bando     Skimboarding    Paragliding    Cnapan

What is a team winter sport played on ice, in which skaters use sticks to direct a ball into the opposing team's goal?
Bandy    Croquet    Checkers    Bocce

What is a tarmac or dirt track racing type of motorsport event popularised in both North America and Europe and especially United Kingdom, Ireland, Belgium and the Netherlands in which drivers of old vehicles race against one another around a race track and the race is won in terms of the first car to the chequered flag?
Banger racing    Unicycling    Toboggan    Ancient games

What is a pool (pocket billiards) game that has as its most fundamental requirement that all scoring shots in the game must be made by  a called ball off a  and into a called pocket?
Bank pool    Royal Shrovetide Football    Volleyball    Hot box 

What is a form of billiards which is often thought to be based on the traditional game of bagatelle?
Bar billiards    Dressage    Noodling    Gig racing

What is a rodeo event in which a horse and rider attempt to complete a clover-leaf pattern around preset barrels in the fastest time?
Barrel Racing    Parachuting    Boxing    Sambo 

What is an eclectic martial art and self-defence method originally developed in England during the years 1898–1902. In 1901 it was immortalised (as "baritsu") by Sir Arthur Conan Doyle, author of the Sherlock Holmes mystery stories?
Bartitsu    Skijoring    Friskee    Ba game

What is an activity where participants jump from fixed objects and use a parachute to break their fall?
BASE jumping    Roller skating    Bokator    Water basketball

What is a pocket billiards (pool) game suitable for multiple players that borrows phraseology and even some aspects of form from the game of baseball?
Baseball pocket billiards    Canoe Polo    Juggling club    Sabaki Ball

What is a team sport, the objective being to shoot a ball through a horizontally positioned basket to score points, while following a set of rules?
Basketball    Color guard     Slopestyle    Kite flying

What is a North American medieval combat sport where participants use mock foam-padded weapons (boffer) in live action battles?
Battle gaming    Wood chopping    Superbike racing    Speedball 

What is a modified version of basketball, played on beaches. It was invented in the USA by Philip Bryant?
Beach basketball    Geo caching    Superbike racing    Beach soccer

What is a team sport where two teams pass and bounce a ball, trying to throw it in the goal of the opposing team?
Beach handball    Adi Murai    Stroke play    Silat

What is a sport that can be based on either of the rugby football codes, league or union. There is no centralized regulation of the sport as in beach soccer or beach volleyball, but leagues are common across Europe, and the sport is particularly popular in Italy?
Beach rugby    Caid     Ringette    Wakeboarding

What is a variant of association football played on a beach or some form of sand?
Beach soccer    Freediving    Racquetball    Red rover

What is an Olympic team sport played by two teams of two players on a sand court divided by a net?
Beach volleyball    Cornish hurling     Steeplechase    Dressage

What is the hunting mainly of hares, but also rabbits, and occasionally foxes with beagles by scent?
Beagling    Box lacrosse    Legends car racing    Australian Handball

What is an exercise of the upper body. While on their back, the person performing the bench press lowers a weight to the level of the chest, then pushes it back up until the arm is straight?
Benchpress    Calva    Snow kiting    Indoor field hockey

What is a sport in which very accurate and precise rifles are shot at paper targets. The rifles ride on a front and rear rest, the rests may or may not be joined, depending on the rules of a particular competition?
Benchrest shooting    Formula Libre    Lacrosse    Chinese Checkers

What is any sporting event made up of two disciplines. However, biathlon usually refers specifically to the winter sport that combines cross-country skiing and rifle shooting?
Biathlon    Tricking    Letterboxing     Shotgun start

What is a team sport, similar to traditional polo, except that bicycles are used instead of horses?
Bicycle polo    Sand drags    Benchrest shooting    Rugby league nines

What is the name of a sport, which resembles an aquatic variation of Volleyball. It has originated in Brazil, in the city of Birigüi, in the 60's by Prof?
Biribol    Catch wrestling    Pentathlon    Eton wall game

What is a rejection in a traditional form of secret ballot, where a white ball or ballot constitutes a vote in support and a black ball signifies opposition?
Blackball     Train racing    Hunter    Kneeboarding

What is  a snowboard competition in which a group of snowboarders (typically four or six) start simultaneously atop an inclined course and race to reach the finish line first?
Boardercross    Cuju    Aerobatics    Speed skating

What is a winter sport in which teams of two or four make timed runs down narrow, twisting, banked, iced tracks in a gravity-powered sled?
Bobsleigh    Silambam    Swamp football    Box lacrosse

What is a ball sport belonging to the boules sport family, closely related to bowls and pétanque with a common ancestry from ancient games played in the Roman Empire?
Bocce    Straight pool     One Day International	    Contesting

What is a precision ball sport, similar to bocce, and related to bowls and pétanque. The name  is derived from the Latin word for boss – bottia?
Boccia    Roller skating    American flag rugby    Gig racing

What is a surface water sport in which the surfer rides a bodyboard on the crest, face, and curl of a wave which is carrying the surfer towards the shore?
Bodyboarding    Broomball    Streetboarding    Backstroke

What is the use of progressive resistance exercise to control and develop one's musculature. An individual who engages in this activity is referred to as a bodybuilder?
Bodybuilding    Goaltimate    Archery    Fricket 

What is a Cambodian martial art that includes weapons technics?
Bokator    Train racing    Battle gaming    Formula racing

What is a sport invented in Spain by Filip Eyckmans who developed the concept 2004.  It is similar to volleyball, but also includes elements of football (soccer), gymnastics and capoeira?
Bossaball    A Bracciuta    Ice sledge hockey    Mountainboarding

What is a hybrid billiards game combining aspects of both carom billiards and pocket billiards?
Bottle pool    Duckpin bowling    Canoeing    Arm Wrestling

What is a style of rock climbing undertaken without a rope and normally limited to very short climbs over a padded mat called a crash pad or bouldering mat so that a fall will not result in serious injury?
Bouldering    Hammer throw    F1 Powerboat Racing    One Day International	

What is a pool game often used as a training . The game borrows aspects of ten-pin bowling. The game is divided into ten frames where a player gets a maximum of two innings to  ten balls?
Bowlliards    Practical shooting    Mountain unicycling    Race Walking

What is a sport in which the objective is to roll biased balls so that they stop close to a smaller ball called a  "jack" or "kitty"?
Bowls    ATV Racing    Beach handball    Ultramarathon

What is an indoor version of lacrosse played mostly in North America?
Box lacrosse    Military Service Rifle    Ancient games    Bando 

What is a swimming style in which the swimmer is on his or her chest and the torso does not rotate?
Breaststroke    Czech handball    Mixed martial arts    Hamster racing

What are by many considered one of the top tag-teams in history?
British Bulldogs     Camogie    ATV Racing    Olympic weightlifting

What is a recreational ice game originating in Canada and played around the world. It is played in a hockey rink, either indoors or outdoors, depending on climate and location?
Broomball    Volleyball    Creeking    Orienteering

What is an international Ninja organization based in Japan and headed by Masaaki Hatsumi?
Bujinkan    Demolition derby    Klootschieten    Royal Shrovetide Football

What is a traditional spectacle of Spain, Portugal, southern France and some Hispanic American countries (Mexico, Colombia, Ecuador, Venezuela and Peru) and the Philippines, in which one or more bulls are baited, and then killed in a bullring for the entertainment of the audience?
Bull fighting    Beach basketball    Janggi    Floor 

What is a pocket billiards game played on an octagonal or rectangular table fitted with an array of fixed cushioned obstacles, called bumpers, at the center of its surface?
Bumper pool    Lawn bowling    Gliding    Toboggan

What is a game that is thought to have been created by Russian soldiers to pass the time while stationed in northern Siberia during the early nineteenth century (although a 16th-century painting exists which may or may not show bunnock being played)?
Bunnock    Rotation     Synchronized swimming    Yukigassen

What is a swimming stroke swum on the breast, with both arms moving simultaneously, accompanied by the butterfly kick (also known as the "dolphin kick")?
Butterfly stroke    Harpastum    Jogo do Pau    Hillclimbing

What is the Central Asian sport played among Kazakhs, Afghans, Uzbeks, Hazaras, Tajiks, Kyrgyz, Turkmens and Pashtuns?
Buzkashi    Endurance racing     Canoe polo    Shidokan

What is the cradle of this sport, that became known as giuoco del calcio fiorentino ("Florentine kick game") or simply calcio (later being the name applied to football in Italian)?
Calcio Fiorentino    Drifting     Sprint football    Shidokan

What is a form of exercise consisting of a variety of simple, often rhythmical, movements, generally without using equipment or apparatus?
Calisthenics    Clean and jerk    Hot air ballooning    Bandy

What is a department in the Lower Normandy region in northwestern France. It takes its name from a cluster of rocks off the English Channel coast?
Calva    Valencian pilota    Volleyball    Practical shooting

What is a popular sport in Pakistan, Saudi Arabia, Egypt, Bahrain, Jordan, Qatar, United Arab Emirates, Oman,  Australia, and Mongolia?
Camel racing    Power hockey    Underwater ice hockey    Benchrest shooting

What is a team sport originating on the Isle of Man. It is closely related to the Scottish game of shinty and is similar to the Irish hurling?
Cammag    Cubbies    Stock car racing    Road racing

What is an Irish stick-and-ball team sport played by women; it is almost identical to the game of hurling played by men?
Camogie    Taekwondo    Trugo    Steeplechase 

What is a unique Australian sport involving a horse and rider working cattle. The riding style is like that of Western riding and the event is somewhat related to the American events such as cutting, working cow horse, team penning, and ranch sorting?
Campdrafting    Tower running    Jogo do Pau    Clean and jerk

What is a form of gridiron football played  in Canada in which two teams of 12 players each compete for territorial control of a field of play  long and  wide attempting to advance a pointed prolate spheroid ball into the opposing team's scoring area (end zone)?
Canadian football    Combat robot    Shinty    Nordic skiing

What is a variation of bowling that is played primarily in the Canadian Maritime provinces, Ontario, Quebec, and the New England states of Maine, Massachusetts, New Hampshire, and Vermont?
Candlepin bowling    Muay Thai    Ssireum    Field lacrosse

What is a competitive ball sport played on water, in a defined "field", between two teams of five players, each in a kayak?
Canoe polo    Muay Thai    Hoop     Fox hunting

What is a competitive ball sport played on water, in a defined "field", between two teams of five players, each in a kayak?
Canoe Polo    Shuffleboard    Durango boot    MCMAP

What is a paddle sport in which you kneel or sit facing forward in an open-decked canoe, and propel yourself with a single-bladed paddle, under your own power?
Canoeing    Casting     Board track racing    Footbag 

What is traveling in canyons using a variety of techniques that may include other outdoor activities such as walking, scrambling, climbing, jumping, abseiling (rapelling), and/or swimming?
Canyoning     Hill Climb    Shot put    Touring car racing

What is a traditional outdoor sport where two teams each have a flag (or other marker) and the objective is to capture the other team's flag, located at the team's "base", and bring it safely back to their own base?
Capture the flag    Finswimming    F1 Powerboat Racing    Baseball pocket billiards

What is the overarching title of a family of billiards games generally played on cloth-covered, 5 by 10 feet (approximately 1.5 × 3 m) pocketless tables, which often feature heated slate beds?
Carom billiards    ITHF table hockey    Hiking    Desert racing

What is a two-wheeled, human-powered land vehicle that is closely related to the skateboard and the snakeboard?
Casterboarding    Touch football     Flag football    Caid 

What is a classical hybrid grappling style that was developed in Britain circa 1870 by Mr. J. G?
Catch wrestling    Wood chopping    Yak polo    Road racing

What is a competitive event similar to rodeo and was developed from animal husbandry practices used on the haciendas of old Mexico?
Charreada    Knattleikr    Hana Ichi Monme    Breaststroke

What is an intense physical activity based upon organized routines, usually ranging anywhere from one to three minutes, which contains many components of tumbling, dance, jumps, cheers and stunting in order to direct spectators of events to cheer for sports teams at games or to participate in cheerleading competitions?
Cheerleading    Sky Race    Judo    Mountaineering

What is a two-player strategy board game played on a chessboard, a checkered gameboard with 64 squares arranged in an eight-by-eight grid?
Chess    Bull riding    Rugby league nines    Squash 

What is a hybrid sport that combines chess with boxing in alternating rounds. The sport was invented by French artist and filmmaker Enki Bilal in his comic book Froid Équateur in 1992. The first real event of chess-boxing was organized by Dutch artist Iepe Rubingh in 2003. Chess boxing is a fast growing sport, with large followings in Berlin and London, where most events take place?
Chessboxing    Laser tag    Laser tag    Sambo 

What is a city in the U.S. state of Illinois, and is the third most populous city in the United States, and the most populous city in the American Midwest with over 2.7 million residents?
Chicago     Equitation    Desert racing    Sprint 

What is a traditional sport in Chile. It was declared the national sport in 1962. It has since thrived, especially in the more rural areas of the country?
Chilean rodeo    Darts    Test cricket		 	    Isle of Man TT

What is a strategy board game which can be played by two, three, four, or six people, playing individually or with partners?
Chinese Checkers    Kneeboarding    Bottle pool    Individual Medley

What is a form of American handball popular on the streets of New York City, Philadelphia, and Bridgewater, NJ during the 1960s,'70s, and '80s and is still played today, mostly in New York City, Philadelphia, and San Diego?
Chinese handball    Bagatelle    Ribbon     Benchrest shooting

What is the traditional sport of Burma (Myanmar).  is a combination of sport and dance, a team sport with no opposing team?
Chinlone    Chinese Checkers    Sprint     Palla

What is the art of shooting at special flying targets, known as clay pigeons or clay targets, with a shotgun or any type of firearm?
Clay pigeon shooting    Field handball    Chinese handball    Bocce

What is a lift that is a composite of two weightlifting movements: the clean and the jerk?
Clean and jerk    Powered hang glider    Toboggan    Golf

What is a form of archery in which archers shoot arrows at a flag (known as "the Clout") from a relatively long distance and score points depending on how close each arrow lands to the flag?
Clout archery    Slacklining    Abseiling    Rossall Hockey

What is a form of ballooning where a harness attaches a balloonist to a cluster of helium-inflated rubber balloons?
Cluster ballooning    Wireball	    Long jump    Squash 

What is a Welsh name for a Celtic form of medieval football?
Cnapan    Lawn bowling    Folkrace    Rope climbing

What is a type of rowing performed at sea.  Due to the harsher conditions encountered, the boats are wider and more robust than those used on rivers and lakes?
Coastal and ocean rowing    Horseshoes     Hide and seek    Snowboarding

What is a hobby/sport in which two or more custom-built machines use varied methods of destroying or disabling the other?
Combat robot    Individual Medley    Ski touring    Benchrest shooting

What is a sport in which participants compete against each other to consume large quantities of food in a short time period?
Competitive eating    Deer hunting    Zourkhaneh    Duckpin bowling

What is a competitive activity pursued by amateur radio operators.  In a contest, an amateur radio station, which may be operated by an individual or a team, seeks to contact as many other amateur radio stations as possible in a given period of time and exchange information?
Contesting    Indoor netball    Palla    Race of Champions

What is an outdoor team game of Celtic origin played only in Cornwall, United Kingdom?
Cornish hurling    Whitewater kayaking    Suicide     Letterboxing 

What is an animal herder who tends cattle on ranches in North America, traditionally on horseback, and often performs a multitude of other ranch-related tasks?
Cowboy     Rugby union    Target archery    Petanque

What is a competitive shooting sport that originated in Southern California, USA, in the early 1980s?
Cowboy Action Shooting    Gaelic handball    Kronum    Dancing

What is a variation of polo played mostly in the western United States. Like regular polo, it is played in chukkars (periods) with two teams on horses who use mallets to hit a ball through a goal?
Cowboy polo    Boule lyonnaise    Disc golf    Group Gymnastics

What is a branch of canoeing and kayaking that involves descending very steep low-volume whitewater?
Creeking    Shorinji Kempo    Rally Raid    Equitation

What is a card game traditionally for two players, but commonly played with three, four, or more, that involves playing and grouping cards in combinations which gain points?
Cribbage     Footbag     Shuffleboard    Canoeing

What is a sport that involves hitting plastic or wooden balls with a mallet through  (often called "wickets" in the United States) embedded in a grass playing court?
Croquet    Candlepin bowling    swimming     Hurling

What is a form of ski touring in which participants propel themselves across snow-covered terrain using skis and poles?
Cross country skiing    Adventure racing    Horseshoe    Toe wrestling

What is a fitness company founded by Greg Glassman (with Lauren Glassman) in 2000.  CrossFit's exercise program is practiced by members of approximately 6,100 affiliated gyms,  most of which are located in the United States, and by individuals who complete daily workouts posted on the company's website or workouts prescribed by a coach at a local affiliate?
Crossfit    Blackball     Banger racing    Sepak takraw

What is an informal variant on football originating spontaneously in different parts of the world?
Cubbies    Fistball    Midget car racing    Twenty20	

What is a wide variety of games of skill generally played with a cue stick which is used to strike billiard balls, moving them around a cloth-covered billiards table bounded by rubber ?
Cue sports    Chess    MCMAP    Jujutsu

What is an ancient ball game with similarities to association football. It is seen by FIFA as the earliest form of football for which there is evidence, being first mentioned as a military training exercise in the 2nd-3rd century BCE?
Cuju    Catch wrestling    Rugby league    Land speed records

What is an unincorporated community in Jennings Township, Crawford County, Indiana. It is a populated place that is not incorporated and has no legal boundaries?
Curby    Chess    Bar billiards    Camping 

What is a sport in which players slide stones across a sheet of ice towards a target area which is segmented into four rings?
Curling    Cushion caroms    Fly Fishing    Luge

What is a carom billiards discipline generally played on a cloth-covered, 5 foot × 10 foot, pocketless table with two cue balls and a third red-colored ball?
Cushion caroms    Sepak Takraw    Parallel Bars    Aggressive inline skating

What is a species of freshwater fish in the salmon family of order Salmoniformes?
Cutthroat     Isle of Man TT    Wakesurfing    Pond hockey

What is an outdoor ball game which was created in 1905 in Prague and is still played today?
Czech handball    Bossaball    Bowling    Sumo

What is a type of art that generally involves movement of the body, often rhythmic and to music. It is performed in many cultures as a form of emotional expression, social interaction, or exercise, in a spiritual or performance setting, and is sometimes used to express ideas or tell a story?
Dancing    Kinomichi    Sprint     Woggabaliri

What is a form of throwing game in which darts are thrown at a circular target (dartboard) fixed to a wall?
Darts    Russian pyramid    Double disc court    Ice Racing

What is a weight training exercise where a loaded barbell is lifted off the ground from a stabilized, bent over position?
Deadlifting    Kite landboarding    Squirt Boating    Rope climbing

What is basketball played by deaf people.  Sign language is used to communicate whistle blows and communication between players?
Deaf basketball    Indoor soccer    Javelin throw    Indoor soccer

What is contention in argument; dispute, controversy; discussion; esp. the discussion of questions of public interest in Parliament or in any assembly?
Debating    Frisian handball    Muay Thai    Varpa

What is a combined event in athletics consisting of ten track and field events. The word decathlon is of Greek origin, from δέκα (déka, meaning "ten") and ἄθλος (áthlos, or ἄθλον, áthlon, meaning "feat")?
Decathlon    Skiboarding    Bumper pool    Ringo 

What is survival hunting or sport hunting for deer, which dates back tens of thousands of years?
Deer hunting    5x5x5    Uneven Bars    Mod league

What is a motorsport usually presented at county fairs and festivals. While rules vary from event to event, the typical demolition derby event consists of five or more drivers competing by deliberately ramming their vehicles into one another?
Demolition derby    Tennikoit    F1 Powerboat Racing    Sport fishing

What is the act of racing through the desert in a 2 or 4 wheeled off-road vehicle. Races, which generally consist of two or more loops around a course covering up to 40 miles, can take the form of His and Hound or Hare scramble style events, and are often laid out over a long and harsh track through relatively barren terrain?
Desert racing    Team handball    Rallying    Boccia

What is the activity of sailing small boats by using five essential control?
Dinghy sailing    Biathlon    Chinese Checkers    Hydroplane racing

What is the art and practice of conducting negotiations between representatives of groups or states?
Diplomacy     Bartitsu    Roller skating    Savate

What is one of the names given to the practice of riding bikes over cement type jumps of dirt or soil and becoming airborne?
Dirt jumping    Kick the can    Bagatelle    A Brazzos

What is a type of auto racing performed on oval tracks. It began in the United States before World War I and became widespread during the 1920s and 30s?
Dirt track racing    Arm Wrestling    Judo    Street football 

What is the more generic name for what is commonly called  Frisbee dog.  In disc dog competitions, dogs and their human flying disc throwers compete in events such as distance catching and somewhat choreographed freestyle catching?
Disc dog    Sepak Takraw    Scuba Diving    Kickball

What is a flying disc game in which individual players throw a flying disc at a target. According to the Professional Disc Golf Association, "The object of the game is to traverse a course from beginning to end in the fewest number of throws of the disc." The number of disc golf courses has more than doubled in 8 years from 2000 to 2008. The game is played in about 40 countries around the world?
Disc golf    Street hockey    Field archery    Caid 

What is a game in which players on two teams try to throw large balls at each other while avoiding being hit themselves?
Dodgeball    Chinese Checkers    Kenjutsu    Taido

What is an organized, competitive industry in which greyhound dogs are raced around a track?
Dog Racing    Individual Medley    Cushion caroms    Horseshoes 

What is activities that involve dog?
Dog sports    Rhythmic gymnastics    Static trapeze    Outrigger canoeing

What is a time trial event held on a steep, rough terrain that often features jumps, rock gardens and other obstacles?
Downhill mountain biking    San shou    Swing boarding    La soule

What is a form of drag racing which takes place on water rather than land?
Drag boat racing    Unicycle basketball    Sea kayaking    Road bicycle racing

What is a competition in which specially prepared automobiles or motorcycles compete, usually two at a time, to be first to cross a set finish line?
Drag racing    Street football     Equitation    Cushion caroms

What is a  human-powered watercraft traditionally made in the Pearl River Delta region of China's southern Guangdong Province out of teak wood to various designs and sizes?
Dragon boat    Bando    Auto Race    Yak polo

What is a competitive equestrian sport, defined by the International Equestrian Federation as "the highest expression of horse training", where "horse and rider are expected to perform from memory a series of predetermined movements."  Competitions are held at all levels from amateur to the World Equestrian Games?
Dressage    Indoor archery    Torball    Cubbies

What is an athletic event that consists of a running leg, followed by a cycling leg and then another running leg in a format bearing some resemblance to triathlons?
Duathlon    Paragliding    Haidong Gumdo    Powered hang glider

What is a variation of 10-pin bowling. The balls used in duckpin bowling are 4-3/4 in (12 cm) to 5 in (12.7 cm) in diameter (which is slightly larger than a softball), weigh 3 lb 6 oz  (1.5 kg) to 3 lb 12 oz (1.7 kg) each, and lack finger holes?
Duckpin bowling    Dog sports    Hydroplane racing    Freestyle scootering

What is the Filipino style of wrestling while standing upright and refers to the grappling aspect of Filipino martial arts?
Dumog    Streetball    Motocross    Ultimate 

What is a competitive, non-contact sport that makes use of a flying disc (known popularly by the trademark Frisbee), somewhat similar to Ultimate?
Durango boot    Hapkido    Swedish football     Dog Racing

What is a sporting event in which participants must balance an egg or similarly shaped item upon a spoon and race with it to the finishing line?
Egg and spoon race    Team penning    Shidokan    Pommel Horse

What is the Modern Egyptian term for a traditional form of Egyptian folk dance involving a wooden stick, also known as "stick dance" or "cane dance"?
Egyptian stick fencing    Footbag     Friskee    Crab soccer

What is a variant of polo played whilst riding elephants. It is played in Nepal, Sri Lanka, Rajasthan (India), and Thailand?
Elephant polo    Red rover    Glima    Canoeing

What is the ability of an organism to exert itself and remain active for a long period of time, as well as its ability to resist, withstand, recover from, and have immunity to trauma, wounds, or fatigue?
Endurance    Hurdles     Throwing    Letterboxing 

What is an equestrian sport based on controlled long-distance races.  It is one of the international competitions recognized by the FEI?
Endurance riding    Squash     Streetluge    Jeet Kune Do

What is a form of motorcycle sport run on courses that are predominantly off-road.  consists of many different obstacles and challenges?
Enduro    Mod league    Taekkyeon    Sports acrobatics

What is most often described as gymnastics and dance on horseback?
Equestrian vaulting    Flyak    Streetboarding    Rossall Hockey

What is the art or practice of horse riding or horsemanshi?
Equitation    Contesting    Bossaball    Modern pentathlon

What is a British independent boarding school located in Eton, near Windsor in England?
Eton College    Roller hockey    Clay pigeon shooting    Gymkhana

What is one of two codes of football devised and played at Eton College. The other is the Eton Wall Game?
Eton field game    Boccia    Creeking    Street football 

What is a game similar to football and rugby union, that originated from and is still played  at Eton College?
Eton wall game    Kemari    Steeplechase     Wrestling

What is an equestrian event where a single horse and rider combination compete against other combinations across the three disciplines of dressage, cross-country, and show jumping?
Eventing    Individual Medley    Deer hunting    Haxey Hood

What is an international motorboat racing competition for powerboats organised by the Union Internationale Motonautique (UIM) and promoted by H2O Racing, hence it often being referred to as F1H2O?
F1 Powerboat Racing    Eskrima    Equestrian vaulting    Sipa

What is a form of softball played commonly by women and men, though coed fast-pitch leagues also exist?
Fast Pitch    Fullbore target rifle    Slow Pitch    Bounceball

What is typically divided into Olympic fencing, Classical fencing and historical fencing,. The sport of fencing (commonly called olympic fencing or competitive fencing) is divided into three weapon categories: foil, sabre and épée?
Fencing    Banger racing    Shaolin kung fu    Shurikenjutsu

What is an endurance test or stunt in which ferrets are trapped in trousers worn by a participant?
Ferret legging    English public school football games    Pole vault    Sand drags

What is now handball and was played at the 1936 Summer Olympics in Berlin?
Field handball    Bottle pool    Wheelchair basketball    Canoeing

What is a team sport of the hockey family which is played between two teams of eleven players with hockey sticks and a hard, solid plastic ball?
Field Hockey    Windsurfing    Tricking    Harpastum

What is a full contact outdoor men's sport played with ten players on each team?
Field lacrosse    Air hockey    Lacrosse    Czech handball

What is an outdoor air gun discipline originating in the United Kingdom, in the early 1980s, but gaining popularity worldwide?
Field target    Skibobbing    Offshore powerboat racing    Jacquet 

What is a sport and activity in which individuals, duos, or groups perform on figure skates on ice?
Figure skating    Jeu de paume    Tapball    Pencak Silat

What is the progression of a swimmer using monofins or normal swimfins (called bifins or stereofins within the sport) either on the water surface or underwater, using only muscle strength?
Finswimming    Floorball    Triathlon    Suicide 

What is a sport of European origin. It is similar to volleyball in that players try to hit a ball over a net?
Fistball    Spongee    Red rover    Horseball

What is an English sport believed to derive from the same origins as many racquet sports. In fives, a ball is propelled against the walls of a special court using a gloved or bare hand as though it were a racquet?
Fives    Mountain unicycling    Aggressive inline skating    Stock car racing

What is a version of American football or Canadian football where the basic rules of the game are similar to those of the mainstream game (often called "tackle football" for contrast), but instead of tackling players to the ground, the defensive team must remove a flag or flag belt from the ball carrier ("deflagging") to end a down?
Flag football    Racquetball    Arm Wrestling    Keep Away

What is the art, practice, or skill of propelling arrows with the use of a bow, from Latin arcus. Historically, archery has been used for hunting and combat, while in modern times, its main use is that of a recreational activity?
Flight archery    Basketball    Biathlon    High Power Rifle

What is the walking surface of a room or vehicle. Floors vary from  in a cave to many-layered surfaces using modern technology?
Floor     16 Inch    Nordic combined    Eton Fives

What is an indoor team sport which was developed in the 1970s in Sweden?
Floorball    Flutterguts    Flying disc freestyle    Duckpin bowling

What is a hydrofoil adaptation to the conventional kayak. It uses twin hydrofoils designed to raise the hull out of the water to increase the speed?
Flyak    Touch rugby    Toboggan    Skijoring

What is a specific form of the trapeze in which a performer jumps from a platform with the trapeze so that gravity makes the trapeze swing?
Flying trapeze    Bumper pool    Water Polo    Rugby league sevens

What is a popular, inexpensive, and entry-level form of Swedish rallycross that originally came from Finland, where it was called Jokamiesluokka (Everyone's Class)?
Folkrace    Tag Rugby    Beach soccer    Tee Ball

What is both a small, round bag, and the term for the various sports played with one – characterized by controlling the bag by using one's feet?
Footbag     Equitation    Mod league    Vault 

What is a sport in which players kick a footbag over a five-foot-high net. Players may use only the feet?
Footbag net    Freeride mountain biking    Freeboating    Team handball

What is a sport which combines aspects of beach volleyball and association football (also known as soccer in some English-speaking countries)?
Footvolley    Ssireum    Ski touring    3x3 

What is a form of automobile racing allowing a wide variety of types, ages and makes of purpose-built racing cars to compete "head to head"?
Formula Libre    Catch wrestling    Camel racing    Mountainboarding

What is any of several forms of open-wheeled single-seater motorsport. The origin of the term lies in the nomenclature that was adopted by the FIA for all of its post-World War II single-seater regulations, or ?
Formula racing    Gateball    Banzai skydiving    Pocket Cube

What is a student engineering competition held annually in the UK. Student teams from around the world design, build, test, and race a small-scale formula style racing car?
Formula Student    Knattleikr    Indoor cricket    Freestyle BMX

What is a type of golf match used in match play competition?
Fourball    Backgammon    Hammer throw    Hydroplane racing

What is a type of match in the sport of gol?
Foursome     Pocket Cube    Unicycling    British Bulldogs 

What is an activity involving the tracking, chase, and sometimes killing of a fox, traditionally a red fox, by trained foxhounds or other scent hounds, and a group of unarmed followers led by a master of foxhounds, who follow the hounds on foot or on horseback?
Fox hunting    Roller skating    Boxing    Killer 

What is a holistic training discipline using movement that developed out of military obstacle course training?
Free running    Hiking    American handball    Skateboarding

What is a branch of whitewater kayaking that combines playboating and creeking?
Freeboating    Juttejutsu    Jianzi    Hide and seek

What is a form of underwater diving that relies on a diver's ability to hold his or her breath until resurfacing rather than on the use of a breathing apparatus such as scuba gear?
Freediving    Synchronized swimming    Barrel Racing    Bull fighting

What is a discipline of mountain biking closely related to downhill cycling and dirt jumping focused on tricks, style, and technical trail features?
Freeride mountain biking    Ski jumping    Bicycle Motocross or BMX    Kabaddi

What is a synonym for BMX stunt riding, a sport branch that hails from extreme sports. It consists of five disciplines: street, park, vert, trails, and  flatland?
Freestyle BMX    Fast Pitch    Snow kiting    Telemark skiing

What is the art of expressing yourself with a football, while performing various tricks with any part of the body?
Freestyle Football    Bartitsu    Hana Ichi Monme    Regularity rally

What is a variation on the sport of motocross in which motorcycle riders attempt to impress judges with jumps and stunts?
Freestyle Motocross    Mod league    Bunnock    Tent pegging

What is an action sport which involves using scooters (also known as kick scooters) to perform freestyle tricks, in a manner similar to skateboarding and BMX freestyle?
Freestyle scootering    Street hockey    English public school football games    Vault 

What is a form of skiing which originally encompassed two disciplines: aerials, and moguls?
Freestyle skiing    Juggling club    Field archery    Wrestling

What is a highly technical field of skating that involves performing tricks around a straight line of equally spaced cones?
Freestyle slalom skating    Episkyros    Bujinkan    Powerbocking

What is a winter sport that involves descending a slope that is covered with snow while standing on a board attached to a rider's feet, using a special boot set onto a mounted binding?
Freestyle snowboarding    Letterboxing     Skysurfing    Bouldering

What is a category of swimming competition, defined by the rules of the International Swimming Federation (FINA), in which competitors are subject to only limited restrictions on their swimming stroke?
Freestyle swimming    Sporting clays    Atlatl    Clean and jerk

What is a traditional Frisian sport, related to American handball and fives, that is most commonly practiced by people from the northern Dutch province of Friesland (Fryslân)?
Frisian handball    Unicycle basketball    Enduro    Northern Praying Mantis

What is a Southern Chinese martial art which originated in Fujian (福建) province and is now practiced throughout the world?
Fujian White Crane    Varpa    Freestyle Motocross    Canoe Polo

What is a distinctively British and Commonwealth of Nations shooting discipline that evolved from Service rifle (SR) shooting in the late 1860s, and is governed in the UK by the rules of the National Rifle Association, UK (NRA)?
Fullbore target rifle    Dog sports    Pehlwani    Silambam

What is a variant of association football that is played on a smaller pitch and mainly played indoors?
Futsal    Squirt Boating    Stroke play    Tee Ball

What is a sport played in Ireland where players hit a ball with a hand or fist against a wall in such a way as to make a shot the opposition cannot return, and that may be played with two (singles) or four players (doubles)?
Gaelic handball    Aerobatics      Steeplechase    Casterboarding

What is a mallet team sport similar to croquet.  It is a fast-paced, non-contact, highly-strategic team game, which can be played by anyone regardless of age or gender?
Gateball    Hooverball    Paintball    Unicycle hockey

What is a weapon-based martial art associated with the Punjab region. It has also traditionally been practiced by other ethno-cultural groups in India and Pakistan?
Gatka    Kuk Sool Won    Dodgeball    Fox hunting

What is an outdoor recreational activity, first played in May 2000, in which the participants use a Global Positioning System (GPS) receiver or mobile device and other navigational techniques to hide and seek containers, called "geocaches" or "caches", anywhere in the world?
Geo caching    Fujian White Crane    Keep Away    Shorinji Kempo

What is an outdoor recreational activity, first played in May 2000, in which the participants use a Global Positioning System (GPS) receiver or mobile device and other navigational techniques to hide and seek containers, called "geocaches" or "caches", anywhere in the world?
Geocaching    Rugby sevens    Ice yachting    Gaelic handball

What is a recreational activity and competitive air sport in which pilots fly unpowered aircraft known as gliders or sailplanes using naturally occurring currents of rising air in the atmosphere to remain airborne?
Gliding    Folkrace    Surf fishing    Whitewater kayaking

What is the Old Norse word that covers several types of Scandinavian folk wrestlin?
Glima    Road racing    Lapta     Video game

What is one of the major positions of association football?
Go     Stock car racing    Ancient games    Lumberjack

What is a team sport designed specifically for blind athletes, originally devised in 1946 by the Austrian Hans Lorenzen and German Sepp Reindle as a means of assisting the rehabilitation of visually impaired World War II veterans?
Goalball    team handball    Royal Shrovetide Football    Underwater football

What is a half-court disc game derived from ultimate, similar to hot box. The object is to score points by throwing a flying disc to a teammate in a small scoring area, through a large semicircular hoop called the goal?
Goaltimate    Dirt jumping    Universal football    Ninjutsu

What is a precision club and ball sport in which competing players (or golfers) use many types of clubs to hit balls into a series of holes on a course using the fewest number of strokes?
Golf    Moscow broomball    Powered paragliding    Alpine skiing

What is the premier championship of motorcycle road racing. It is currently divided into three classes: MotoGP, Moto2 and Moto3. All three classes use four-stroke engines?
Grand Prix motorcycle racing    Sport kite     Medley swimming    Road racing

What is a form of motorcycle racing which typically, in its current form,  takes place on a flat track consisting of two straights and two bends usually constructed in a field?
Grass Track    Powered hang glider    Kenjutsu    Auto Race

What is football primarily played in the United States and Canada?
Gridiron football    Uppies and Downies    Patball    Swing boarding

What is a water buffalo horn-based composite reflex bow, standardized about 1900 AD from the variety of such weapons in earlier use?
Gungdo    Iaijutsu    MCMAP    Chinese handball

What is a tube by which bilaterian animals transfer food to the digestion organs?
Guts     Hoop     Bumper pool    Dinghy sailing

What is a typical Anglo-Indian expression, which is derived from the Hindi-Urdu word Jamat-khana, is an Indian term which referred to a place of assembly?
Gymkhana    Aerobatics    Mob football    Pig racing

What is a Scottish sport involving the hurling of a haggis as far as possible for distance and accuracy from atop a platform (usually a whisky barrel)?
Haggis hurling    Race Walking    Freestyle skiing    Kite flying

What is a road running event of . It is half the distance of a marathon and usually run on roads?
Half marathon    Hwa Rang Do    Pocket billiards     Metallic silhouette

What is a sport in which hamsters are placed in hamster wheels or hamster balls – often fitted to miniature racing vehicles – and raced down a straight 9 meter (30 ft) course?
Hamster racing    Canyoning     Butts Up    Soap shoes

What is an air sport in which a pilot flies a light and non-motorized foot-launch aircraft called a hang glider that is of a delta wing design?
Hang gliding    Competitive Marching Band    Road crawling    Haidong Gumdo

What is a dynamic and also  eclectic Korean martial art?
Hapkido    Trial    Sepak takraw    Touring car racing

What is the pursuit of hares with greyhounds and other sighthounds, which chase the hare by sight and not by scent?
Hare coursing    Beach basketball    Horseball    Kite landboarding

What is a form of horse racing in which the horses race at a specific gait (a trot or a pace)?
Harness racing    Fullbore target rifle    Kickball    Modified Pitch

What is a code of football played between two teams of eleven players, each attempting to win by scoring more bases (goals) than their opponent?
Harrow Football    Vovinam    Trailer racing    Fistball

What is a traditional event in at the village of Haxey in North Lincolnshire, England, on the afternoon of 6 January, the Twelfth Day of Christmas (though if this falls on a Sunday, it is held on 5 January)?
Haxey Hood    Matball    Palla    Western Pleasure

What is a track and field combined events contest made up of seven events. The name derives from the Greek hepta (seven) and athlon (contest)?
Heptathlon    Bodyboarding    Cutthroat     Swamp football

What is a track and field athletics event in which competitors must jump over a horizontal bar placed at measured heights without the aid of certain devices?
High jump    Freestyle scootering    Duckpin bowling    Hill Climb

What is a specific format of competitive shooting popular in the United States. It is many times referred to as "Across the Course" and sometimes as 'traditional' High Power?
High Power Rifle    Heptathlon    Bandy    Egyptian stick fencing

What is an outdoor activity which consists of walking in natural environments, often in mountainous or other scenic terrain?
Hiking    Capoeira    Squash     Tang Soo Do

What is a branch of motorsport in which drivers compete against the clock to complete an uphill course?
Hill Climb    Dog Racing    Segway polo    Pencak Silat

What is a branch of motorsport in which drivers compete against the clock to complete an uphill course?
Hillclimbing    Novuss    Bouldering    Capture the flag

What is a family of sports in which two teams play against each other by trying to maneuver a ball or a puck into the opponent's goal using a hockey stick?
Hockey    Ball hockey    Ball hockey    Bumper pool

What is a colourful bird that is found across Afro-Eurasia, notable for its distinctive 'crown' of feathers?
Hoop     Woggabaliri    Roller hockey     Tent pegging

What is a medicine ball game invented by President Herbert Hoover's personal physician to help keep then-President Hoover fit?
Hooverball    Boxing    Crab soccer    Demolition derby

What is an apparatus used by male gymnasts in Artistic Gymnastics?
Horizontal bar    Kitesurfing    Snowkiting    Eton wall game

What is a team sport played on horseback in which the objective is to score goals against an opposing team?
Horse polo    Benchpress    Banzai skydiving    Jianzi

What is an equestrian sport that has a long history. Archaeological records indicate that horse racing occurred in ancient Greece, Babylon, Syria, and Egypt?
Horse racing    Lawn bowls    Horseshoes     Charreada

What is a game played on horseback where a ball is handled and points are scored by shooting it through a high net (approximately 1.5m×1.5m)?
Horseball    Human powered aircraft    Sipa    Calva

What is a fabricated product, normally made of metal, although sometimes made partially or wholly of modern synthetic materials, designed to protect a horse's hoof from wear?
Horseshoe    Beach volleyball    Volleyball    Horseball

What is the activity of flying hot air balloons.  Attractive aspects of ballooning include the exceptional quiet  (except when the propane burners are firing), the lack of a feeling of  movement, and the bird's-eye view?
Hot air ballooning    Lelo burti    Samoa Rules    Cluster ballooning

What is the term used when an axle bearing overheats on a piece of railway rolling stock.  The term is derived from the journal-bearing trucks used before the mid-20th century?
Hot box     Roller skating    Vintage racing    Kart racing

What is an aircraft belonging to the human-powered vehicles. It is powered by direct human energy and the force of gravity; the thrust provided by the human may be the only source; however, a hang glider that is partially powered by pilot power is a human-powered aircraft where the flight path can be enhanced more than if the hang glider had not been assisted by human power?
Human powered aircraft    Sport aerobics    Association football    Calcio Fiorentino

What is the practice of pursuing any living thing, usually wildlife or feral animals, by humans for food, recreation, or trade?
Hunter    Sand drags    Longboarding    Table Tennis 

What is a type of track and field rac?
Hurdles    Paralympic association football    Cribbage     Austus

What is an outdoor team game of ancient Gaelic origin, administered by the Gaelic Athletic Association?
Hurling    Carom billiards    Throwball    Fastnet 

What is a Korean martial art that was created by Joo Bang Lee and his brother Joo Sang Lee. This martial art teaches fighting techniques, weapons, spiritual training, intellectual enhancement, and artistic pursuits?
Hwa Rang Do    Wing Tsun    Balance beam     Shot put

What is a sport involving racing hydroplanes on lakes and rivers?
Hydroplane racing    Hwa Rang Do    Scuba Diving    Formula Libre

What is one of the Japanese koryū martial art disciplines in the education of the classical warrior (bushi)?
Iaijutsu    Indoor short track    Casting     Gridiron football

What is the activity of ascending inclined ice formations. Usually, ice climbing refers to roped and protected climbing of features such as icefalls, frozen waterfalls, and cliffs and rock slabs covered with ice refrozen from flows of water?
Ice Climbing    Aerobatics     Wheelstand competition    Bobsleigh

What is a form of racing that uses cars, motorcycles, snowmobiles, all-terrain vehicles, or other motorized vehicles?
Ice racing    Shaolin kung fu    Roller skating    Calva

What is a form of racing that uses cars, motorcycles, snowmobiles, all-terrain vehicles, or other motorized vehicles?
Ice Racing    Knattleikr    Pentathlon    Kite buggy

What is moving on ice by using ice skates. It can be done for a variety of reasons, including health benefits, leisure, traveling, and various sports?
Ice skating    Artistic gymnastics    Spongee    Street football 

What is a sport that was designed to allow participants who have a physical disability to play the game of ice hockey?
Ice sledge hockey    Sport stacking    Field lacrosse    Andartza

What is the sport of sailing and racing iceboats, also called ice yachts. It is practiced in Austria, Germany, Great Britain, Poland, Norway and Sweden, to some extent, and is very popular in the Netherlands and on the Gulf of Finland, but its highest development is in the United States and Canada?
Ice yachting    Folkrace    Speed skating    Team handball

What is a combination of four different swimming styles —Butterfly, Backstroke, Breaststroke, and Freestyle— into one race?
Individual Medley    Flight archery    Sports acrobatics    Mini footy

What is football played indoors. While varied, the rules of indoor football are specifically designed to allow for play in a smaller area which would normally be used for a sport such as basketball or ice hockey?
Indoor American football    Beach soccer    Ulama    Backpacking 

What is a variant of and shares many basic concepts with cricket. The game is most often played between two teams each consisting of six or eight players?
Indoor cricket    Rallycross    Bicycle Motocross or BMX    Xiangqi

What is a hybrid motorcycle competition, a mix of supercross, trials, and enduro racing held indoors over obstacles resembling a trials track?
Indoor enduro    Table football    Drag racing    Snow kiting

What is an indoor variant of "traditional" outdoor field hockey. It is not to be confused with other indoor hockey variants such as rink hockey or floorball?
Indoor field hockey    Biribol    Snowkiting    Ball hockey

What is a variation of netball, played exclusively indoors, in which the playing court is surrounded on each side and overhead by a net?
Indoor netball    Aquakart    Wood chopping    Street hockey

What arena soccer, or six-a-side football in the United Kingdom, is a game derived from association football adapted for play in an indoor arena such as a turf-covered ice hockey arena or skating rink?
Indoor soccer    Sand drags    Boardercross    Pankration

What is a team sport played on an appropriate smooth surface, in which skaters use wooden or composite sticks to shoot a hard plastic puck into their opponent's net?
Inline hockey    Mountainboarding    Boule lyonnaise    Beach rugby

What is the roller sport of racing on inline skates. It is often called inline racing by participants?
Inline speed skating    Janggi    Charreada    Skittles 

What is a non-contact form of lacrosse with a standardized set of rules using intercrosse equipment?
Intercrosse    Russian pyramid    Board track racing    Twenty20	

What is an indirect style ball game created for to come together some varieties (such as American handball, Basque pelota, Gaelic handball and Valencian fronto) and be played in the Handball International Championships?
International fronton    Indoor cricket    Bull riding    Gig racing

What is a sport played on table hockey games. The International Table Hockey Federation (ITHF) uses only table hockeys made by Stiga?
ITHF table hockey    Road racing    Streetboarding    Land sailing

What is a strategy board game popular in Korea?
Janggi    Atlatl    Rugby sevens    Kurash

What is a track and field athletics event where the javelin, a spear about  in length, is thrown?
Javelin throw    Wakeboarding    Eskrima    Sport kite 

What is an eclectic/hybrid system and philosophy of life founded by martial artist Bruce Lee  with direct, non classical, and straightforward movements?
Jeet Kune Do    ATV Enduro    Novuss    Rugby league sevens

What is a form of racing sport in which jetboats with a crew of two race individually against the clock through twisting series of channels in less than a metre of water?
Jet sprint boat racing    Video game    Lumberjack    Sport fishing

What is a ball-and-court game that originated in France. It was an indoor precursor of tennis played without racquets, though these were eventually introduced?
Jeu de paume    Water Polo    Ringo     Butts Up

What is a traditional Asian game in which players aim to keep a heavily weighted shuttlecock in the air by using their bodies, apart from the hands, unlike in similar games peteca and indiaca?
Jianzi    Rugby Fives    Unicycle basketball    Yoga

What is a Portuguese martial art which developed in the northern regions of Portugal (Minho and Trás-os-Montes), focusing on the use of a staff of fixed measures and characteristics?
Jogo do Pau    Backstroke    Indoor cricket    Bobsleigh

What is a sport which combines aspects of volleyball and football (soccer?
Jokgu    if u look at this article ur stupid    Fast Pitch    Systema

What is a modified form of 2 on 2 Association football taking influence from squash and football?
Jorkyball    American flag rugby    Wingsuit flying    Hammer throw

What is a prop used by jugglers, as are other props such as balls or rings?
Juggling club    Basketball    Bando     Uppies and Downies

What is a Japanese martial art and a method of close combat for defeating an armed and armored opponent in which one uses no weapon or only a short weapon?
Jujutsu    Medieval football    Horse racing    Jujutsu

What is a South Asian team sport. The name is derived from the Tamil word (கை-பிடி) "kai" (hand), "pidi" (catch), which is translated into "Holding Hands"?
Kabaddi    Bossaball    Harpastum    Model aircraft

What is a hybrid martial art that combines Western Boxing, Judo, Jujutsu, Kenpo Karate, Eskrima, Tang Soo Do, and Kung Fu?
Kajukenbo    Rally raid    Synchronized skating    Hiking

What is an Indian martial art from the southern state of Kerala. One of the oldest fighting systems in existence, it was originally practiced in northern and central parts of Kerala and the Tulunadu region of Karnataka?
Kalarippayattu    Disc golf    Baseball pocket billiards    Unicycle basketball

What is a martial art developed in the Ryukyu Islands in what is now Okinawa, Japan. It was developed partially from the indigenous martial arts of Ryukyu Islands called  and from Chinese kenpo?
Karate    Dinghy sailing    Wiffleball    Tetherball

What is a variant of open-wheel motorsport with small, open, four-wheeled vehicles called karts, go-karts, or gearbox/shifter karts depending on the design?
Kart racing    Laser tag    Indoor American football    Shorinji Kempo

What is a pocket billiards game played on a standard pool table using fifteen numbered markers called peas or pills, and a standard set of sixteen pool balls?
Kelly pool    Powerlifting    Ultramarathon    Field lacrosse

What is a ball game that was popular in Japan during the Heian Period.  has been revived in modern times?
Kemari    Indoor American football    Orienteering    Medieval football

What is a modern Japanese  martial art/sport, which descended from traditional swordsmanship (kenjutsu) and uses bamboo swords (Shinai), and protective armor?
Kendo    Indoor cricket    Table Tennis     Jeet Kune Do

What is a Bangladeshi, Indian, Pakistani and South African sport played by teams of twelve players who try to avoid being touched by members of the opposing team, only 9 players of the team enter the field?
Kho kho    Road racing    Indoor American football    Combine racing

What is a children's game related to tag, hide and seek, and capture the flag which can be played outdoors, with as many as three to a few dozen players?
Kick the can    Capture the flag    Unicycle basketball    ATV Enduro

What is a playground game and league game, similar to baseball, invented in the United States in the first half of the 20th Century.  may also be known as kick baseball, base soccer, foot-base, soccer-base, or soccer-baseball. It is similar to baseball where players kick the ball to bat it instead of using bats, making it more accessible to young children. As in baseball, teams alternate innings with one team on the infield attempting to score by having its players circle the bases and the other team it the outfield working to stop runs from being scored.  Players in the infield kick an inflated rubber ball to advance players around the bases and thus score runs. The team with the most runs after a predefined number of innings (usually nine) win?
Kickball    Modified Pitch    Slamball    Iaijutsu

What is a group of martial arts and stand-up combat sports based on kicking and punching, historically developed from Karate, Muay Thai and Western boxing?
Kickboxing    Kart racing    Snowkiting    Time Attack

What is a light, purpose-built vehicle powered by a traction kite (power kite). It is single-seated and has one steerable front wheel and two fixed rear wheels?
Kite buggy    Crossfit    Biathlon    Snowkiting

What are kites used for the sport of kite fighting. Traditionally most are small, unstable single line flat kites where line tension alone is used for control, and an abrasive line is used to cut down other kites?
Kite fighting    Atlatl    Popinjay     Sprint 

What is a tethered aircraft. The necessary lift that makes the kite wing fly is generated when air flows over and under the kite's wing, producing low pressure above the wing and high pressure below it?
Kite flying    Masters Rugby League    Roller hockey    Speed skiing

What is based on the ever-growing sport of Kitesurfing, where a rider on a surf-style board is pulled over water by a kite?
Kite landboarding    Adventure racing    Cutthroat     Yubi lakpi

What is a surface water sport combining aspects of wakeboarding, windsurfing, surfing, paragliding, and gymnastics into one extreme sport?
Kitesurfing    Underwater rugby    Hana Ichi Monme    Rapid ball

What is an aquatic sport where the participant is towed on a buoyant, convex, and hydrodynamically shaped board at a planing speed, most often behind a motorboat?
Kneeboarding    Rope climbing    Tchoukball    Streetluge

What is an art, sport, combat skill, or variously an entertainment technique, involving an artist skilled in the art of throwing knives, the weapons thrown, and a target?
Knife throwing    Zourkhaneh    Carom billiards    Caid 

What is a mixed gender team sport, with similarities to netball and basketball. A team consists of eight players; four female and four male?
Korfball    Hill Climb    Zui Quan    Go 

What is a non-competitive tactical self-defense system developed in Israel that consists of a wide combination of techniques sourced from boxing, Muay Thai, Wing Chun, Judo, jiu-jitsu, wrestling, and grappling, along with realistic fight training?
Krav Maga    Kemari    Backgammon    Fistball

What is a sport which was invented in 2008 by Bill Gibson in Villanova, Pennsylvania. It is played only in the United States, with professional league games taking place in Philadelphia?
Kronum    Sports car racing    Racquetball    Free running

What is a Korean martial arts system founded by Suh In-Hyuk (; the Kuk Sa Nim or Grandmaster) in 1958. The name  translates to "National Martial Art Association" and despite often being shortened to 'Kuk Sool,' the name kuk sool (국술; 國術) is a non-trade marked name used to denote similar Korean martial arts developed prior to or about the same time as the formation of ?
Kuk Sool Won    Keep Away    Power hockey    Speedcubing

What is a number of fighting styles that have developed over the centuries in China?
kung fu    Half marathon    Popinjay     Drifting 

What is the Turkic term for "wrestling" (from Old Turkic keriš, c.f?
Kurash    Dragon boat    Metallic silhouette    Mongolian wrestling

What is a traditional team sport that originated in Normandy and Picard?
La soule    Ice skating    Mancala    Horseshoe

What is a team sport of Native American origin played using a small rubber ball and a long-handled stick called a crosse or lacrosse stick?
Lacrosse    Dog Racing    Silambam    Riverboarding

What is based on the ever-growing sport of Kitesurfing, where a rider on a surf-style board is pulled over water by a kite?
Land Kiteboarding    Legends car racing    Rinkball    Danish longball

What is the act of moving across land in a 3wheeled vehicle powered by wind through the use of a sail?
Land sailing    Cammag    Legends car racing    Czech handball

What is the highest speed achieved by a wheeled vehicle on land?
Land speed records    Universal football    ATV Racing    Juggling club

What is a sport similar to traditional windsurfing that is performed on land rather than water?
Land windsurfing    Rink bandy    Bungee jumping    Roller hockey 

What is a team or individual sport or recreational activity where players attempt to score points by tagging targets, typically with a hand-held infrared-emitting targeting device?
Laser tag    Royal Shrovetide Football    Bowlliards    Shaolin kung fu

What is a sport in which the objective is to roll biased balls so that they stop close to a smaller ball called a  "jack" or "kitty"?
Lawn bowling    Freeboating    Croquet    Tricking

What is a sport in which the objective is to roll biased balls so that they stop close to a smaller ball called a  "jack" or "kitty"?
Lawn bowls    Shotgun start    Fox hunting    Sand drags

What is a style of race car, designed primarily to promote exciting racing and to keep costs down?
Legends car racing    Diplomacy     Indoor trial    Freestyle skiing

What is a Georgian folk sport, which is a full contact ball game, and very similar to rugby?
Lelo burti    Eton Fives    Mud bogging    Powerbocking

What is an unarmed Burmese martial art. It is similar to related styles of Indochinese kickboxing, namely Muay Thai from Thailand, pradal serey from Cambodia, Muay Lao from Laos and tomoi from Malaysia?
Lethwei    Shooting sports    Camogie    Downhill mountain biking

What is a track and field event in which athletes combine speed, strength, and agility in an attempt to leap as far as possible from a take off point?
Long jump    Boardercross    Luge    Northern Praying Mantis

What is the act of riding on a longboard skateboard. A longboard is greater in size (both length and width) than its smaller counterpart, the skateboard, and has more stability, traction and durability due to lower wheel durometers?
Longboarding    Freestyle skiing    Rugby tens    Kite flying

What is a small one- or two-person sled on which one sleds supine (face up) and feet-first. Steering is done by flexing the sled's runners with the calf of each leg or exerting opposite shoulder pressure to the seat?
Luge    Mountain unicycling    Sports acrobatics    5x5x5

What is a worker in the logging industry who performs the initial harvesting and transport of trees for ultimate processing into forest products?
Lumberjack    Hooverball    Sepak takraw    Horse racing

What is a game that originated in China, commonly played by four players (with some three-player variations found in Korea and Japan)?
Mahjong    Road crawling    Tractor pulling    Metro footy

What is a person doing choreographed dance or movement, primarily baton twirling associated with marching bands during parades?
Majorettes    Kuk Sool Won    Trapeze    Banger racing

What is a family of board games played around the world, sometimes called "sowing" games, or "count-and-capture" games, which describes the gameplay?
Mancala    Tchoukball    Ringette    Kendo

What is a long-distance running event with an official distance of 42.195 kilometres (26 miles and 385 yards), that is usually run as a road race?
Marathon    Straight pool     Ultralight aviation    Wolf hunting

What is a collective name given to a number of traditional Indigenous Australian recreational pastimes believed to have been played at gatherings and celebrations of up to fifty players?
Marn Grook    Indoor trial    Silambam    Nordic combined

What is a derivative of rugby league for a wide age range of older, semi-retired and non-competitive players and officials?
Masters Rugby League    Skimboarding    Pocket billiards     Jujutsu

What areas it is known as Big Base, is a sport, usually played indoors but also sometimes outdoors, played in schools throughout the United States?
Matball    Paralympic association football    Danish longball    Rock Climbing

What is a scoring system for golf in which a player, or team, earns a point for each hole in which they have bested their opponents; this is as opposed to stroke play, in which the total number of strokes is counted over one or more rounds of 18 holes?
Match play    Fricket     Horseball    Pocket billiards 

What is a combat system developed by the United States Marine Corps to combine existing and new hand-to-hand and close quarters combat (CQC) techniques with morale and team-building functions and instruction in the Warrior Ethos?
MCMAP    Demolition derby    Ribbon     Pond hockey

What is a modern term sometimes used for a wide variety of localised football games which were invented and played in Europe of the Middle Ages?
Medieval football    Freediving    Target shooting    Subbuteo

What is a combination of four different swimming styles —Butterfly, Backstroke, Breaststroke, and Freestyle— into one race?
Medley swimming    Decathlon    Backpacking     Dodgeball

What is a group of target shooting disciplines that involves shooting at metal cutouts representing game animals at varying distances?
Metallic silhouette    Artistic cycling    Netball    Shot put

What is a modified version of Australian rules football rules played on gridiron football, rugby or Association football fields, predominantly in the United States of America?
Metro footy    Austus    Decathlon    Swedish football 

What are very small race cars with a very high power-to-weight ratio and typically use four-cylinder engines?
Midget car racing    Biribol    Lacrosse    Skittles 

What is a form of rugby league developed by the Australian Rugby League?
Mini footy    Kuk Sool Won    Bowling    Backpacking 

What is a form of rugby union designed to introduce the sport to children?
Mini rugby    Ice sledge hockey    Power hockey    Boardercross

What is a full contact combat sport that allows the use of both striking and grappling techniques, both standing and on the ground, from a variety of other combat sports?
Mixed martial arts    Underwater target shooting    Banger racing    Rope 

What is the name given to some varieties of Medieval football, which emerged in Europe during the Middle Ages?
Mob football    Synchronized skating    Horseshoe    Grass Track

What is a form of rugby league developed by the Australian Rugby League. It was developed to introduce children to rugby league?
Mod league    Sea kayaking    Episkyros    Draughts 

What are flying or non-flying small sized replicas of existing or imaginary aircraft using a variety of materials including paper, plastic, metal, synthetic resins, wood, foam and fibreglass?
Model aircraft    International rules football    Mini rugby    Snowboarding

What is the system of Filipino martial arts founded by the late Remy Presas as a self-defense system?
Modern Arnis    Powerchair Football    Paralympic volleyball    Taekkyeon

What is a sports contest that includes five events: pistol shooting,  fencing, 200 m freestyle swimming, show jumping, and a 3 km cross-country run?
Modern pentathlon    Show Jumping    Shorinji Kempo    Sports which use the wind 

What is the folk wrestling style of Mongols in Mongolia, Inner Mongolia (China) and other regions?
Mongolian wrestling    Hiking    Sepak Takraw    Atlatl

What is a pickup truck, typically styled after pickup trucks' bodies, modified or purposely built with extremely large wheels and suspension?
Monster truck    Sanshou    Midget car racing    Yak polo

What is a sport similar to ice-hockey played by non-Russians in Moscow. It is known by its players simply as "broomball", but is called  elsewhere to distinguish it from the similar sport of the same name played in Canada?
Moscow broomball    Squash     Disc golf    Time Attack

What is a form of motorcycle racing held on enclosed off-road circuits. The sport evolved from motorcycle trials competitions held in the United Kingdom?
Motocross    Sumo    Sea kayaking    Medieval football

What is a motorcycle sport involving four and sometimes up to six riders competing over four anti-clockwise laps of an oval circuit?
Motorcycle speedway    Shogi    Fastnet     Wolf hunting

What is an adventure sport that consists of traversing rough terrain on a unicycle.  ('muni') is undertaken on similar terrain to mountain biking?
Mountain unicycling    Mini rugby    Streetball    Lumberjack

What is a well established if little-known action sport, derived from snowboarding?
Mountainboarding    Sprint football    Footbag net    Flag football

What is the sport, hobby or profession of hiking, skiing, and climbing mountains?
Mountaineering    Kite landboarding    Pato    Road racing

What is a combat sport from the muay martial arts of Thailand that uses stand-up striking along with various clinching techniques?
Muay Thai    Bando     Kajukenbo    Toss juggling

What is a form of off-road motorsport popular in Canada and the United States in which the goal is to drive a vehicle through a pit of mud of a set length?
Mud bogging    Toe wrestling    Skater hockey    Harpastum

What is a ball sport played by two teams of seven players. Its development, derived from early versions of basketball, began in England in the 1890s?
Netball    Backpacking     Czech handball    Mahjong 

What is a ball game played as a variation of volleyball?
Newcomb ball    Royaking    Artistic pool    Catch wrestling

What is the martial art, strategy, and tactics of unconventional warfis and guerrilla warfis as well as the art of espionage purportedly practiced by the shinobi (commonly known outside of Japan as ninja)?
Ninjutsu    Kabaddi    Target archery    Military Service Rifle

What is fishing for catfish using only bare hands, practiced primarily in the southern United States?
Noodling    Sabaki Ball    Target shooting    Quidditch

What is a winter sport in which athletes compete in both cross-country skiing and ski jumping?
Nordic combined    Match play    Time Attack    Football tennis

What is a combination of winter sports that encompasses all types of skiing where the heel of the boot cannot be fixed to the ski, as opposed to Alpine skiing?
Nordic skiing    Team penning    Connect Four    Torball

What is a style of Chinese martial arts, sometimes called Shandong Praying Mantis after its province of origin?
Northern Praying Mantis    Ferret legging    Netball    Hurdles

What is a two-player (or four-player, doubles) game of physical skill which is closely related to carrom and pocket billiards?
Novuss    Show Jumping    Dinghy sailing    Underwater rugby

What is racing by large, specially designed ocean-going powerboats, typically point-to-point racing?
Offshore powerboat racing    Football tennis    Shuffleboard    Skijoring

What is an athletic discipline in the modern Olympic programme in which participants attempt a maximum-weight single lift of a barbell loaded with weight plates?
Olympic weightlifting    Yoga    Unicycle trials    Western Pleasure

What is a form of limited overs cricket, played between two teams with international status, in which each team faces a fixed number of overs, usually fifty?
One Day International	    Campdrafting    Formula Student    Table Tennis 

What is a family of sports that requires navigational skills using a map and compass to navigate from point to point in diverse and usually unfamiliar terrain, and normally moving at speed?
Orienteering    Fullbore target rifle    Riverboarding    Ball 

What is a sport in which an outrigger canoe (Va'a, waʻa, and waka ama in Tahitian, Hawaiian, and Māori languages, respectively; similar words are used in other Polynesian languages) is propelled by means of paddles?
Outrigger canoeing    Jeu de paume    Superside    Spearfishing

What is a non-contact team game in which each player wears a belt that has two velcro tags attached to it, or shorts with velcro patches?
Oztag    Gig racing    Gaelic handball    Indoor cricket

What is a sport in which players compete, in teams or individually, to eliminate opponents by tagging them with capsules containing water soluble dye and gelatin shell outside (referred to as paintballs) propelled from a device called a paintball marker (commonly referred to as a paintball gun)?
Paintball    Single scull    Slamball    Sea kayaking

What is a street in the City of Westminster, London, and parallel to The Mall, from St. James's Street across Waterloo Place to the Haymarket; while Pall Mall East continues into Trafalgar Square?
Pall mall     Andartza    Masters Rugby League    Mountaineering

What is a European style of architecture derived from and inspired by the designs of the Venetian architect Andrea dio (1508–1580)?
Palla    Orienteering    Aerobic Gymnastics    Moscow broomball

What is the action sport of exiting an aircraft and returning to Earth with the aid of gravity while using a parachute to slow down during the terminal part of the descent?
parachuting    Kinomichi    Football family    Wolf hunting

What is the action sport of exiting an aircraft and returning to Earth with the aid of gravity while using a parachute to slow down during the terminal part of the descent?
Parachuting    Outrigger canoeing    Hang gliding    Figure skating

What is the recreational and competitive adventure sport of flying paragliders: lightweight, free-flying, foot-launched glider aircraft with no rigid primary structure?
Paragliding    Hooverball    Kart racing    Ultramarathon

What is an apparatus used by male gymnasts in artistic gymnastics.  Gymnasts may optionally wear grips when performing a routine on the parallel bars, although this is uncommon?
Parallel Bars    Noodling    Modified Pitch    Modified Pitch

What is volleyball for disabled athletes entered the Paralympic Games as a demonstration sport for amputees in 1976 in Toronto Canada and played as a medal sport thereafter?
Paralympic volleyball    Downhill mountain biking    Ice yachting    Fricket 

What is a recreational kiting activity where a person is towed behind a vehicle (usually a boat) while attached to a specially designed canopy wing that reminds one of a parachute, known as a parasail wing?
Parasailing    BoÃŸeln    Ultimate     Deadlifting

What is a holistic training discipline using movement that developed out of military obstacle course training?
Parkour    Wing Tsun    Xingyiquan    Javelin throw

What is a non-contact competitive ball game played in many forms using one's hands or head to hit the ball against a wall - the objective being to get the succeeding player out?
Patball    Cuju    F1 Powerboat Racing    Cuju

What is a game played on horseback that combines elements from polo and basketball?
Pato    Cowboy     Horse racing    Twenty20	

What is a form of wrestling from South Asia?
Pehlwani    Horseball    Rink bandy    Grand Prix motorcycle racing

What is an umbrella term for the martial arts of Southeast asia parenthood from Silambam from India?
Pencak Silat    Hot air ballooning    Swing boarding    Gliding

What is a contest featuring five different events. The name is derived from Greek: combining the words pente (five) and -athlon (competition) ()?
Pentathlon    Bartitsu    Systema    Kart racing

What is a recreational watercraft that the rider rides or stands on, rather than inside of, as in a boat?
Personal water craft    Knife throwing    Vintage racing    Tapball

What is a form of boules where the goal is, while standing inside a starting circle with both feet on the ground, to throw hollow metal balls as close as possible to a small wooden ball called a cochonnet (literally "piglet") or jack?
Petanque    Kronum    Chessboxing    Czech handball

What is a traditional sport in Brazil, played with a "hand shuttlecock" from indigenous origins and reputed to be as old as the country itself?
Peteca    Casterboarding    Drifting     Fujian White Crane

What is an auto racing series, running in the United Kingdom, including races on both road courses and ovals?
Pickup truck racing    Frisian handball    Freestyle swimming    Orienteering

What is a sport in which juvenile pigs race around a small enclosed dirt, fake grass or gravel track?
Pig racing    Dancing    Haggis hurling    Alpine skiing

What is at least four main types of competitive pigeon spor?
Pigeon sport    Disc dog    Kurash    Fourball

What is an amateur sport, similar to golf also known as "chip and putt" by Dan Lickman. The maximum hole length for international competitions is  with a maximum total course length of ?
Pitch and putt    Marathon    Hammer throw    Beach volleyball

What is the family of cue sports and games played on a pool table having six receptacles called pockets along the , into which balls are deposited as the main goal of play?
Pocket billiards     Baseball pocket billiards    Cowboy polo    Balkline and straight rail

What is the 2×2×2 equivalent of a Rubik's Cube?
Pocket Cube    3x3     Charreada    Tee Ball

What is a track and field event in which a person uses a long, flexible pole (which today is usually made either of fiberglass or carbon fiber) as an aid to leap over a bar?
Pole vault    Competitive eating    Grand Prix motorcycle racing    Free running

What is a team sport played on horseback in which the objective is to score goals against an opposing team?
Polo    Table football    Carom billiards    Moscow broomball

What is a team sport that is played all over the world. It is a combination of polo and lacrosse?
Polocrosse    Table Tennis     Personal water craft    Whitewater kayaking

What is an artistic gymnastics apparatus. Traditionally, it is used by only male gymnasts?
Pommel Horse    Friskee    Kick the can    Sprint 

What is a form of ice hockey very similar in its object and appearance to traditional ice hockey, but far simpler and designed to be played on part of a natural frozen body of water?
Pond hockey    Dirt jumping    Artistic roller skating    American handball

What is a competitive, fast-paced hockey game based on the use of an electric powered wheelchair?
Power hockey    Freestyle snowboarding    Cnapan    Figure skating

What is an acrobatic sporting discipline which combines some of the skills of artistic gymnastics on the floor with those of trampolining?
Power Tumbling    Freestyle snowboarding    Chess    Gig racing

What is jumping and running with elastic-like spring-loaded stilts. For some it is an extreme sport, for others it is a form of exercise or even a means of artistic expression?
Powerbocking    Aquathlon     Mini footy    Kite flying

What is a competitive team sport for people with disabilities who use power wheelchairs?
Powerchair Football    Hammer throw    Human powered aircraft    Single scull

What is a powered hang glider harness with a motor and propeller in pusher configuration?
Powered hang glider    Sporting clays    Knattleikr    3x3 

What is a form of ultralight aviation where the pilot wears a motor on his back (a paramotor) which provides enough thrust to take off using an adapted paraglider or [http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Paramotor_Reflex_Wing_Profile paramotor wing]?
Powered paragliding    Freediving    Wheelstand competition    Tennikoit

What is a strength sport that consists of three attempts at maximal weight on three lifts: squat, bench press, and deadlift?
Powerlifting    Aggressive inline skating    Kelly pool    Chess

What is a sport which challenges an individual's ability to shoot rapidly and accurately with a full-power handgun, rifle, or shotgun?
Practical shooting    American flag rugby    Gaelic football    Skeleton 

What is an unarmed martial art from Cambodia. In Khmer the word pradal means fighting or boxing and serey means free?
Pradal Serey    ATV Racing    Tent pegging    Akroteri Punching

What is a ball game played as a variation of volleyball?
Prisoner Ball    La soule    Fistball    Freestyle BMX

What is a sport spawned by and similar to baseball, but without a pitcher, catcher, or ba?
Punchball     Steeplechase    Ribbon     Wingsuit flying

What is a competitive sport in the wizarding world of the Harry Potter universe, and is from the series of children's novels and movies?
Quidditch    Paintball    Surf fishing    Combat robot

What is an international motorsport event held at the end of each year, featuring some of the world's best racing and rally drivers?
Race of Champions    Western Pleasure    Street football     Pig racing

What is a long-distance athletic event. Although it is a foot race, it is different from running in that one foot must appear to be in contact with the ground at all times?
Race Walking    Bando    Klootschieten    Cowboy 

What is a racquet sport played with a hollow rubber ball in an indoor or outdoor court. Joseph Sobek is credited with inventing the modern sport of racquetball in 1950 (the outdoor, one-wall game goes back to at least 1910 in N.Y.C.), adding a stringed racquet to paddleball in order to increase velocity and control?
Racquetball    Darts    Marathon    Wolf hunting

What is the use of radio signals to remotely control a device?
Radio control    Sports acrobatics    Toss juggling    Ball hockey

What is the challenging recreational outdoor activity of using an inflatable raft to navigate a river or other bodies of water?
Rafting    Bumper pool    Super sport     Hang gliding

What is a form of long distance off-road racing that takes place over several days?
Rally raid    Tennikoit    Footbag     Streetboarding

What is a form of long distance off-road racing that takes place over several days?
Rally Raid    Marn Grook    Field archery    Eton wall game

What is a form of sprint style automobile racing, held on a closed mixed-surface racing circuit, with modified production or specially built road cars, similar to the World Rally Cars, although usually with about  stronger engines, due to e.g?
Rallycross    Freestyle BMX    Mahjong    Dragon boat

What is a form of auto racing that takes place on public or private roads with modified production or specially built road-legal cars?
Rallying    Canadian football    Flying disc freestyle    Connect Four

What is a relatively new sport derived from squash and racquetball.  It was invented by Peter V?
Rapid ball    Horseball    Sport kite     Stock car racing

What is a non-contact version of the Australian rules football game sanctioned by the Australian Football League?
Rec footy    Air racing    Shorinji Kempo    Bossaball

What is an outdoor game played primarily by children on playgrounds?
Red rover    Rugby Fives    ATV Enduro    Prisoner Ball

What is a western riding competition for horses where the riders guide the horses through a precise pattern of circles, spins, and stops?
Reining    Moscow broomball    Static trapeze    Gliding

What is a sport in which individuals or teams of 5 manipulate one or two pieces of apparatus: clubs, hoop, ball, ribbon, rope and Free (no apparatus)?
Rhythmic gymnastics    Egyptian stick fencing    Trugo    Group Gymnastics

What is a thin band of material, typically cloth but also plastic or sometimes metal, used primarily as decorative binding and tying?
Ribbon     Water basketball    Bobrun skating    Gateball

What is a team sport played on an ice surface. Played primarily by females,  uses the speed of hockey and the skill of basketball and requires the use of straight sticks to control a rubber ring; with the objective of the game being to score goals by shooting the ring into the opponent's net?
Ringette    Butts Up    Autocross     Motocross

What is a Japanese combat sport promotion that has lived three distinct periods: puroresu promotion from its inauguration to 1995, mixed martial arts promotion from 1995 to its 2002 disestablishment, and the revived mixed martial arts promotion from 2008 to date?
Rings     Grass Track    Train racing    Clay pigeon shooting

What are two very similar team sports.  originated in Sweden in the 1960s?
Rink bandy     Throwing    Sports where a player use a racquet     Scrabble

What are two very similar team sports. Rink bandy originated in Sweden in the 1960s?
Rinkball    Valencian pilota    Indoor soccer    Speedball 

What is a boardsport in which the participant lies prone on their board with fins on their feet for propulsion and steering?
Riverboarding    Shorinji Kempo    Freeride mountain biking    Gliding

What is a bicycle racing sport held on paved roads. The term "road racing" is usually applied to events where competing riders start simultaneously (unless riding a handicap event) with the winner being the first to the line at the end of the course (individual and team time trials is another form of cycle racing on roads)?
Road bicycle racing    Wing Tsun    Wheelchair rugby league    Juggling club

What is a general term used in North America for most forms of motor racing held on paved, purpose-built race tracks (i.e?
Road racing    Triple jump    Field target    Street football 

What is a hobby/sport in which two or more custom-built machines use varied methods of destroying or disabling the other?
Robot combat    Surfboat    Tetherball    Hapkido

What is an activity in which participants climb up, down or across natural rock formations or artificial rock walls?
Rock Climbing    Static trapeze    Indoor trial    Royal Shrovetide Football

What is fishing from rocky outcrops into the sea. It is a popular pastime in Australia and New Zealand?
Rock fishing    Kemari    Tapball    Rodeo

What is a cycling team founded in 2007 by Michael Ball. The team is affiliated with Ball's Rock & Republic clothing?
Rock racing    Modern pentathlon    Snowshoeing    Hot box 

What is a competitive sport which arose out of the working practices of cattle herding in Spain, Mexico, and later the United States, Canada, South America and Australia?
Rodeo    Freestyle Motocross    Combat robot    Artistic billiards

What is a sport of long distance cross-country navigation, involving both route planning and navigation between checkpoints using a variety of map types?
Rogaining    Riverboarding    Modified Pitch    Abseiling

What is a contact sport played by two teams of five members roller skating in the same direction around a track?
Roller derby    Powerbocking    Target shooting    Touch football 

What is a form of hockey played on a dry surface using skates with wheels. The term "Roller Hockey" is often used interchangeably to refer to two variant forms chiefly differentiated by the type of skates and sticks used?
Roller hockey    Desert racing    Folkrace    Kite buggy

What is the traveling on surfaces with roller skates. It is a form of recreational activity as well as a sport, and can also be a form of transportation?
Roller skating    Yoga    Canyoning     Baseball pocket billiards

What is a linear collection of plies, yarns or strands which are twisted or braided together in order to combine them into a larger and stronger form?
Rope     Benchrest shooting    Woggabaliri    Freestyle swimming

What is a sport in which competitors, usually men, attempt to climb up a suspended vertical rope using only their hands?
Rope climbing    Kart racing    Land speed records    Air hockey

What is a unique form of hockey played only at Rossall School, in Fleetwood, on the Fylde coast, Lancashire, England?
Rossall Hockey    Speedcubing    Chessboxing    Gymkhana

What is a circular movement of an object around a center (or point) of rotation. A three-dimensional object rotates always around an imaginary line called a rotation axis?
Rotation     American flag rugby    Rock fishing    Track racing

What is a handball game, similar to squash, played in an enclosed court. It has similarities with Winchester Fives (a form of Wessex Fives) and Eton Fives?
Rugby Fives    Footvolley    Flyak    Hunter

What is a style of football named after Rugby School in the United Kingdom. It is seen most prominently in two current sports, rugby league and rugby union?
Rugby football    Janggi    Field archery    Hurdles

What is a full contact sport played by two teams of thirteen players on a rectangular grass field?
Rugby league    Trugo    Polo    Novuss

What is a version of rugby league football played with nine players on each side?
Rugby league nines    Tetherball    Duckpin bowling    Cushion caroms

What is a seven-a-side derivative of rugby league football, which is usually a thirteen-a-side sport?
Rugby league sevens    Trap shooting    Kickball    Sambo 

What is a variant of rugby union in which teams are made up of seven players, instead of the usual 15, with shorter matches?
Rugby sevens    Paragliding    Jianzi    Sport climbing

What is a variant of rugby union in which teams are made up of ten players, typically five forwards and five backs?
Rugby tens    Ball hockey    Swordfighting    Rock Climbing

What is a full contact team sport which originated in England in the early 19th century?
Rugby union    Aikido    Taekwondo    Hapkido

What is a situation in the game of baseball that occurs when the baserunner is stranded between two bases and is in jeopardy of being tagged out?
Rundown     Powerlifting    Pato    Cowboy 

What is a means of terrestrial locomotion allowing humans and other animals to move rapidly on foot?
Running    Yak polo    Sikaran    Trial

What is a cue sport that has several differences from Western pool, although game play is still dominated by attempts to  () billiard balls?
Russian pyramid    Street racing    Chinese handball    Squash tennis

What is a competitive game in which participants place both of their legs inside a sack or pillow case that reaches their waist or neck and jump forward from a starting point toward a finish line?
Sack race    Powerlifting    Road crawling    Surf fishing

What is the propulsion of a vehicle and the control of its movement with large (usually fabric) foils called sails?
Sailing    Rink bandy    Race of Champions    Rotation 

What is a game derived from Australian rules football and rugby union that is occasionally played in Samoa?
Samoa Rules    Indoor netball    Touch rugby    Trapeze

What is a Chinese hand-to-hand self-defense system and combat sport?
San shou    Canadian football    BoÃŸeln    Cornish hurling

What is a board sport similar to snowboardin?
Sandboarding    Connect Four    Tchoukball    Underwater football

What is a Chinese hand-to-hand self-defense system and combat sport?
Sanshou    Sumo    Football tennis    Medieval football

What is a word game in which two to four players score points by forming words from individual lettered tiles on a gameboard marked with a 15×15 grid?
Scrabble    Andartza    Sports car racing    Rodeo

What is a form of underwater diving in which a diver uses a scuba set to breathe underwate?
Scuba Diving    Curling    Ultramarathon    Taido

What is a kayak developed for the sport of paddling on open waters of lakes, bays, and the ocean?
Sea kayaking    Reversi     Autograss    Bank pool

What is a team sport which started to gain some measure of popularity after being played by members of the Bay Area Segway Enthusiasts Group (Bay Area SEG) in 2004. The Bay Area SEG was not the first to play polo on a Segway HT; a team sponsored by Mobile Entertainment played in the Hubert H?
Segway polo    Hiking    Eton College    Sport climbing

What is a sport native to the Malay-Thai Peninsula?
Sepak takraw    swimming     Twenty20	    Sporting clays

What is a sport native to the Malay-Thai Peninsula?
Sepak Takraw    Bobrun cycling    Buzkashi    Formula Libre

What is a team game played with sticks and a ball.  is now played mainly in the Scottish Highlands, and amongst Highland migrants to the big cities of Scotland, but it was formerly more widespread, being once competitively played on a widespread basis in England and other areas in the world where Scottish Highlanders migrated?
Shinty     Jumping    Speed skiing    Table football

What is a two-player strategy board game in the same family as  Western chess, chaturanga, makruk, shatranj and xiangqi, and is the most popular of a family of chess variants native to Japan?
Shogi    Wireball	    wushu     Synchronized skating

What is both a combat sport and a stand-up fighting promotion company based in Tokyo, Japan?
Shoot boxing    Eton wall game    Chilean rodeo    Hamster racing

What is a combat sport and martial art, with competitions governed by the International  Association (ISFA)?
Shootfighting    Hybrid codes    Powerlifting    Street football

What is a competitive sport involving tests of proficiency (accuracy and speed) using various types of guns such as firearms and airguns (see archery for more information on shooting sports that make use of bows and arrows)?
Shooting sports    Aba Guresi    Russian pyramid    Pencak Silat

What is a racetrack of less than one mile (1.6 km) in length?
Short track motor racing    Stroke play    Ski flying    Straight pool 

What is a form of competitive ice speed skating. In competitions, multiple skaters (typically between four and six) skate on an oval ice track with a circumference of 111.12 m?
Short track speed skating    Hiking    Freestyle Football    Vault 

What is a track and field event involving "throwing"/"putting" (throwing in a pushing motion) a heavy spherical object —the shot—as far as possible?
Shot put    Boule lyonnaise    Shoot boxing    Checkers

What is a golf tournament format in which all groups of players tee off simultaneously from different holes?
Shotgun start    Danish longball    Ribbon     Samoa Rules

What is a member of a family of English riding equestrian events that also includes dressage, eventing, hunters, and equitation?
Show Jumping    Karate    Mountainboarding    Freeride mountain biking

What is the general Mandarin Chinese term for wrestling. As a generic name, it may be used to cover various styles of wrestling practised in China in the form of a martial arts system or a sport?
Shuai Jiao    Cluster ballooning    Curby    Bujinkan

What is a distinct Filipino Martial Art that involves hand and foot fightin?
Sikaran    Ice skating    Inline hockey    Field archery

What is a weapon-based Dravidian martial art from Tamil Nadu in south India but also practised by the Tamil community of Sri Lanka and Malaysia?
Silambam    Windsurfing    Benchrest shooting    Indoor archery

What is a collective word for indigenous martial arts from a geo-cultural area of Southeast Asia encompassing most of the Nusantara, as well as the Malay Peninsula and Malay Archipelago?
Silat    Running    Snorkelling    Sport diving 

What is a rowing boat used in the sport of competitive rowing. It is designed for a single person who propels the boat with two oars, one in each hand?
Single scull    Bodyboarding    Podex    Sand drags

What is the Philippines' traditional native sport which predates Spanish rule. The game is related to Sepak Takraw?
Sipa    Ringette    Pato    Juggling club

What is an action sport which involves riding and performing tricks using a skateboard.  can also be considered a recreational activity, an art form, a job, or a method of transportation?
Skateboarding    Train racing    swimming     Dressage

What is team sport played with a plastic ball. The game is played using inline roller skates or quad skates?
Skater hockey    Rope climbing    Backgammon    Lapta 

What is a common arcade game and one of the first redemption games?
Skee ball    Regularity rally    Universal football    Ball hockey

What is a recreational and competitive activity where participants, using shotguns, attempt to break clay disks automatically flung into the air from two fixed stations at high speed from a variety of angles?
Skeet shooting    Kuk Ball    Squirt Boating    Korfball

What is the body part that forms the supporting structure of an organism?
Skeleton     Keep Away    16 Inch    Beach volleyball

What is a sport in which skiers go down a take-off ramp, jump and attempt to land as far as possible down the hill below?
Ski flying    Slow Pitch    Pond hockey    Radio control

What is a sport in which skiers go down a take-off ramp, jump and attempt to land as far as possible down the hill below?
Ski jumping    Sepak Takraw    Water Polo    Tent pegging

What is an activity where long distances are covered on skis. Typically touring is done on trails which are not maintained, and without any mechanical lifts to get up hills?
Ski touring    Reversi     Buzkashi    Powered hang glider

What is a winter sport which combines elements of skating, snowboarding, and skiing. Skiboards are used and worn in conjunction with standard ski boots that connect to the skiboards with use of a binding?
Skiboarding    Shooting sports    Land windsurfing    Tchoukball

What is a winter sport  The actual picture used is not at all a skibob. It is a Lenz Sport Ski Bike in which the user does not use foot skis?
Skibob    Track racing    Geo caching    Unicycle hockey

What is a winter sport  The actual picture used is not at all a skibob. It is a Lenz Sport Ski Bike in which the user does not use foot skis?
Skibobbing    Personal water craft    Lelo burti    Patball

What is a winter sport where a person on skis is pulled by a horse, a dog (or dogs) or a motor vehicle?
Skijoring    Rink hockey    Beach basketball    Sprint car racing

What is a boardsport in which a skimboard (a smaller counterpart to a surfboard without fins) is used to glide across the water's surface?
Skimboarding    Sports where a player use a racquet     Lethwei    Australian handball

What is a type of scoring for various sports, most notably golf but also for disc golf, curling and bowling?
Skins game    Orienteering    Ski touring    Kneeboarding

What is a type of skydiving in which the skydiver wears a board attached to his or her feet and performs surfing-style aerobatics during freefall?
Skysurfing    Underwater hockey    Dirt track racing    Slow Pitch

What is a practice in balance that typically uses nylon or polyester webbing tensioned between two anchor points?
Slacklining    Russian pyramid    Freestyle Motocross    Yak polo

What is a form of basketball played with 4 trampolines in front of each net. It is played "full contact" and has boards around the court?
Slamball    Ball badminton    Underwater hockey    Practical shooting

What is a type of winter sporting event where the goal is to perform the most difficult tricks while getting the highest amplitude off of jumps, with an emphasis on performing different types of tricks instead of doing one great trick repeatedly?
Slopestyle    Mud bogging    Draughts    Samoa Rules

What is a variant of baseball played with a larger ball on a smaller field. It was invented in 1888 in Chicago as an indoor game, it was at various times called indoor baseball, mush ball, playground, softbund ball, kitten ball, and, because it was also played by women, ladies' baseball?
Slow Pitch    Pigeon sport    Video game    Mini footy

What is one of the two olympic weightlifting events (the other being the clean and jerk?
Snatch     Power hockey    Sikaran    Pall mall 

What is a cue sport based on snooker. The variant was created by Joe Davis, who added an orange ball (8 points) and a purple ball (10 points) to the set?
Snooker plus    Tennis Polo    Speedcubing    Tractor pulling

What is an outdoor winter sport where people use kite power to glide on snow or ice?
Snow kiting    Parachuting    Butterfly stroke    Cowboy polo

What is a winter sport that involves descending a slope that is covered with snow while standing on a board attached to a rider's feet, using a special boot set onto a mounted binding?
Snowboarding    Hockey    Intercrosse    Ringette

What is an outdoor winter sport where people use kite power to glide on snow or ice?
Snowkiting    Go     Spongee    Equitation

What is footwear for walking over the snow. Snowshoes work by distributing the weight of the person over a larger area so that the person's foot does not sink completely into the snow, a quality called "flotation"?
Snowshoeing    Biathlon    Cowboy     Aikido

What is the brand name for shoes made for grinding. They were introduced by Chris Morris of Artemis Innovations Inc?
Soap shoes    Valencian pilota    Medley swimming    Novuss

What is a department store chain that operates an extensive network of branches in Japan?
Sogo     Water Polo    Biathlon    Streetluge

What is an ancient method of fishing that has been used throughout the world for millennia. Early civilizations were familiar with the custom of spearing fish from rivers and streams using sharpened sticks?
Spearfishing    Biathlon    Connect Four    Mountain unicycling

What is a sport which involves playing a round of golf in the lowest possible sum of strokes and time?
Speed golf    Kuk Sool Won    Volata    Aerobatics

What is a solitary pool game.  As its name suggests, one  all the pool balls on the table as quickly as possible?
Speed pool    Toe wrestling    Beach handball    Orienteering

What is a competitive form of ice skating in which the competitors race each other in traveling a certain distance on skates?
Speed skating    Wheelchair basketball    Artistic roller skating    Indoor archery

What is the sport of skiing downhill in a straight line as quickly as possible. It is one of the fastest non-motorized sports on land?
Speed skiing    Table football    Indoor American football    Group Gymnastics

What is the activity of solving a Rubik's Cube or related puzzle as quickly as possible?
Speedcubing    Australian football    Duckpin bowling    Camel racing

What is a cult sport played almost exclusively in Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada by thousands of players in dozens of leagues?
Spongee    Episkyros    Majorettes    Mini rugby

What is the ability to perform continuously complex and high-intensity movement patterns to music—which originates from traditional aerobics—with a high degree of perfectly executed elements of difficulty?
Sport aerobics    Netball    Chessboxing    Fullbore target rifle

What is a form of rock climbing that relies on permanent anchors fixed to the rock, and possibly bolts, for protection?
Sport climbing    Sanshou    Triple jump    Rugby league

What is a type of diving that uses SCUBA equipment for the purpose of leisure and enjoyment?
Sport diving     Bando     Chicago     Skimboarding

What is an individual and team sport that involves stacking specialized plastic cups in specific sequences in as little time as possible?
Sport stacking    Banzai skydiving    Heptathlon    Skater hockey

What is a form of clay pigeon shooting, often described as "golf with a shotgun" because a typical course includes from 10 to 15 different shooting stations laid out over natural terrain?
Sporting clays    Subak    Diplomacy     Skibobbing

What is a competitive partner sport combining the strength, flexibility and technical precision of gymnastics with the grace and musicality of dance as well as the trust and camaraderie of a dedicated partnership?
Sports acrobatics    Radio control    Baguazhang    Ball hockey

What is a form of circuit auto racing with automobiles that have two seats and enclosed wheels?
Sports car racing    Snowkiting    Mahjong     Truck racing

What is the top racing series of the National Association for Stock Car Auto Racing (NASCAR)?
Sprint     Angling    Australian football    Underwater orienteering

What are high-powered race cars designed primarily for the purpose of running on short oval or circular dirt or paved tracks?
Sprint car racing    Hurdles    Demolition derby    Ice skating

What is a varsity sport played by United States colleges and universities, under rules similar to American football?
Sprint football    Juggling club    Freeboard     Trampolining

What is an American variant of squash racquets, but played with a ball and racquets that are closer to the equipment used for lawn tennis, and with somewhat different rules?
Squash tennis    Shidokan    Speed pool    Drifting 

What is a form of whitewater kayaking or canoeing where the boat is designed to be as low in volume as possible while still allowing the paddler to float?
Squirt Boating    Pencak Silat    Drag racing    Road racing

What is a folk wrestling style and  traditional national sport of Korea?
Ssireum    Jeet Kune Do    Wheelchair racing    Table football

What is a type of circus art performed on the trapeze.  In contrast to the other forms of trapeze, on static trapeze the bars and ropes mainly stay in place?
Static trapeze    High Power Rifle    Individual Medley    Fistball

What is a form of horse racing (primarily conducted in Ireland, the United Kingdom, Canada, United States, Australia and France) and derives its name from early races in which orientation of the course was by reference to a church steeple, jumping fences and ditches and generally traversing the many intervening obstacles in the countryside?
Steeplechase     Snooker    Triple jump    Bobrun cycling

What is a form of automobile racing found mainly in the United States, Canada, New Zealand, Great Britain, Mexico, Brazil and Argentina?
Stock car racing    Equitation    Ultramarathon    Hill Climb

What is a pocket billiards game, and was the common sport of championship competition until overtaken by faster-playing games like nine-ball (and to a lesser extent eight-ball)?
Straight pool     Sky Race    Artistic billiards    Bowling

What is a strategy board game for two players on a 10×10 square board. Each player controls 40 pieces representing individual officers and soldiers in an army?
Stratego    Street football    Bowlliards    Systema

What is a variation of the sport of ice hockey where the game is played on foot or with inline skates or roller skates with a ball or specially designed puck which is similar to an ice hockey puck but is designed to be played on non-ice surfaces?
Street hockey    Powerlifting    Bobrun cycling    Indoor field hockey

What is a form of unsanctioned and illegal motor racing which takes place on public roads.  can either be spontaneous or well-planned and coordinated?
Street racing    Land windsurfing    Australian handball    Sanshou

What is a variation of the sport of basketball, typically played on outdoor courts and featuring significantly less by way of formal structure and enforcement of the game's rules?
Streetball    Rowing     Chilean rodeo    Eton Fives

What is a board that was invented in 1989 by James Fisher and Oliver Macleod Smith?
Streetboarding    Drag boat racing    Noodling    Bar billiards

What is an extreme gravity-powered activity that involves riding a streetluge board (sometimes referred to as a sled) down a paved road or course?
Streetluge    Ball badminton    Air racing    Speed skiing

What is a scoring system in the sport of golf. It involves counting the total number of strokes taken on each hole during a given round, or series of rounds?
Stroke play    Bowls    Rock fishing    Horse polo

What is either a specific or generic ancient Korean martial art. Historically this term may have specified the old Korean martial art of taekkyeon, but it is unsure?
Subak    Sport climbing    Water polo    Footbag net

What is a group of table top games simulating team sports such as association football, cricket, both codes of rugby and hockey?
Subbuteo    Scuba Diving    Volleyball    Sipa

What is a logic-based, combinatorial number-placement puzzle. The objective is to fill a 9×9 grid with digits so that each column, each row, and each of the nine 3×3 sub-grids that compose the grid (also called "boxes", "blocks", "regions", or "sub-squares") contains all of the digits from 1 to 9. The puzzle setter provides a partially completed grid, which typically has a unique solution?
Sudoku    Boxing    Skiboarding    Cutthroat 

What is the act of intentionally causing one's own death?
Suicide     Land Kiteboarding    Supercross    Longboarding

What is the signature performance option package offered by Chevrolet, a United States Auto Maker, on a limited number of its vehicles?
Super sport     Sea kayaking    Sipa    Formula racing

What is a category of motorcycle racing that employs modified production motorcycles. Superbike World Championship is the international superbike championship, and national superbike championships are held in many countries as well, including the United Kingdom, the United States, Japan, and Canada?
Superbike racing    swimming     English Pleasure    Taekwondo

What is a motorcycle racing sport involving off-road motorcycles on an artificially-made dirt tracks consisting of steep jumps and obstacles?
Supercross    Heptathlon    Nordic skiing    Sipa

What is motorcycle racing on a circuit that alternates between three types of track: flat track, motocross and road racing, using motorcycles designed for that purpose?
Supermoto    Boccia    Luge    Judo

What is the sport of catching fish standing on the shoreline or wading in the surf.  A general term, surf fishing may or may not include casting a lure or bait, and refers to all types of shore fishing - from sandy and rocky beaches, rock jetties, or even fishing piers?
Surf fishing    Ball     Power hockey    Artistic pool

What is the sport, technique, and equipment, used in surfing ocean waves with kayaks. Surf kayaking has many similarities to surf board surfing, but with boats designed for use in surf zones, and with a paddle?
Surf Kayaking    Ski jumping    Power hockey    Taekkyeon

What is an oar-driven boat designed to enter the ocean from the beach in heavy surf or severe waves?
Surfboat    Static trapeze    Tractor pulling    Cammag

What is a surface water sport in which the wave rider, referred to as a "surfer", rides on the forward face of a wave, which is most often carrying the surfer towards shore?
Surfing    Rock racing    Hapkido    Fast Pitch

What is a form of association football that is played in bogs or swamps?
Swamp football    Kurash    Cluster ballooning    Freeboard 

What is a water based sport governed by the Fédération Internationale de Natation (FINA?
swimming     Unicycle basketball    Fricket     Endurance racing 

What is a physical activity that involves standing on a short board (typically a skateboard) which is suspended from a frame which allows the board to swing freely?
Swing boarding    Kendo    Endurance racing     Horseshoes 

What is modern, and as such was mainly used to refer to smallsword fencing, but by extension it can also be applied to any martial art involving the use of a sword?
Swordfighting    Mancala    Hurdles    Harpastum

What is a hybrid form of swimming, dance and gymnastics, consisting of swimmers (either solos, duets, trios, combos, or teams) performing a synchronized routine of elaborate moves in the water, accompanied by music?
Synchronized swimming    Field Hockey    Baseball pocket billiards    16 Inch

What is a Russian martial art.  Training includes but not limited to: hand to hand combat, grappling, knife fighting and fire arms training as well?
Systema    Bobsleigh    Indoor soccer    Czech handball

What is a table-top game and sport that is loosely based on association football?
Table football    Kickball    Shuai Jiao    Harrow Football

What is a traditional Korean military martial art with a dance-like appearance in some aspects.  is also frequently romanized informally as Taekkyon or Taekyun?
Taekkyeon    Casting     Chinese Checkers    Tennikoit

What is a martial art originating in Korea. It combines combat and self-defense techniques with sport and exercise?
Taekwondo    One Day International	    Team penning    Hiking

What is an Austronesian language spoken as a first language by a quarter of the population of the Philippines and as a second language by most of the rest?
Tag     Ice sledge hockey    Glima    Snowboarding

What is a non-contact team game in which each player wears a belt that has two velcro tags attached to it, or shorts with velcro patches?
Tag Rugby    Torball    Bicycle polo    Hybrid codes

What is a county in eastern Taiwan. While its name means "Eastern Taiwan", it is also known as "Houshan" () by many of the locals, meaning behind the mountains or the back mountains?
Taido    Streetboarding    Oztag    Grand Prix motorcycle racing

What is a Korean martial art "incorporating fighting principles from Soo Bahk Do (as described in the Kwon Bup Chong Do) and techniques from northern and southern Chinese kung fu."?
Tang Soo Do    Powerbocking    Dinghy sailing    Curling

What is governed by the World Archery Federation, abbreviated WA (formerly FITA - Fédération Internationale de Tir à l'Arc)?
Target archery    Kinomichi    Enduro    Flight archery

What is a competitive sport involving tests of proficiency (accuracy and speed) using various types of guns such as firearms and airguns (see archery for more information on shooting sports that make use of bows and arrows)?
Target shooting    Sandboarding    Heptathlon    Fistball

What is an outdoor team sport developed in the dark ages by the Nords.  Swiss biologist Hermann Brandt, who believed that "The objective of all physical activities is not to make champions, but make a contribution to building a harmonious society"?
Tchoukball    Eton wall game    High jump    Shuai Jiao

What is a team sport in which two teams of seven players each (six outfield players and a goalkeeper on each team) pass a ball to throw it into the goal of the other team?
team handball    BoÃŸeln    Episkyros    Xingyiquan

What is a team sport in which two teams of seven players each (six outfield players and a goalkeeper on each team) pass a ball to throw it into the goal of the other team?
Team handball    Checkers    Robot combat    Inline hockey

What is a western equestrian sport that evolved from the common ranch work of separating cattle into pens for branding, doctoring, or transport?
Team penning    Ice racing    Flying disc freestyle    Basque pelota

What is "work done by several associates with each doing a part but all subordinating personal prominence to the efficiency of the whole" ?
Team play    Lethwei    Unicycle hockey    Mahjong 

What is a sport based on baseball and is intended as an introduction for children to develop baseball skills and have fun?
Tee Ball    Xingyiquan    Breaststroke    Dragon boat

What is a form of downhill skiing using bindings where the boot is attached only at the toe (similar to those of Cross-country skiing), allowing the heel to come up from the ski?
Telemark skiing    Quidditch    Heptathlon    Wing Chun

What is an outdoor game which was started in the early 1960s. It was played by high school girls in the USA since the 1930s?
Tennikoit    Offshore powerboat racing    Episkyros    Superbike racing

What is a cavalry sport of ancient origin, and is one of only ten equestrian disciplines officially recognised by the International Equestrian Federation?
Tent pegging    Checkers    Slow Pitch    Power Tumbling

What is the longest form of the sport of cricket. Test matches are played between national representative teams with "Test status", as determined by the International Cricket Council (ICC)?
Test cricket		 	    Medieval football    International rules football    Snowshoeing

What is a North American game for two opposing players. The equipment consists of a stationary metal pole, from which is hung a volleyball from a rope, or tether?
Tetherball    Paintball    Flutterguts    Knattleikr

What is a variation of association football with three teams instead of the usual two?
Three sided football    Race of Champions    Footvolley    Basketball

What is a non-contact ball sport played across a net between two teams of seven players on a rectangular court?
Throwball    Speed pool    Sepak Takraw    Ice Racing

What is a children's game played by two players in a tournament called a thumb-a-war (or thumb war) using the thumbs to simulate fighting?
Thumb wrestling    Wicketball    Hunter    Eton Fives

What is another term for time trial. The term is commonly used in Japan for individual time trial events for motor vehicles that involves a vehicle running around the circuit in lieu of a  lap and the term is widely adopted outside the country for tuner event and media?
Time Attack    Eskrima    Bobsleigh    Fastnet 

What is a simple sled which is a traditional form of transport used by the Innu and Cree of northern Canada?
Toboggan    Rogaining    Klootschieten    Bull fighting

What is a sport gaining popularity in the UK.  World championships started in Wetton in the 1970s and are now held at the Bentley Brook Inn in Ashbourne, Derbyshire?
Toe wrestling    Australian football    Banger racing     Jumping

What is a sport for the blind and visually impaired. It is played by two teams on opposite sides of an indoor playing field?
Torball    Footvolley    Royaking    Bodybuilding

What is the form of juggling which is most recognisable as 'juggling'.  can be used as: a performing art, a sport, a form of exercise, as meditation, a recreational pursuit or hobby?
Toss juggling    Thumb wrestling    Drifting     Ice Racing

What is a general term for a number of distinct auto racing competitions in heavily-modified street cars?
Touring car racing    Fistball    Twenty20	    Practical shooting

What is a sport, which involves running up tall man-made structures. Usually the races take place on the internal staircases of skyscrapers, but the term can cover any foot race which involves a course that ascends a man-made structure?
Tower running    Archery    Friskee    Sports car racing

What is a bicycle racing sport usually held on specially built banked tracks or velodromes (but many events are held at older velodromes where the track banking is relatively shallow) using track bicycles?
Track cycling    Carom billiards    Supercross    Red rover

What is a form of motorcycle racing where teams or individuals race opponents around an oval track?
Track racing    Model aircraft    Pehlwani    Swedish football 

What is a motorsport competition, popular in America, Europe (especially in the Netherlands), Australia and Brazil, which requires modified tractors to pull a heavy sledge (sled) along a 35 ft wide and length of 100 meter or 300 ft+ track, with the winner being the tractor that pulls the sledge farthest?
Tractor pulling    Mountainboarding    Noodling    Shoot boxing

What is a competitive Olympic sport in which gymnasts perform acrobatics while bouncing on a trampoline?
Trampolining    Deer hunting    Kite buggy    Fastnet 

What is one of the three major disciplines of competitive clay pigeon shooting  (shotgun shooting at clay targets)?
Trap shooting    Kneeboarding    Kite landboarding    Gymkhana

What is a short horizontal bar hung by ropes or metal straps from a support. It is an aerial apparatus commonly found in circus performances?
Trapeze    Snowshoeing    Episkyros    Pehlwani

What is a coming together of parties to a , to present information (in the form of evidence) in a tribunal, a formal setting with the authority to adjudicate claims or disputes?
Trial    Half marathon    Shurikenjutsu    Backstroke

What is a multiple-stage competition involving the completion of three continuous and sequential endurance disciplines?
Triathlon    Red rover    Footvolley    Sepak takraw

What is a method for describing the tinctures (colours) used in a coat of arms by means of text abbreviations or symbols?
Tricking    Luge    Capture the flag    Majorettes

What is a track and field sport, similar to the long jump, but involving a "hop, bound and jump": the competitor runs down the track and performs a hop, a bound and then a jump into the sand pit?
Triple jump    Hybrid codes    Wiffleball    Clay pigeon shooting

What is the selective hunting of wild game animals. Although parts of the slain animal may be kept as a hunting trophy or memorial (usually the skin, antlers and/or head), the carcass itself is sometimes used as food?
Trophy hunting    Race Walking    Race Walking    Calisthenics

What is a form of motor racing which involves modified versions of heavy tractor units on racing circuits?
Truck racing    Fourball    Team penning    Debating

What is a sport or game said to have been invented in the Newport Railway Workshops in the Western suburbs of Melbourne, by railway workers in the 1920s?
Trugo    Freestyle snowboarding    Ski flying    Basque Pelota

What is a form of cricket originally introduced in England and Wales for professional inter-county competition by the England and Wales Cricket Board (ECB), in 2003. A Twenty20 game involves two teams, each has a single innings, batting for a maximum of 20 overs?
Twenty20	    Duckpin bowling    Freeboating    Robot combat

What is the largest mixed martial arts  promotion company in the world, which hosts most of the top-ranked fighters in the sport and produces events worldwide?
Ultimate     Personal water craft    Football tennis    High Power Rifle

What is the flying of lightweight, 1 or 2 seat fixed-wing aircraft, ?
Ultralight aviation    Kite flying    Land sailing    Rallying

What is a two-team sport that shares common elements with underwater hockey and underwater rugby?
Underwater football    Silambam    La soule    Mancala

What is a global non-contact sport in which two teams compete to maneuver a puck across the bottom of a swimming pool into goals?
Underwater hockey    Ulama    American handball    Inline hockey

What is a minor extreme sport that is a variant of ice hockey?
Underwater ice hockey    Freeboard     Calisthenics    Paragliding

What is an underwater sport that has its origin in the physical fitness training of German diving clubs and has little in common with rugby football except for the name?
Underwater rugby    Mob football    Northern Praying Mantis    Streetboarding

What is an artistic gymnastics apparatus. It is  used only by female gymnasts?
Uneven Bars    Calcio Fiorentino    Isle of Man TT    Land speed records

What is a team sport, the objective being to shoot a ball through a horizontally positioned basket to score points, while following a set of rules?
Unicycle basketball    Lethwei    Bodybuilding    Hybrid codes

What is a team sport, similar to roller or inline hockey, except that each player must be mounted on a unicycle (with both feet on the pedals) to play the ball?
Unicycle hockey    Hare coursing    Wheelchair basketball    Ball badminton

What is a form of unicycling which involves participants attempting to ride a unicycle over obstacles without any part of the rider touching the ground?
Unicycle trials    Curling    Trailer racing    Super sport 

What is a human-powered, single-track vehicle with one wheel. Unicycles resemble bicycles, but are less complex?
Unicycling    Bull riding    Ulama    Kajukenbo

What is home to a tradition known as "", a version of Medieval football and with roots in even earlier games?
Uppies and Downies    Mixed martial arts    Naginatajutsu    Hana Ichi Monme

What is a traditional handball sport played in the Valencian Community?
Valencian pilota    Rossall Hockey    Horseshoes     Shinty

What is an old outdoor game. The game dates back to the Viking Age and survived in Gotland together with several other medieval or Viking games?
Varpa    Quidditch    Twenty20	    Chinese handball

What is an architectural term for  an arched form  used to provide a space with a ceiling or roof?
Vault     Bar billiards    Bull riding    Ringo 

What is an electronic game that involves human interaction with a user interface to generate visual feedback on a video device?
Video game    Road bicycle racing    Kelly pool    Buzkashi

What is a ball game that was developed in fascist Italy as a substitute for  association football and rugby union?
Volata    Buzkashi    Land speed records    Metallic silhouette

What is a team sport in which two teams of six players are separated by a net. Each team tries to score points by grounding a ball on the other team's court under organized rules?
Volleyball    Chicago     Gridiron football    Masters Rugby League

What is a Vietnamese martial ar?
Vovinam    Judo    Sambo     Boccia

What is a surface water sport which involves riding a  over the surface of a body of water. It was developed from a combination of water skiing, snowboarding and surfing techniques?
Wakeboarding    Palla    Combat robot    Czech handball

What is a water sport in which a surfer trails behind a wakeboard boat, surfing the boat's wake without being directly attached to the boat?
Wakesurfing    Boxing    Akroteri Punching    Water basketball

What is "wallball"?
Wallball    Supermoto    One Day International	    Paragliding

What is a fast-paced sport that was created by Bill Dejonghe at the Calabasas Racquetball Club (Calabasas, California), in 1979 ?
Wallyball    Debating    Javelin throw    Arm Wrestling

What is a water sport which mixes the rules of basketball and water polo, played in a swimming pool?
Water basketball    Slamball    Tag Rugby    Cnapan

What is a team water sport. The playing team consists of six field players and one goalkeeper?
Water polo    Discus throw    Floorball    Street football

What is a team water sport. The playing team consists of six field players and one goalkeeper?
Water Polo    Hooverball    MCMAP    Indoor short track

What is the posting of signs – waymarks (sometimes way-mark or way mark) – along a route so that travelers can easily follow the route?
Waymarking    Rugby league sevens    Gaelic football    Orienteering

What is a  western style competition at horse shows that evaluates horses on manners and suitability of the horse for a relaxed but collected gait cadence and relatively slow speed of gait, along with calm and responsive disposition?
Western Pleasure    Horseball    Hapkido    Blackball 

What is basketball played by people in wheelchairs and is considered one of the major disabled sports practiced?
Wheelchair basketball    Inline hockey    Haidong Gumdo    Creeking

What is the racing of wheelchairs in track and road races.  is open to athletes with any qualifying type of disability, amputees, spinal cord injuries, cerebral palsy and partially sighted (when combined with another disability)?
Wheelchair racing    Subbuteo    Desert racing    Rotation 

What is a wheelchair-based version of rugby league football. It was developed by French rugby league player, coach and official, Robert Fassolette and Wally Salvan in 2004. Unlike other wheelchair sports, people without disabilities is allowed to compete in top level competition?
Wheelchair rugby league    Pitch and putt    Australian football    Shooting sports

What is a form of motorsport where specially prepared vehicles compete in order to have the highest, longest, most photogenic and violent wheelstand, normally in dragstrips or Monster Trucks?
Wheelstand competition    Wallball    Uppies and Downies    Bobsleigh

What is the sport of paddling a kayak on a moving body of water, typically a whitewater river?
Whitewater kayaking    Rugby league sevens    Squirt Boating    Tee Ball

What is a variation of the sport of baseball designed for indoor or outdoor play in confined areas?
Wiffleball    Midget car racing    Moscow broomball    Telemark skiing

What is a surface water sport that combines elements of surfing and sailing. It consists of a board usually 2 to 3 metres long, with a volume of about 60 to 250 liters, powered by wind on a sail?
Windsurfing    Air racing    Gridiron football    Powered paragliding

What is a branch of Wing Chun, led by Leung Tin?
Wing Tsun    Rugby league nines    Backpacking     Chessboxing

What is the sport of flying the human body through the air using a special jumpsuit, called a wingsuit, which adds surface area to the human body to enable a significant increase in lift?
Wingsuit flying    Road bicycle racing    Tennis Polo    Stroke play

What is a street game related to baseball, usually formed as a pick-up game, in  urban areas of the United States?
Wireball	    Power hockey    Savate    Prisoner Ball

What is a traditional Indigenous Australian "co-operative kicking volley game" similar to the games of keepie uppie and footbag?
Woggabaliri    Swamp football    Horseshoe    Cue sports

What is the practice of hunting gray wolves (Canis lupus) or other lupine animals. Wolves are mainly hunted for sport, for their skins, to protect livestock, and, in some rare cases, to protect humans?
Wolf hunting    Hiking    Hapkido    Deadlifting

What is a sport that has been around for hundreds of years in several cultures. In wood chopping competitions, skilled contestants attempt to be the first to cut or saw through a log or other block of wood?
Wood chopping    Friskee    Candlepin bowling    Squat 

What is a form of combat sport involving grappling type techniques such as clinch fighting, throws and takedowns,  joint locks, pins and other grappling holds?
Wrestling    ITHF table hockey    Equitation    Geo caching

What is an strategy board game for two players?
Xiangqi    Mixed martial arts    Canadian football    Snowkiting

What is one of the major "internal" styles of Chinese martial arts. The word translates approximately to "Form/Intention Boxing", or "Shape/Will Boxing", and is characterized by aggressive, seemingly linear movements and explosive power?
Xingyiquan    Rugby Fives    Harpastum    Aerobatics

What is a Mongolian variant of the sport polo. It is played on yaks instead of on horseback?
Yak polo    Kajukenbo    Basque pelota    Indoor field hockey

What is a commonly known generic term for physical, mental, and spiritual disciplines which originated in ancient India?
Yoga    Bunnock    Bunnock    Catch wrestling

What is a seven-a-side traditional football game played in Manipur, India, using a coconut, which has some notable similarities to rugby?
Yubi lakpi    Lelo burti    Unicycle basketball    Canoe Polo

What is a traditional Martial art and a style of Wrestling that originated in Iran?
Zourkhaneh    Kalarippayattu    Sudoku    Hurdles

What is literally Drunken Fist, also known as Drunken Boxing or Drunkard's Boxing) is a concept in traditional Chinese martial arts, as well as a classification of modern Wushu forms?
Zui Quan    Road crawling    Cammag    Chinese Checkers

