What is an American television sitcom created by Steven H. Berman, Mitchel Katlin, and Nat Bernstein for Nickelodeon?
100 Deeds for Eddie McDowd    Breakfast News    Aqua Teen Hunger Force    The Chimp Channel

What is an American situation comedy series which premiered on NBC on May 27, 2010. In May 2009 the network announced that the show would debut midseason in March 2010 on Tuesday nights at 9:30 pm, after NBC's coverage of the 2010 Winter Olympics was completed?
100 Questions    The Adventures of Ellery Queen    Celebrity Blackjack    Cheez TV

What is a live interactive game show on GSN, officially hosted by Jessica York. Jeff Thisted and Shandi Finnessey served as substitute hosts?
100 Winners    The Amazing Race    Baywatch    Big Arvo

What is an anthology television series that premiered on Spike on May 14, 2008, and ended on July 15, 2012. The program recreates unusual supposed deaths and debunked urban legends and includes interviews with experts who describe the science behind each death?
1000 Ways to Die    Bob Hope Presents the Chrysler Theatre    Caroline in the City    Allen Gregory

What is a British quiz show produced by Endemol for the BBC, hosted by Steve Jones and Nemone?
101 Ways to Leave a Gameshow    Aqua Teen Hunger Force    The Adventures of Ellery Queen    The Abbott and Costello Show

What is an MTV reality television series produced by Morgan J. Freeman and Dia Sokol Savage, and was first broadcast on June 11, 2009. The series gets its name from the song "18 and Life" by Skid Row?
16 and Pregnant    Barnaby Jones    The Amazing Race Asia    Celebrity Deathmatch

What is a Canadian television sitcom that debuted on January 4, 2010, on CBC Television. The series is shown in Quebec on Vrak.TV with the title Majeurs et mariés?
18 to Life    Camp Lazlo    Celebrity Rehab Presents Sober House    Beany and Cecil

What is an American television sitcom that debuted on CBS during the 2011–12 television season?
2 Broke Girls    The Banana Splits    Ace Lightning    CatDog

What is an American police procedural crime drama television series that aired on the Fox Network and in first run syndication from April 12, 1987, to April 27, 1991, with a total of 103 episodes?
21 Jump Street    All That    Basil Brush    The Bradys

What is a British satirical animated television show that was broadcast on ITV in the United Kingdom from March 2001 to December 2004. Lasting a total of five series and thirty-three episodes,  became the successor of popular 80's TV series Spitting Image, and the predecessor of 2008 ITV satirical animation Headcases?
2DTV    Acme Hour    Andy Richter Controls the Universe    Beyblade

What is a drama that aired on CBS from November 14 to 28, 2006, replacing the cancelled series Smith?
3 lbs    All About Faces    Alfred Hitchcock Presents    8 Simple Rules

What is an American television comedy series that ran on NBC from October 11, 2006 to January 31, 2013 and was created by Tina Fey?
30 Rock    The Barbara Stanwyck Show    Blue Peter    All About Me

What is the debut studio album by American singer Mike Posner. It was released on August 10, 2010, by J Records?
31 Minutes    Carl Squared    Bubble Guppies    Aliens in America

What is an American sitcom that aired from 1996 to 2001 on NBC?
3rd Rock from the Sun    Angry Beavers    American Pickers    Breaking Bonaduce

What is a reality television series hosted by Michael Irvin that premiered on Spike on May 18, 200?
4th and Long    As Told By Ginger    All That    Bob and Margaret

What is an American television news program that was created in 1968. The program was created by Don Hewitt who set it apart by using a unique style of reporter-centered investigation?
60 Minutes    The Bradys    100 Deeds for Eddie McDowd    The Bold Ones

What is a children's cartoon created by Belgian-born English author An Vrombau?
64 Zoo Lane    Charlie Chalk    The Charmings    Back at the Barnyard

What is an American supernatural drama series, which premiered on ABC on September 30, 2012. The series was created and produced by David Wilcox, and was loosely based upon the novel of the same name by Gabriella Pierce?
666 Park Avenue    The Big Bang Theory    Breaking Bad    As Told By Ginger

What is a Canadian animated sitcom, which premiered in Canada in 2004 on Teletoon. In the USA,  first premiered on Nickelodeon on December 18, 2005 and was removed from the schedule on May 13, 2006 before being removed completely in 2007 before the series' run could be completed?
6teen    Captain Scarlet and the Mysterons    Captain Scarlet and the Mysterons    Alice

What is an American sitcom that aired on CBS from April to May 1994. A spin-off of All in the Family (the final of several), the series is built around the concept of a black family, the Cumberbatches, moving into the former Queens home of Archie Bunker years after Bunker had sold the house?
704 Hauser    Aqua Teen Hunger Force    Bumper Stumpers    Back to You

What is an hour-length American television private detective series created by Roy Huggins and starring Efrem Zimbalist, Jr., Roger Smith, and Edd Byrnes?
77 Sunset Strip    The Abbott and Costello Show    Celebrity Charades    Adventures of Sonic The Hedgehog

What is an American family drama television series, created and produced by Brenda Hampton. The series premiered on August 26, 1996, on The WB, the first time that the network aired Monday night programming, and was originally broadcast from August 26, 1996 to May 13, 2007. The series finale was scheduled for May 8, 2006; however, the show was renewed by the CW when the intended final episode received high ratings?
7th Heaven    100 Questions    Babes    Bourbon Street Beat

What is an American sitcom television series, originally starring John Ritter and Katey Sagal?
8 Simple Rules    Active Kids    Batman Beyond    Atomic Betty

What is a live-action, single-camera adventure series created by Bruce Kalish. Originally broadcast with the launch of Disney XD on February 13, 2009. It was the first original series to air on the network?
Aaron Stone    Bunheads    Captain Power    American Pickers

Whatvision from 1960. Its original presenter was Dick Joice?
About Anglia    Braceface    Batfink    Black Books

What is a British sitcom created by Jennifer Saunders, based on an original idea by her and Dawn French, and written by Saunders, who plays the leading character?
Absolutely Fabulous    The Adventures of the Scarlet Pimpernel    Brooke Knows Best    The Benny Hill Show

What is a weekday television entertainment news program covering events and celebrities in the entertainment industry?
Access Hollywood    All That    American Dream Derby    Barney Miller

What is an American sitcom television series starring Jim Belushi in the title role as a suburban father of three children (five children starting with the season-seven finale)?
According to Jim    18 to Life    Baretta    Angry Beavers

What is a children's television show co-produced by the BBC and Alliance Atlantis, which has been broadcast in the United States as well as in the United Kingdom and Australia?
Ace Lightning    Active Kids    Animal Jam    Bridget Loves Bernie

What is an American reality television show which aired on the Food Network.  The show focused on the daily operations of Duff Goldman's custom cake shop, Charm City Cakes, in Baltimore, Maryland; including small-business ownership, working with various vendors, tasting with customers, constructing cakes, and delivering his products?
Ace of Cakes    The 4400    Alphablocks    The Adventures of Tintin

What was an hour-long program that aired on Cartoon Network. It was an hour-long compilation of various Warner Bros., MGM, Jay Ward, Walter Lantz, Popeye, Felix the Cat, and public domain Betty Boop cartoon shorts?
Acme Hour    101 Ways to Leave a Gameshow    Beat the Clock    The Catherine Tate Show

What is a short series of exercise television programs to encourage children to be more physically active, which was broadcast on the ABC at 4.30 pm weekdays in Australia, it was presented by Scott Ehler and Amy Wilkins?
Active Kids    The Alan Young Show    Beyblade    BodyShock

What is a British television series which ran from 1966 to 1967 on the BBC. Proposing that an adventurer born in 1867 had been revived from hibernation in 1966, the show was a comedy adventure that took a satirical look at life in the 1960s through the eyes of an Edwardian (Adamant vanished in 1902 when Edward VII had been on the throne just one year)?
Adam Adamant Lives    Better Off Ted    Arthur Godfrey and His Friends    The Assistants

What is an American animated television series created by Pendleton Ward for Cartoon Network?
Adventure Time    The Brady Bunch Hour    The Amazing Race    Burn Notice

What is a live-action musical television series based on Walt Disney's animated classic Alice in Wonderland?
Adventures in Wonderland    California Dreams    Adventures in Wonderland    Austin City Limits

What is an American animated series that was first broadcast in September 1993. It follows the adventures of the video game character Sonic the Hedgehog, and his sidekick Tails, as they attempt to stop the evil Doctor Robotnik and his array of robots from taking over the planet Mobius?
Adventures of Sonic The Hedgehog    8 Simple Rules    Banacek    All Grown Up

What is a Japanese seinen dōjinshi manga series written and illustrated by manga artist Takashi Okazaki?
Afro Samurai    The Adventures of Ellery Queen    The Andy Dick Show    8 Simple Rules

What is an American situation comedy that aired on CBS from September 26, 1983, to December 11, 1984. A spin-off of the series M*A*S*H, the show takes place immediately following the end of the Korean War and chronicles the adventures of three characters from the original series: Colonel Potter (played by Harry Morgan), Klinger (played by Jamie Farr) and Father Mulcahy (played by William Christopher)?
AfterMASH    Animal Jam    77 Sunset Strip    Barnaby Jones

What is an American television series that ran from 1984 until 1987.  The program centers on a high-tech military helicopter, code named , and its crew as they undertake various missions, many involving espionage, with a Cold War theme?
Airwolf    The Bradys    Chicago Hope    Ballbreakers

Whatis a Japanese science fiction tokusatsu television series, created by Shotaro Ishinomori and produced by Toei Company?
Akumaizer 3    The Assistants    The Bachelorette    60 Minutes

What is a British comedy sketch television series featuring Mel Smith and Griff Rhys Jones?
Alas Smith and Jones    The Brady Bunch    Baby Daddy    Alice

What is an American television anthology series hosted by Alfred Hitchcock. The series featured dramas, thrillers, and mysteries?
Alfred Hitchcock Presents    Blonde Charity Mafia    Bubble Guppies    Angry Beavers

What is an animated cartoon spin-off based on the live-action Sitcom series ALF?
AlfTales    Angry Beavers    Celebrity Blackjack    The Big Valley 

What is an American Western series that originally aired on ABC from 1971 to 1973.  It stars Pete Duel as Hannibal Heyes and Ben Murphy as Jedediah "Kid" Curry, a pair of cousin outlaws trying to reform?
Alias Smith and Jones    The Brady Brides    Barnaby Jones    As Told By Ginger

What is an American rock singer, songwriter and musician whose career spans six decades?
Alice    2 Broke Girls    American Dreams    Baywatch

What is an American sitcom created by David Guarascio and Moses Port that aired on The CW for one season from 2007-2008. Guarascio and Port also served as executive producers of the show alongside Tim Doyle?
Aliens in America    Charmed    Baywatch    American Dream Derby

What is an American sci-fi/fantasy sitcom that aired on ABC, conceived as part of its TGIF lineup From the Creators of Dinosaurs and The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air?
Aliens in the Family    The Bold and the Beautiful    21 Jump Street    The Benny Hill Show

What is a game show which ran from August 30, 1971 to September 1972; The series incorporated a "hidden camera" format similar to Candid Camera and Punk'd?
All About Faces    Baywatch    The Buzz on Maggie    Ballbreakers

What is a British television sitcom starring Jasper Carrott about a multicultural family living in Birmingham?
All About Me    Celebrity Rehab Presents Sober House    Charlie Jade    Babylon 5

What is an  animated television series created by Arlene Klasky and Gábor Csupó for Nickelodeon?
All Grown Up    Byker Grove    The Andy Williams Show    Car 54

What is an American sitcom that was originally broadcast on the CBS television network from January 12, 1971, to April 8, 1979. In September 1979, a new show, Archie Bunker's Place, picked up where  had ended?
All in the Family    Alice    Brat Camp    Beat The Chef

What is an American television soap opera that aired on ABC for 41 years, from January 5, 1970 to September 23, 2011. Created by Agnes Nixon,  is set in Pine Valley, Pennsylvania, a fictitious suburb of Philadelphia?
All My Children    The Adventures of the Scarlet Pimpernel    100 Questions    Bob and Margaret

What is an American live-action, sketch comedy-variety show that aired on the Nickelodeon cable television network featuring short comedic sketches and weekly musical guests?
All That    Better Off Ted    Afro Samurai    Boston Legal

What is an American animated television series created by Jonah Hill, Andrew Mogel and Jarrad Paul?
Allen Gregory    60 Minutes    The Adventures of Wild Bill Hickok    Call Red

What is an American legal comedy-drama television series, originally aired on Fox from September 8, 1997 to May 20, 2002. Created by David E?
Ally McBeal    Animaniacs    The Andy Dick Show    Black Books

What is a children's educational television programme that attempts to teach children how to spell with the use of animated blocks representing each letter?
Alphablocks    Childrens Hospital    American Dreams    The Amazing Chan and the Chan Clan

What is an American science fiction dramatic television series created by Zak Penn and Michael Karnow?
Alphas    The Bugs Bunny Show    Allen Gregory    Basil Brush

What is a New Zealand children's program featuring the adventures of a modern day superhero teenage boy and his friends?
Amazing Extraordinary Friends    Acme Hour    The Bold and the Beautiful    The Amazing World Of Gumball

What was an American music-performance show that aired in various versions from 1952 to 1989 and was hosted from 1956 until its final season by Dick Clark, who also served as producer?
American Bandstand    Akumaizer 3    Brat Camp    Ballbreakers

What is a reality television series that airs on Discovery Channel, produced by Pilgrim Films & Television?
American Chopper    The Adventures of Rin Tin Tin    Charlie Rose    The Amazing Race Asia

What is an American horse racing-themed reality show that aired on GSN. Eight one-hour episodes were produced, with the first two airing on January 10, 2005; the show then aired weekly through the February 21 finale?
American Dream Derby    The Big Gig    Camp Candy    The Andy Dick Show

What is an American television drama program broadcast on the NBC television network, produced by Once A Frog and Dick Clark Productions in association with Universal Network Television and NBC Studios?
American Dreams    American Dreams    Chico and the Man    The Adventures of Chico and Guapo

What is an American competition television program that aired in syndication from September 1989 to May 1996. The series matched a cast of amateur athletes against each other, as well as against the show's own gladiators, in contests of strength and agility?
American Gladiators    The Banana Splits    Allen Gregory    American Dream Derby

What is a horror genre television franchise created and produced by Ryan Murphy and Brad Falchuk?
American Horror Story    The Backyardigans    Atomic Betty    Andy Richter Controls the Universe

What is an American reality television series that premiered on January 18, 2010, on History?
American Pickers    Card Sharks    The Assistants    All That

What was a sitcom which aired from 2002–2003 on the Fox network. The series was Andy Richter's first starring role after leaving NBC's Late Night with Conan O'Brien in 200?
Andy Richter Controls the Universe    Animal Jam    Adam Adamant Lives    Acme Hour

What is an American animated television series created by Mitch Schauer for the Nickelodeon channel?
Angry Beavers    The Arsenio Hall Show    The Bold Ones    Bob Hope Presents the Chrysler Theatre

What is an Australian television mockumentary series written by and starring Chris Lilley. Continuing the mockumentary style of his previous series, the show explores the issues faced by young males in the 21st century – their influences, their pressures, their dreams and ambitions?
Angry Boys    Blue Peter    Camp Lazlo    Candid Camera

What is a children's television show created by John Derevlany (who also wrote most of the episodes) and produced by Jim Henson Television which first aired on February 24, 2003 until 201?
Animal Jam    Ask This Old House    3rd Rock from the Sun    Cake Boss

What is an American animated television series, distributed by Warner Bros?
Animaniacs    BrainSurge    Captain Kangaroo    Ben 10

What is a vivarium which is designed primarily for the study of ant colonies and how ants behave?
ANT Farm    Akumaizer 3    Cake Boss    Batfink

What is an American television sitcom, which aired on ABC from March 7, 1989 to June 3, 1992, spanning four seasons and 56 episodes?
Anything but Love    Card Sharks    Adventures of Sonic The Hedgehog    All About Me

What is an American animated television series on Cartoon Network's late night programing block, Adult Swim?
Aqua Teen Hunger Force    Chicagolicious    2 Broke Girls    704 Hauser

What is an American anthology drama television series which ran from 1950 to 1957 on NBC, and then until 1963 on CBS?
Armstrong Circle Theatre    Captain Scarlet and the Mysterons    The Beachcombers    2 Broke Girls

What is a British children's television series revolving around art. The original series was one of CITV's longest running programmes, running from 1990 to 2007, and was presented throughout by Neil Buchanan?
Art Attack    Bug Juice    Aaron Stone    The Beachcombers

What is an American television variety show hosted by Arthur Godfrey. The hour-long series aired on CBS Television from January 1949 to June 1957 (as The Arthur Godfrey Show after September 1956), then again as a half-hour show from September 1958 to April 195?
Arthur Godfrey and His Friends    Adam Adamant Lives    Beetleborgs    60 Minutes

What is an American animated series aimed at preteens and teenagers that was produced by Klasky-Csupo and aired on Nickelodeon?
As Told By Ginger    Camp Runamuck    The Backyardigans    Ben Casey

What is a British television quiz show originally made by the BBC and broadcast between 1967 and 1984. In 1999, it was revived by the BBC, and in 2005 again returned with a series on BBC?
Ask The Family    American Dream Derby    The Book Quiz    The Adventures of Rin Tin Tin

Whathis Old House is an American home improvement magazine and television series aired on the American television station Public Broadcasting Service (PBS) which follows remodeling projects of houses over a number of weeks?
Ask This Old House    Baby Daddy    Beetleborgs    The Charmings

What is a cartoon ant and superhero, created by Hanna-Barbera in 1965. Atom costarred in The /Secret Squirrel Show (sharing top billing with Secret Squirrel)?
Atom Ant    All That    The Bob Cummings Show    Celebrity Deathmatch

What is a Canadian-French animated television series produced by Atomic Cartoons, Breakthrough Films & Television, and Tele Images Kids?
Atomic Betty    Aliens in America    Baby Daddy    Boston Public

Whatvision program formerly shown weeknights on G4, G4 Canada Fuel TV, HOW TO Channel, and Maxxx?
Attack Of The Show    The 700 Club    Celebrity Deathmatch    Captain Video and His Video Rangers

What is an American public television music program recorded live in Austin, Texas by Public Broadcasting Service (PBS) Public television member station KLRU, and broadcast on many PBS stations around the United States?
Austin City Limits    The Arsenio Hall Show    100 Deeds for Eddie McDowd    ChalkZone

What is an American situation comedy series that ran for one season on the Fox Television Network from September 13, 1990 to August 10, 1991. It was created by Gail Parent and executive produced by Dolly Parton and Sandy Gallin's Sandollar Productions for Twentieth Century Fox Television?
Babes    1000 Ways to Die    Blackadder    About Anglia

What is a British soft porn TV sex line aired since 2002. The first and most well-known show of its kind in the UK, it allows viewers to communicate live with female presenters via a premium-rate telephone number or text messaging?
Babestation    30 Rock    All About Me    30 Rock

What is an ABC Family original comedy television series starring Jean-Luc Bilodeau. The series was green-lighted on February 2, 2012 and began production on March 28, 2012. The show premiered on June 20, 2012. On August 17, 2012, the series was renewed for a second season, which is set to premiere on May 29, 201?
Baby Daddy    Black Books    The Beachcombers    Braceface

What is an American space opera television series created by writer and producer J. Michael Straczynski, under the Babylonian Productions label, in association with Straczynski's Synthetic Worlds Ltd?
Babylon 5    Charmed    Aliens in America    Cake Boss

What is a Nickelodeon CGI animated show that is a spin-off from the 2006 film Barnyard?
Back at the Barnyard    Brat Camp    The Beverly Hillbillies    Chicago Hope

What is an American situation comedy series, which aired on Fox from September 19, 2007 to May 14, 2008. The creators and executive producers were Christopher Lloyd and Steven Levitan, and the director was James Burrows?
Back to You    The Chimp Channel    The Big Gig    Captain Video and His Video Rangers

Whatvision program that aired on the Nine Network between 2000 through to 2007 before its cancellation?
Backyard Blitz    Breakfast News    Banacek    Catscratch

What is a 1974 UK children's television series, made by Peter Firmin and Oliver Postgate through their company Smallfilms?
Bagpuss    All Grown Up    Breaking Away    Absolutely Fabulous

What is a pocket billiards game show that began on the Game Show Network on July 18, 2005. The hosts were Sal Masekela, Ewa Mataya Laurance, and Adrianne Curry?
Ballbreakers    Back to You    Blue Peter    Brat Camp

What is an American detective TV series starring George Peppard that aired on the NBC network from 1972 to 1974. The series was part of the rotating NBC Wednesday Mystery Movie anthology?
Banacek    Black Books    The Adventures of Brisco County    Banacek

What is a planned animated television program by Brendon Small, creator of Home Movies and Metalocalypse?
Barbarian Chronicles    Ally McBeal    Angry Beavers    Beauty and the Geek

What is an American detective television series which ran on ABC from 1975 to 1978. The show was a milder version of a successful 1973–74 ABC series, Toma, starring Tony Musante as chameleon-like, real-life New Jersey police officer David Toma?
Baretta    Austin City Limits    California Dreams    Baywatch Nights

What is a television detective series starring Buddy Ebsen and Lee Meriwether as father- and daughter-in-law who run a private detective firm in Los Angeles?
Barnaby Jones    Backyard Blitz    All About Me    Charlie Rose

What is an American situation comedy television series set in a New York City police station in Greenwich Village?
Barney Miller    Cheez TV    The Amazing Race Asia    BodyShock

What is a fictional anthropomorphic red fox, best known for his appearances on daytime British children's television?
Basil Brush    Ben Casey    Better Off Ted    Charlie Rose

What is an animated television series, consisting of five-minute shorts, that first aired in September 1967. The 100-episode series was quickly created by Hal Seeger, starting in 1966, to parody the popular Batman and The Green Hornet television series which had premiered the same year?
Batfink    Absolutely Fabulous    Bunheads    Beauty and the Geek

What is an American animated television series created by Warner Bros?
Batman Beyond    Cheez TV    The Abbott and Costello Show    The Adventures of Ellery Queen

What is an American comedy-drama series that aired on NBC from October 1983 to November 1983. The series stars Michael Nouri, Dennis Franz, and Pat Corley, and was created and produced by Steven Bochco?
Bay City Blues    The Chimp Channel    Ask The Family    Camp Candy

What is an American action drama series about the Los Angeles County Lifeguards who patrol the beaches of Los Angeles County, California, starring David Hasselhoff?
Baywatch    16 and Pregnant    The Adventures of Tintin    The Big Bang Theory

What is an American police and science fiction drama series that aired in syndication from 1995 to 1997. Created by Douglas Schwartz, David Hasselhoff, and Gregory J?
Baywatch Nights    The Charmings    Carl Squared    Card Captors

Whateared as a hand puppet TV show in the late 40's created by Bob Clampett.  It later became an animated cartoon series under the Warner Brothers aegis?
Beany and Cecil    Big Town    100 Deeds for Eddie McDowd    Aaron Stone

What is a television program for young children produced for the Playhouse Disney channel by Mitchell Kriegman and The Jim Henson Company?
Bear in the Big Blue House    All in the Family    Bourbon Street Beat    The Big Gig

Whatvision show shown on ABC-TV in Australia. It is a part game show part cooking show where two contestants cook a meal out of strange ingredients within 25 minute time limit?
Beat The Chef    Allen Gregory    American Gladiators    Aqua Teen Hunger Force

What is a Goodson-Todman game show which has aired on American television in several versions since 195?
Beat the Clock    Basil Brush    Canadian Idol    Celebrity Deathmatch

What is a reality television series that is an international franchise, the U.S version is shown on The CW?
Beauty and the Geek    The Bionic Woman    The Adventures of Brisco County    Bob the Builder

What is an American television series produced by Saban Entertainment?
Beetleborgs    All Grown Up    Charlie Jade    Adventure Time

What is a television series on VH1. The series places its generality on documentation of musical artists or groups who are interviewed and profiled, and discuss how their careers became successful and what hardships they undertook?
Behind the Music    Back to You    American Gladiators    The Banana Splits

What is a Canadian comedy-drama television series that aired on CBC from January 5, 2009 to December 12, 201?
Being Erica    Airwolf    Catscratch    100 Questions

What is a Canadian animated series produced by Studio B Productions, Corus Entertainment and Nelvana, focusing on 12-year-old Ian Kelley, who aspires to become a filmmaker?
Being Ian    Bourbon Street Beat    Ally McBeal    The Brady Bunch

What is an American media franchise created by "Man of Action" (a group consisting of Duncan Rouleau, Joe Casey, Joe Kelly, and Steven T?
Ben 10    Chicagolicious    Ask The Family    The Adventures of Chico and Guapo

What is an American medical drama series which ran on ABC from 1961 to 1966. The show was known for its opening titles, which consisted of a hand drawing the symbols "♂, ♀, ✳, †, ∞" on a chalkboard, as cast member Sam Jaffe intoned, "Man, woman, birth, death, infinity." Neurosurgeon Joseph Ransohoff was a medical consultant for the show and may have influenced the personality of the title character?
Ben Casey    Black Books    Bagpuss    Blonde Charity Mafia

Whathis other television series Andy Richter Controls the Universe and the short-lived show Life on a Stick), who also served as the show's Executive Producer?
Better Off Ted    64 Zoo Lane    Art Attack    The Amazing Race

What is an American romantic sitcom TV show starring Joanna Garcia Swisher and Jennifer Finnigan?
Better with You    Being Ian    American Gladiators    The Beachcombers

What is an affluent city in Los Angeles County, California, United States, surrounded by the City of Los Angeles?
Beverly Hills    The Amanda Show    The Barbara Stanwyck Show    Baretta

What is an American situation comedy originally broadcast for eight seasons on ABC from 1964 to 1972. It was created by Sol Saks under executive director Harry Ackerman, and stars Elizabeth Montgomery, Dick York (1964–1969), Dick Sargent (1969–1972), Agnes Moorehead, and David White?
Bewitched    Adventures in Wonderland    Batman Beyond    Airwolf

Whatis a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Takao Aoki in order to promote sales of spinning tops called "s"?
Beyblade    7th Heaven    6teen    Blue Peter

What is an Australian television series that was broadcast on the Seven Network from 1999 until 2005. It starred four hosts, who hosted the show in a large model bus?
Big Arvo    Adam Adamant Lives    The Alan Young Show    666 Park Avenue

Whatvision drama that aired on HBO between March 2006 and March 2011.  The show is about a fictional fundamentalist Mormon family in Utah that practices polygamy?
Big Love    Childrens Hospital    Canadian Idol    Beverly Hills

What is an American television series created by Scott Fellows about the Hollywood misadventures of four hockey players from Minnesota—Kendall, James, Carlos, and Logan, after they are selected to form a boy band?
Big Time Rush    The Abbott and Costello Show    Babestation    Armstrong Circle Theatre

What is a popular long-running radio drama series which was later adapted to both film and television and a comic book published by DC Comics?
Big Town    8 Simple Rules    Camp Runamuck    Babylon 5

What is an educational television program that originally aired from September 10, 1993 to June 20, 1998, hosted by William "Bill" Nye and produced by Buena Vista Television?
Bill Nye the Science Guy    The Brady Bunch Hour    Being Erica    The Bold Ones

What is a British sitcom created by Dylan Moran and Graham Linehan that was broadcast on Channel 4 from 2000 to 2004. Starring Moran, Bill Bailey and Tamsin Greig, the series is set in the eponymous London bookshop  and follows the lives of its owner Bernard Black, his assistant Manny Bianco (Bailey) and their friend Fran Katzenjammer (Greig)?
Black Books    Big Time Rush    The Beachcombers    As Told By Ginger

What is the name that encompassed four series of a BBC 1 period British sitcom, along with several one-off instalments?
Blackadder    American Dreams    The Andy Griffith Show    Bob Hope Presents the Chrysler Theatre

Whatvision series produced by Patty Ivins and Julie Pizzi that followed the lives of three socialites whose lives revolved around charity events?
Blonde Charity Mafia    Captain Planet and the Planeteers    Charlie Rose    Bob Hope Presents the Chrysler Theatre

What is an Australian police drama series which depicted the lives of police officers stationed at the fictional Mount Thomas police station in a small town in Victoria?
Blue Heelers    American Chopper    Bob and Margaret    Bagpuss

What is the world's longest-running children's television programme. Although the show has a nautical title and theme, its current format takes the form of a magazine/entertainment show containing viewer and presenter challenges, as well as the famous arts and crafts "makes" (see below)?
Blue Peter    BodyShaping    1000 Ways to Die    Babestation

What is an American television series from premium cable channel HBO, set in Atlantic City, New Jersey during the Prohibition era?
Boardwalk Empire    The Andy Dick Show    Big Arvo    Afro Samurai

What is a Canadian/UK animated television series that was also shown in the United States and all over the world?
Bob and Margaret    Bewitched    Canadian Idol    Big Love

What is an American anthology series, sponsored by Chrysler Corporation, which ran on NBC from 1963 through 1967.  The show was hosted by Bob Hope, but it had a variety of formats, including musical, dramatic, and comedy?
Bob Hope Presents the Chrysler Theatre    Champion the Wonder Horse    Carl Squared    Carl Squared

What is a British children's animated television show created by Keith Chapman. In the original series Bob appears as a building contractor specializing in masonry in a stop motion animated programme with his colleague Wendy, various neighbours and friends, and their gang of anthropomorphised work-vehicles and equipment (all made of clay)?
Bob the Builder    2DTV    Angry Boys    The Brady Bunch Hour

What is an American home improvement television show host known for This Old House (1979–1989), 's Home Again (1990–2005), and  (2005–2007)?
Bob Vila    BrainSurge    Backyard Blitz    Bubble Guppies

What is a TV fitness and exercise show, with segments on weight training, cardiovascular exercise, stretching and nutrition?
BodyShaping    Brass Eye    The Arthur Murray Party    Beyblade

What is a sensationalistic documentary series about the conditions or lives of extraordinary people?
BodyShock    Beetleborgs    Captain Kangaroo    Blackadder

What is an NBC televison western series, that ran from September 12, 1959 to January 16, 1973. Lasting 14 seasons and 430 episodes, it ranks as the second longest running western series (behind Gunsmoke) and still continues to air in syndication?
Bonanza    The Amazing World Of Gumball    The Amazing Race Asia    Allen Gregory

What is an American comedy series that ran on HBO from September 20, 2009 to November 28, 2011. The show was created by author Jonathan Ames, and stars Jason Schwartzman as a fictional Jonathan Ames—a writer based in Brooklyn, New York City, who moonlights as an unlicensed private detective?
Bored to Death    The Carol Burnett Show    Beverly Hills    6teen

What is an American legal dramedy created by David E. Kelley and produced in association with 20th Century Fox Television for the ABC?
Boston Legal    BrainSurge    Braceface    Afro Samurai

What is an American drama television series created by David E. Kelley and broadcast on Fox. It centered on Winslow High School, a fictional public high school located in Boston, Massachusetts?
Boston Public    Access Hollywood    Anything but Love    Atomic Betty

What is a private detective series which aired on the ABC network from 1959-1960 and featured Richard Long as Rex Randolph, Andrew Duggan as Cal Calhoun, Van Williams as Kenny Madison, and Arlene Howell as Melody Lee Mercer, the secretary at the New Orleans detective agency in which they worked?
Bourbon Street Beat    The Brady Brides    American Bandstand    Aliens in the Family

What is an American television sitcom that chronicles the coming of age events and everyday life-lessons of Cory Matthews (played by Ben Savage), a Philadelphian who grows up from a young boy to a married man?
Boy Meets World    All Grown Up    Boardwalk Empire    Chicagolicious

What is a Canadian animated series that aired on Teletoon in Canada, and on Disney Channel and ABC Family in the United States, as well as Pop Girl in Australia?
Braceface    Big Time Rush    Celebrity Rehab Presents Sober House    All My Children

What is an American children's game show aired on Nickelodeon hosted by Jeff Sutphen. The show taped its first season in February 2009, and debuted on September 28, 2009. The show's format was adapted from the Tokyo Broadcasting System game show Brain Survivor?
BrainSurge    Bubble Guppies    All My Children    Bubble Guppies

What is a UK television series of satirical news magazines. A series of six aired on Channel 4 in 1997, and a further episode in 200?
Brass Eye    Bourbon Street Beat    Ace of Cakes    Beat The Chef

What is a reality television sho?
Brat Camp    The Beverly Hillbillies    Captain Nice    Call Red

What was a breakfast news show which first aired on BBC One on 4 September 1989. The programme was previously known as Breakfast Time?
Breakfast News    The Barbara Stanwyck Show    Absolutely Fabulous    Bagpuss

What is a 1979 American coming of age comedy-drama film that follows a group of four male teenagers in Bloomington, Indiana, who have recently graduated from high school?
Breaking Away    The Amazing Chan and the Chan Clan    100 Winners    Byker Grove

What is an American television drama series created and produced by Vince Gilligan. Set and produced in Albuquerque, New Mexico,  is the story of Walter White (Bryan Cranston), a struggling high school chemistry teacher who is diagnosed with inoperable lung cancer at the beginning of the series?
Breaking Bad    The Bob Newhart Show    Big Time Rush    All in the Family

What is an American reality series on VH1 that starred former child actor Danny Bonaduce and his wife Gretchen?
Breaking Bonaduce    Baywatch Nights    Aliens in the Family    Afro Samurai

What is an  created by Bernard Slade, the creator of the 1970–74 ABC sitcom, The Partridge Family, and the 1967-70 sitcom The Flying Nun?
Bridget Loves Bernie    BrainSurge    The Bob Newhart Show    The Carol Burnett Show

What is an animated series about a British high school in South London. It first aired on Teletoon in Canada and Channel 4 in the United Kingdom (incomplete run)?
Bromwell High    Camp Runamuck    Bug Juice    Acme Hour

What is a VH1 reality series spin off from the hit VH1 reality program, Hogan Knows Best?
Brooke Knows Best    Beat the Clock    Baretta    Baretta

What is an American preschool children's television series produced for Nickelodeon and created by Jonny Belt and Robert Scull?
Bubble Guppies    Captain Video and His Video Rangers    The Book Quiz    The Bionic Woman

What is a Disney Channel reality series that premiered on February 28, 1998. It was named after the slang term for large quantities of super-sweet juice drinks made with artificially flavored powder such as Kool-Aid that are often served at summer camps?
Bug Juice    Art Attack    American Pickers    Camp Lazlo

What is a Canadian game show in which two teams of two players attempted to decipher vanity license plates?
Bumper Stumpers    Bumpety Boo    Ben 10    Back at the Barnyard

Whatvision show produced by the Nippon Animation company from 1985 to 1986. The series consisted of 130 10-minute episodes, distributed as 43 half-hour segments?
Bumpety Boo    Captain Kangaroo    Camp Lazlo    The Backyardigans

What is an American television comedy-drama series created by Amy Sherman-Palladino and Lamar Damon, starring Sutton Foster?
Bunheads    Boardwalk Empire    Allen Gregory    Aliens in the Family

What is an American television series created by Matt Nix. The show stars Jeffrey Donovan, Gabrielle Anwar, Bruce Campbell, Sharon Gless, and, beginning in the fourth season, Coby Bell?
Burn Notice    The Brady Bunch    Ace of Cakes    Alphas

What is a British television series which aired between 1989 and 2006 and was created by Adele Rose?
Byker Grove    Brass Eye    Angry Beavers    21 Jump Street

What is an educational Canadian children's television series, based on the books by author Christine L'Heureux and illustrator Hélène Desputeaux?
Caillou    Breaking Bonaduce    704 Hauser    Boy Meets World

What is an American reality television series, airing on the cable television network TLC. The show follows the operations of Carlo's Bakery, a family-owned business in Hoboken, New Jersey owned and operated by siblings Buddy Valastro (to whom the series' title refers), Lisa Valastro, Maddalena Castano, Grace Faugno and Mary Sciarrone?
Cake Boss    4th and Long    3 lbs    Animal Jam

What is an American teen-oriented sitcom that aired from 1992 to 1996 on Saturday mornings during NBC's TNBC programming block?
California Dreams    Bunheads    The Beachcombers    Bob Hope Presents the Chrysler Theatre

What is a British drama television series created by J. C. Wilsher. The series premiered 8 January 1996, on ITV?
Call Red    Art Attack    Blue Peter    Ask The Family

What is a 1989-1992 animated television series produced by DIC Entertainment, with comedian John Candy providing the voice for an animated version of himself?
Camp Candy    Animaniacs    Ally McBeal    Airwolf

What is an American animated television series created by Joe Murray. The series was released on July 8, 2005, in the United States and was released on November 1, 2005, in the United Kingdom?
Camp Lazlo    Behind the Music    Boy Meets World    Charlie Rose

What is an American sitcom which aired on NBC during the 1965-1966 television season. The series was created and executive produced by David Swift, and aired for 26 episodes?
Camp Runamuck    The Bugs Bunny Show    Babes    21 Jump Street

Whatvision competition show which aired on CTV, based on the British show Pop Idol?
Canadian Idol    The Andy Dick Show    ChalkZone    Boston Legal

What is an American hidden camera/practical joke reality television series created and produced by Allen Funt, which initially began on radio as Candid Microphone June 28, 1947. After a series of theatrical film shorts, also titled Candid Microphone, Funt's concept came to television on August 10, 1948. Its last original broadcast was on May 5, 200?
Candid Camera    Andy Richter Controls the Universe    3rd Rock from the Sun    Celebrity Charades

What is an animated series created by Joe Ruby and Ken Spears and produced by Hanna-Barbera Productions from September 10, 1977 to June 21, 1980 on ABC?
Captain Caveman and the Teen Angels    The Adventures of Chico and Guapo    Car 54    Black Books

What is an American children's television series which aired weekday mornings on the American television network CBS for nearly 30 years, from October 3, 1955 until December 8, 1984, making it the longest-running nationally broadcast children's television program of its day?
Captain Kangaroo    The Ben Stiller Show    The Amazing World Of Gumball    According to Jim

What is an American comedy TV series that ran from January–May 1967 on NBC.  Riding the tide of the camp superhero craze of the 1960s, the show's premise involved police chemist Carter Nash (William Daniels), a mild-mannered mama's boy who discovered a secret formula that, when taken, transformed him into ?
Captain Nice    Babylon 5    Absolutely Fabulous    The Arsenio Hall Show

What is an American animated environmentalist television program created by Ted Turner, Robert Larkin III, and Barbara Pyle, produced by Pyle, Nicholas Boxer, Andy Heyward and Robby London, and developed by Pyle, Boxer, Heyward, London, Thom Beers, Bob Forward, Phil Harnage and Cassandra Schafhausen?
Captain Planet and the Planeteers    Basil Brush    American Chopper    Ally McBeal

What is a 1987–88 science fiction/action television series, merging live action with animation based on computer-generated images, that ran for 22 episodes in Canadian and American syndication?
Captain Power    Barney Miller    The Charmings    Boston Legal

What is a 1960s British science-fiction television series produced by the Century 21 Productions company of Gerry and Sylvia Anderson, John Read and Reg Hill?
Captain Scarlet and the Mysterons    The Adventures of Wild Bill Hickok    Barnaby Jones    AfterMASH

What is an American science fiction television series, which was aired on the DuMont Television Network, and was the first series of its kind on American television?
Captain Video and His Video Rangers    Bridget Loves Bernie    American Dream Derby    The Chimp Channel

What is an American sitcom that ran on NBC from 1961 to 1963, and featured two New York police officers in their patrol car?
Car 54    2 Broke Girls    Bored to Death    Brat Camp

What is a Japanese shōjo manga series written and illustrated by the manga group Clamp?
Card Captors    Beyblade    Bridget Loves Bernie    The Bob Cummings Show

What is an American television game show created by Chester Feldman for Mark Goodson-Bill Todman Productions?
Card Sharks    The Chimp Channel    Celebrity Charades    Back at the Barnyard

What is a Canadian animated series which explores what would happen if a teenager had a clone?
Carl Squared    1000 Ways to Die    The Adventures of Brisco County    The Catherine Tate Show

What is an American situation comedy that ran on the NBC television network. It stars Lea Thompson as cartoonist Caroline Duffy, who lives in Manhattan in New York City?
Caroline in the City    Boston Legal    The Adventures of Chico and Guapo    Ally McBeal

What is a TV game show devised by Adam Wood that originated in the United Kingdom and has been licensed to television networks in numerous other countries?
Cash Cab    2 Broke Girls    Bay City Blues    Camp Runamuck

What is an American animated television series which premiered on April 4, 1998. The series was created for Nickelodeon by Peter Hannan?
CatDog    All Grown Up    The Bob Cummings Show    Ace of Cakes

Whatvision series created by Doug TenNapel. It was aired on Nickelodeon in 2005 and on Nicktoons in 2005. It was also shown on Nickelodeon UK / Ireland in 2006. It is a lighthearted adaptation of TenNapel's graphic novel, Gear, which is also the name of the cats' monster truck?
Catscratch    Aqua Teen Hunger Force    30 Rock    Attack Of The Show

Whatvision show on GSN where celebrities played tournament style blackjack for charity?
Celebrity Blackjack    Bourbon Street Beat    Bubble Guppies    Baby Daddy

What is a series which originally aired from January to September, 1979 as a syndicated series throughout the United States?
Celebrity Charades    Blonde Charity Mafia    2 Broke Girls    Barbarian Chronicles

What is a claymation television show that depicts celebrities against each other in a wrestling ring, almost always ending in the loser's gruesome death?
Celebrity Deathmatch    Baywatch    Captain Nice    The Adventures of Rin Tin Tin

What is a VH1 reality television show. It is a spin-off of Celebrity Rehab with Dr?
Celebrity Rehab Presents Sober House    Celebrity Deathmatch    Chicagolicious    Akumaizer 3

What is an American animated television series created by Bill Burnett and Larry Huber and produced by Frederator Studios for the Nickelodeon TV channel?
ChalkZone    The Big Gig    Ben Casey    Angry Boys

What is an American children's Western series that aired from September 23, 1955 to March 3, 1956 for 26 episodes on CBS?
Champion the Wonder Horse    Aliens in America    Babylon 5    Barnaby Jones

What is the main protagonist in the comic strip Peanuts by Charles M. Schul?
Charlie Brown    BodyShock    Baretta    Being Erica

Whatvision programmes that are Gran and Bertha?
Charlie Chalk    Alphas    The Amanda Show    All About Me

What is a science fiction television program filmed mainly in Cape Town, South Africa. It stars Jeffrey Pierce in the title role, as a detective from a parallel universe who finds himself trapped in our universe?
Charlie Jade    Babestation    The Abbott and Costello Show    The Candy Apple News Company

What is an American television talk show host and journalist?
Charlie Rose    Blue Heelers    Baywatch    Ask The Family

What is an American television series created by writer Constance M. Burge and produced by Aaron Spelling and his production company Spelling Television, with writer/director Brad Kern as showrunner?
Charmed    The Backyardigans    Charlie Brown    Blonde Charity Mafia

What is an American sitcom television series that ran for 11 seasons from 1982 to 1993. It was produced by Charles/Burrows/Charles Productions, in association with Paramount Network Television for NBC, and was created by the team of James Burrows, Glen Charles, and Les Charles?
Cheers    American Horror Story    The Beverly Hillbillies    The Carol Burnett Show

What was an Australian children's cartoon show, created by Bill McQueen, that aired on weekday mornings on Network Ten?
Cheez TV    Bug Juice    Bob and Margaret    Carl Squared

What is a reality television series which airs on Food Network Canada. It is a 26-part docu-soap that follows the experiences of 12 students at the Stratford , one of Canada's most prestigious culinary schools?
Chef School    The Buzz on Maggie    Burn Notice    Adventures in Wonderland

What is an American medical drama television series, created by David E. Kelley. It ran on CBS from September 28, 1994, to May 4, 2000. The series is set in a fictional private charity hospital in Chicago, Illinois?
Chicago Hope    Alice    The Adventures of Ellery Queen    2 Broke Girls

What is an American reality television series on the Style Network. The series debuted on June 11, 2012. The series is a spin off of the popular series Jerseylicious?
Chicagolicious    4th and Long    According to Jim    The Book Quiz

What is an American sitcom which ran on NBC for four seasons, from September 13, 1974, to July 21, 1978. It stars Jack Albertson as Ed Brown (the Man), the cantankerous owner of a run down garage in an East Los Angeles barrio, and (until his suicide late in the third season) Freddie Prinze as Chico Rodriguez, an upbeat, optimistic Chicano young man who comes in looking for a job?
Chico and the Man    Batfink    101 Ways to Leave a Gameshow    Bubble Guppies

What is a satirical American comedy television series and web series that lampoons the medical drama genre, created by and starring actor/comedian Rob Corddry?
Childrens Hospital    Champion the Wonder Horse    Charlie Jade    Captain Scarlet and the Mysterons

What is a science fiction TV series produced by CBS Paramount Network Television in association with Sky Television, Renegade 83, and American Zoetrope for USA Network?
The 4400    The Banana Splits    Babestation    Charmed

What is the flagship television program of the Christian Broadcasting Network, airing in syndication throughout the United States and also available worldwide on CBN.com?
The 700 Club    Afro Samurai    Alfred Hitchcock Presents    American Bandstand

What is an American television sitcom starring the popular comedy team of Bud Abbott and Lou Costello that premiered in syndication in the fall of 1952 and ran until May 195?
The Abbott and Costello Show    Batfink    The Beachcombers    ANT Farm

Whatrisco or Brisco County, is an American Western/science fiction television series created by Jeffrey Boam and Carlton Cuse?
The Adventures of Brisco County    Bob Hope Presents the Chrysler Theatre    The Amazing Race Asia    21 Jump Street

What is a show that aired originally on MTV2's Sic 'Em Fridays, but currently it can be found on MTV Overdrive?
The Adventures of Chico and Guapo    Captain Kangaroo    Captain Planet and the Planeteers    Bonanza

What is the title of a radio series and four separate television series made from the 1950s through the 1970s?
The Adventures of Ellery Queen    ANT Farm    Breaking Away    The Alan Young Show

What is an American children's television program, which originally aired in 166 episodes on ABC from October 1954 until May 1959. It starred child actor Lee Aaker as Rusty, a boy orphaned in an Indian raid, who was being raised by the soldiers at a US Cavalry post known in the series as Fort Apache?
The Adventures of Rin Tin Tin    Captain Power    Boy Meets World    Charlie Chalk

What is a British television series based on the adventure novel of the same name by Baroness Emmuska Orczy?
The Adventures of the Scarlet Pimpernel    Arthur Godfrey and His Friends    31 Minutes    18 to Life

What is a series of comic albums created by Belgian cartoonist  (1907–1983), who wrote under the pen name of Hergé?
The Adventures of Tintin    Alas Smith and Jones    Animaniacs    Card Captors

What is an American Western television series which ran for eight seasons from 1951 through 1958.  The Screen Gems series began in syndication, but ran on CBS from 1955 through 1958, and, at the same time, on ABC from 1957 through 195?
The Adventures of Wild Bill Hickok    21 Jump Street    Ace Lightning    Basil Brush

What is an American radio and television series presented in diverse formats over a nine-year period and starring Canadian-English actor Alan Young?
The Alan Young Show    Caroline in the City    AfterMASH    The Charmings

What is an American live-action sketch comedy and variety show that aired on Nickelodeon from October 16, 1999 to September 21, 2002. It starred Amanda Bynes, Drake Bell, and Nancy Sullivan, along with several performing artists who came and left at different points, such as John Kassir, Raquel Lee, and Josh Peck?
The Amanda Show    The Adventures of Ellery Queen    Ballbreakers    Bridget Loves Bernie

What is a 1972 TV series made by Australia's Eric Porter Studios for American Hanna-Barbera Studios and CBS?
The Amazing Chan and the Chan Clan    American Bandstand    Bewitched    Back to You

What is a reality television game show in which teams of two people, who have some form of a preexisting personal relationship, race around the world in competition with other teams?
The Amazing Race    Big Love    Brooke Knows Best    Catscratch

What is a reality game show based on the American series, The Amazing Rac?
The Amazing Race Asia    The Andy Griffith Show    Captain Caveman and the Teen Angels    The Bradys

What is an Annie Award winning British/American animated television series created by Ben Bocquelet and produced by Cartoon Network Development Studio Europe?
The Amazing World Of Gumball    The Chimp Channel    Baywatch    Ben 10

What is an American drama series that aired on Fox from March to April 2002. The series was created by James D?
The American Embassy    Beauty and the Geek    Ace Lightning    Ben Casey

What is an American sketch comedy series that aired on MTV from February 2001 to May 2002. The series was created by and starred comedian Andy Dick?
The Andy Dick Show    Cheez TV    64 Zoo Lane    All My Children

What is an American sitcom first televised on CBS between October 3, 1960, and April 1, 1968. Andy Griffith portrays the widowed sheriff of the fictional small community of Mayberry,  North Carolina?
The Andy Griffith Show    The Bob Cummings Show    Bubble Guppies    Anything but Love

What is an American television variety show that ran from 1962 to 1971 (alternating during the summer of 1970 with Andy Williams Presents Ray Stevens), and a short-lived run in syndication, beginning in the fall of 1976.  It was hosted by crooner Andy Williams?
The Andy Williams Show    ChalkZone    The Carol Burnett Show    The Banana Splits

What is an American variety/talk show that aired late weeknights in syndication from January 3, 1989 to May 27, 1994. The show was created and hosted by comedian/actor Arsenio Hall, and took place at the Paramount Studios in Hollywood, Los Angeles?
The Arsenio Hall Show    Boston Legal    Backyard Blitz    Childrens Hospital

What is an American television variety show which ran from July 1950 until September 1960. The show was hosted by famous dancers Arthur and Kathryn Murray, and was basically one long advertisement for their chain of dance studios?
The Arthur Murray Party    The Barbara Stanwyck Show    The Adventures of Chico and Guapo    CarnivÃ le

What is a Canadian sitcom that aired from 10 July 2009 to 11 September 2009. The series is the second original comedy to air on the Nickelodeon channel, The N (now TeenNick) after the series About a Girl?
The Assistants    2DTV    The Amazing World Of Gumball    Atomic Betty

What is a spin-off from the American competitive reality dating game show The Bachelor. In its January 2003 debut on ABC, the first season featured Trista Rehn, the runner-up date from the first season of The Bachelor, offering the opportunity for Rehn to choose a husband among 25 bachelors?
The Bachelorette    The Bold Ones    31 Minutes    Ace of Cakes

What is a Canadian-American 3-D CGI-animated children's TV series, created by Janice Burgess?
The Backyardigans    Black Books    Allen Gregory    The Brady Bunch

Whatvision variety program featuring , a fictional rock band composed of four funny animal characters?
The Banana Splits    2 Broke Girls    Being Ian    Batman Beyond

What is an American anthology drama television series which ran on NBC from September 1960 to September 1961. Barbara Stanwyck served as hostess, and starred in all but four of the half-hour productions?
The Barbara Stanwyck Show    60 Minutes    Alfred Hitchcock Presents    The Assistants

What is a Canadian comedy-drama television series that ran from October 1, 1972 to December 12, 1990 and is the longest-running dramatic series ever made for English-language Canadian television?
The Beachcombers    Andy Richter Controls the Universe    Burn Notice    100 Deeds for Eddie McDowd

What is the name of two sketch comedy television shows that aired on MTV from 1990 to 1991, and then on Fox from September 1992 to January 1993. The Fox show stars Ben Stiller, Andy Dick, Janeane Garofalo and Bob Odenkirk?
The Ben Stiller Show    The Bob Newhart Show    The Bob Newhart Show    77 Sunset Strip

Whattish comedy television show starring Benny Hill. There were various incarnations of the show between 15 January 1955 and 30 May 1991, and it aired in over 140 countries?
The Benny Hill Show    The 4400    The Bachelorette    Charmed

What is a television game show in the United States where men competed against women in a "battle of the sexes" format?
The Better Sex    Ask This Old House    Blackadder    Big Time Rush

What is an American situation comedy originally broadcast for nine seasons on CBS from 1962 to 1971, starring Buddy Ebsen, Irene Ryan, Donna Douglas, and Max Baer, Jr?
The Beverly Hillbillies    Bewitched    The Bionic Woman    American Gladiators

What is an American sitcom created by Chuck Lorre and Bill Prady, both of whom serve as executive producers on the show, along with Steven Molaro?
The Big Bang Theory    The Bob Cummings Show    The Bradys    The American Embassy

Whatvision comedy series based on the British TV series Saturday Live?
The Big Gig    Angry Boys    The Brady Bunch    Bourbon Street Beat

Whatis an American western television series which ran on ABC from September 15, 1965, to May 19, 1969. The show stars Barbara Stanwyck, as the widow of a wealthy nineteenth century California rancher?
The Big Valley     Active Kids    Big Time Rush    60 Minutes

What is an American television series starring Lindsay Wagner that aired for three seasons between 1976 and 1978 as a spin off from The Six Million Dollar Man?
The Bionic Woman    Babestation    Armstrong Circle Theatre    The American Embassy

What is an American sitcom starring Robert "Bob" Cummings which was produced from January 2, 1955 to September 15, 1959.  was the first series ever to debut as a midseason replacement?
The Bob Cummings Show    American Gladiators    The Ben Stiller Show    Alfred Hitchcock Presents

What is an American situation comedy produced by MTM Enterprises, which aired 142 original episodes on CBS from September 16, , to April 1, ?
The Bob Newhart Show    The Barbara Stanwyck Show    Captain Scarlet and the Mysterons    The Adventures of Tintin

What is an American television soap opera created by William J?
The Bold and the Beautiful    1000 Ways to Die    Aqua Teen Hunger Force    Celebrity Rehab Presents Sober House

What is the umbrella title for several television series. It was produced by Universal Television and broadcast on NBC from 1969 to 1973. It was a wheel format series, an NBC programming approach also used by that network in series such as The Name of the Game and the NBC Mystery Movie?
The Bold Ones    Chico and the Man    The Brady Bunch    The Arsenio Hall Show

What is a BBC Four quiz programme. The first series, first broadcast in 2007, was hosted by David Baddiel with a second 2008 series hosted by Kirsty Wark?
The Book Quiz    Byker Grove    American Gladiators    The Bugaloos

What is a locally-produced children's television program that aired on WGN-TV in Chicago and nationally on what is now WGN America?
The Bozo Show    Braceface    Camp Candy    Brass Eye

What is an American sitcom created by Sherwood Schwartz and starring Robert Reed, Florence Henderson, and Ann B?
The Brady Brides    Camp Candy    2 Broke Girls    Anything but Love

What is an American sitcom created by Sherwood Schwartz and starring Robert Reed, Florence Henderson, and Ann B?
The Brady Bunch    CatDog    About Anglia    Big Arvo

What is an American variety television series produced by Sid and Marty Krofft in association with Paramount Television, which aired on ABC between 1976 to 197?
The Brady Bunch Hour    Bonanza    The 700 Club    All That

What is a six-episode American drama series that aired on CBS in 1990. It was a revival of the early 1970s sitcom, The Brady Bunch (1969–1974), and was about the trials and tribulations of the extended Brady family some 15 years after the end of the earlier series?
The Bradys    Baby Daddy    Adventures in Wonderland    Afro Samurai

Whatvision series, produced by brothers Sidney Krofft and Martin Krofft, airing on NBC on Saturday mornings from 1970 to 1972. The show featured a musical group composed of four British-accented teenagers, who lived in fictional Tranquility Forest?
The Bugaloos    The Bold Ones    Bumpety Boo    Canadian Idol

What is an Animated television anthology series hosted by Bugs Bunny, that was mainly composed of Looney Tunes and Merrie Melodies cartoons released by Warner Bros?
The Bugs Bunny Show    American Bandstand    Boy Meets World    The Buzz on Maggie

Whatvision series which originally aired for 21 episodes between June 2005 and May 2006. The series focuses on Maggie Pesky, a happy-go-lucky tween fly, that aspires of becoming a rock star, but many episodes focus on her daily life?
The Buzz on Maggie    Bubble Guppies    Beat The Chef    The Adventures of Ellery Queen

Whatvision series that aired in the 1970s and 1980s on WCAU-TV, Channel 10 in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania?
The Candy Apple News Company    Canadian Idol    Ben Casey    Camp Runamuck

What is an American variety/sketch comedy television show starring Carol Burnett, Harvey Korman, Vicki Lawrence, Lyle Waggoner, and Tim Conway?
The Carol Burnett Show    Bob Hope Presents the Chrysler Theatre    AfterMASH    100 Winners

What is a British television sketch comedy written by Catherine Tate and Aschlin Ditta?
The Catherine Tate Show    The Candy Apple News Company    Camp Lazlo    CatDog

What is an American fantasy sitcom that aired from March 1987 to February 1988 on ABC. Based on the fairy tale Snow White, it chronicles Snow White and Prince Charming after they are transported in time from the Enchanted Forest to the 20th Century Los Angeles suburbs?
The Charmings    Breaking Away    Brat Camp    The Amanda Show

What is an American comedy television series which aired on TBS Superstation in 1999. Based on the Monkey-ed Movies interstitials that TBS aired one year prior, it is the network's first original sitcom?
The Chimp Channel    Blue Heelers    Car 54    Angry Beavers

