What is a self-taught software engineer, game developer and entrepreneur most widely known as the co-creator of Endless Ages, a first person shooter MMOG combined with elements of role playing; thus making it the world's first MMOFPSRPG (massively-multplayer-online-first-person-shooter-role-playing-game), as it was heralded in its day?
Aaron Boucher    Jeff Bonwick    R. Luke DuBois    Jeff Atwood

Whatvist?
Aaron Swartz    Michael J. Karels    Ronald Dale Harris    Biz Stone

What is an American software engineer, and one of the three authors of DTrace, a dynamic tracing facility in Solaris 10 (Sun Microsystems' latest OS) which allows users to observe, debug and tune system behavior in real time?
Adam Leventhal (programmer)    Jeremie Miller    Charles Simonyi    Brad Fitzpatrick

What (December 21, 1920 – November, 1964), born Adele Katz, wrote the complete technical description for the first electronic digital computer, ENIAC?
Adele Goldstine    Ward Christensen    Scott Guthrie    Corrinne Yu

What is an American software designer and programmer. Widely recognized as the “Father of Visual Basic," Cooper is also known for his books on About Face 3: The Essentials of Interaction Design and The Inmates Are Running the Asylum: Why High-Tech Products Drive Us Crazy and How to Restore the Sanity?
Alan Cooper    Bram Cohen    Eric Allman    Scott A. Jones

Whattis Kay (born May 17, 1940) is an American computer scientist, known for his early pioneering work on object-oriented programming and windowing graphical user interface design, and for coining the phrase, "The best way to predict the future is to invent it?
Alan Kay    Dick Smith (software)    Jeff Bonwick    Pito Salas

Whattist known for his work at Digital Equipment Corporation (Digital, or DEC) and at the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C)?
Alan Kotok    Jeffrey Peterson    Jon Mittelhauser    Phil Katz

What is one of the initiators of the agile movement in software development, helping write the Manifesto for Agile Software Development in 2001, the agile PM Declaration of Interdependence in 2005, and co-founding the [http://icagile.com International Consortium for Agile] in 2009 (with Ahmed Sidky and Ash Rofail)?
Alistair Cockburn    Rich Skrenta    Robert Abbott (game designer)    Wil Shipley

What is an American computer programmer best known for his iOS app Twittelator, which to date has sold over a million units for the iPhone and the iPad?
Andrew C. Stone    O. Arthur Stiennon    Daniel Kottke    Darin Adler

Whatlisher, photographer, programmer and attorney best known as the inventor of what is now known as the shareware business model for software marketing?
Andrew Fluegelman    Steven Snyder    Robert Tappan Morris    Andrew Fluegelman

What is a former AT&T and Bell Labs researcher and programmer. He is the author of C Traps and Pitfalls, co-author (with Barbara Moo) of Accelerated C++ & Ruminations on C++, and his name is associated with argument-dependent name lookup, also known as "Koenig lookup"?
Andrew Koenig (programmer)    Wayne Chang    Bob Scheifler    Stephen Warshall

What is a writer of books on software development. Hunt co-authored The Pragmatic Programmer, six other books and many article?
Andy Hunt (author)    Ward Christensen    Russ Nelson    Bruce Ableson

What is an American businessman, investor, and autho?
Andy Kessler (author)    Kelley Deal    Steve Wozniak    Mark Harris (programmer)

What is an American TV host, acclaimed fisherman, and web entrepreneur.  He is the founder and owner of Sound Strategies, Inc a leading NY based web services provider specializing in search engine optimization?
Andy LoCascio    Virgil Griffith    Qi Lu    Gordon Lyon

What is a software developer best known for her work with Drupal, a free and open source content management system and content management framework?
Angela Byron    Wayne Bell (computer specialist)    Phil Katz    Danny Goodman

What is an American  interface designer. He is the son of human-computer interface expert Jef Raskin?
Aza Raskin    Angela Byron    Pat Villani    Ward Christensen

What is a computer scientist and software researcher.  He retired from IBM's Thomas J?
Barry Leiba    Lois Haibt    Death of Kevin Flanagan    Daniel Weinreb

What is a Taiwanese-born American and Canadian computer programmer and entrepreneur?
Ben Chiu    Peter Norton    Jeff Raikes    Daniel Kottke

What is an author and Senior Technical Evangelist for Adobe Systems, particularly ColdFusion and Flex, and the owner of EmTek Systems?
Ben Forta    Joe Hewitt (programmer)    Martin Roesch    Ward Christensen

What is a co-founder (with wife Mena Trott) of Six Apart, creator of Movable Type and TypePad?
Benjamin Trott    Jeff De Luca    Trung Dung    Mark Allen (software developer)

WhatFrances Elizabeth "Betty" Holberton (March 7, 1917 – December 8, 2001) was one of the six original programmers of ENIAC, the first general-purpose electronic digital computer?
Betty Holberton    Samy Kamkar    Ken Arnold    Elliot Koffman

What is an American business magnate, investor, programmer, inventor and philanthropist?
Bill Gates    Ben Forta    Wendell Brown    Phil Katz

What is an American computer scientist.  Joy co-founded Sun Microsystems in 1982 along with Vinod Khosla, Scott McNealy and Andreas von Bechtolsheim, and served as chief scientist at the company until 2003. He played an integral role in the early development of BSD UNIX while a graduate student at Berkeley, and he is the original author of the vi text editor?
Bill Joy    Donald Knuth    Cathy Hudgins    Joel McCormack

What is an American software engineer best known for creating and maintaining Tux Paint, an open source bitmap graphics editor for children?
Bill Kendrick    Owen Mock    Paul Buchheit    Jonathan Alexander

WhatWilliam Paul "Bill" Zeller (October 26, 1983 – January 5, 2011) was an American computer programmer who was best known for creating the MyTunes application?
Bill Zeller    Carl Hewitt    John D. Carmack    Paul Dilascia

Whatristopher Isaac "Biz" Stone (born March 10, 1974) is a co-founder and Creative Director of Twitter, Inc and also helped to create and launch Xanga, Blogger, Odeo, and [http://obvious.com/ The Obvious Corporation], founded in June 2011 with his long-time collaborators Evan Williams and Jason Goldman to focus on building systems that help people work together to improve the world?
Biz Stone    Greg Skibiski    Robert Abbott (game designer)    Andy LoCascio

WhatMissouri) is an American computer scientist. He is most notable for leading the development of the X Window System from the project's inception in 1984 until the closure of the MIT X Consortium in 1996.   He lat?
Bob Scheifler    Peter Norton    Michael Hawley    John D. Carmack

What is a computer programmer, owner of Wholly Genes Software, and creator of The Master Genealogist, genealogy software?
Bob Velke    Death of Kevin Flanagan    Earl Isaac    Ken Schwaber

What is an American programmer. He is best known as the creator of LiveJournal and is the author of a variety of free software projects such as memcached and OpenID?
Brad Fitzpatrick    Richard Wallace (scientist)    Daniel Robbins    Matthew Haughey

What is an American computer programmer, best known as the author of the peer-to-peer (P2P) BitTorrent protocol, as well as the first file sharing program to use the protocol, also known as BitTorrent?
Bram Cohen    Michael Morrison (author)    Jim Kent    Corrinne Yu

What is an inventor and founder of several network technology companies whose well known products include PIX Firewall, the first stateful-inspection firewall and Cisco Systems first load-balancer, LocalDirector?
Brantley Coile    Christopher Abad    Biz Stone    Victor A. Vyssotsky

What is an American computer programmer and creator of the JavaScript scripting language?
Brendan Eich    Adam Leventhal (programmer)    Bob Scheifler    Daniel Kottke

What is the publisher and editor of The Perl Review, a magazine devoted to Perl and co-author of several books on Perl including Learning Perl and Intermediate Perl?
Brian d foy    Andy Hunt (author)    Steve Wood (entrepreneur)    R. Luke DuBois

What is an American computer programmer and designer. He works at Midway Games, and his completed designs include several of the most popular and influential pinball machines of the 1990s, including Attack From Mars, Medieval Madness?
Brian Eddy    Jim Hall (programmer)    Peter Samson    Lemuel Davis

What is an American computer programmer and website developer?
Bruce Ableson    Jim Highsmith    Scott Seebass    Jonathan Alexander

Whatware (later renamed Indie Built) in 1982.  It began by producing titles for 8-bit computers, including Beach-Head, Beach Head II: The Dictator Strikes Back, Raid over Moscow and many others?
Bruce Carver    Monte Davidoff    Marc Andreessen    Trung Dung

What is Board Chair of the International Society for Inconsistency Robustness. He has been a Visiting Professor at Stanford University and the University of Keio?
Carl Hewitt    Jim Highsmith    Bob Scheifler    Ron Jeffries

What is a Democratic member of the Fairfax County Board of Supervisors; representing the Hunter Mill district, which includes the town of Reston?
Cathy Hudgins    Steven McGeady    Mike Lesk    Dick Smith (software)

What is a Professor of Software Engineering at Florida Institute of Technology, and the Director of Florida Tech's Center for Software Testing Education & Research (CSTER) since 2004.  He is perhaps best known outside academia as an advocate of software usability and software testing?
Cem Kaner    Bram Cohen    Lemuel Davis    Daniel Robbins

What is the inventor of the Forth programming language?
Charles H. Moore    Randal L. Schwartz    David Ungar    Peter Norton

What is a Hungarian-American computer software executive who, as head of Microsoft's application software group, oversaw the creation of Microsoft's flagship Office suite of applications?
Charles Simonyi    Bob Scheifler    Mark Jason Dominus    Michael Holve

What is an American software developer, best known as the primary author of the LLVM project and related projects, such as the clang compiler?
Chris Lattner    Dick Smith (software)    Ken Schwaber    Mark Zuckerberg

Whatris Roberts (born May 27, 1968) is a video game designer, programmer, film producer and film director?
Chris Roberts (game developer)    Larry Kaplan    Bruce Ableson    Ho Thanh Viet

What is an American hacker, museum curator, artist, network engineer and programmer. He is best known for his qualitative analysis of specialization stratification in the underground economies related to computer crime?
Christopher Abad    Jon Phillips    Eric Haines    Steve Wozniak

What is a software developer, game programmer, entrepreneur, and the founder of Bethesda Softworks?
Christopher Weaver    Declan McCullagh    Declan McCullagh    Steve Wozniak

What is a writer and free software programmer who resides in Hillsboro, Oregon, United States. He is the author of Extreme Programming Pocket Guide, a co-author of Perl Testing: A Developer's Notebook, the lead author of Perl Hacks, and an uncredited contributor to The Art of Agile Development?
Chromatic (programmer)    Steven Snyder    Richard Green (technologist)    Jeff Raikes

Whatmission protocols popular for uploading and downloading files from dial-up bulletin board systems in the 1990s?
Chuck Forsberg    Alan Kotok    Biz Stone    Mark Davis (Unicode)

What is a programmer from Columbus, Ohio also known as the Dead Body Guy. He has gained fame playing dead people in film and television?
Chuck Lamb    Narendra Rocherolle    Cormac Kinney    Gordon Lyon

Whattis (born 1958 near  Salem, Illinois) is a United States computer programmer and ex employee of NASA and ExxonMobil, currently living in Northern California, who worked for Yang Enterprises (YEI) in Oviedo, Florida until February 2001. He is notable chiefly for making a series of whistleblower allegations about his former employer and about Republican Congressman Tom Feeney, including an allegation that in 2000, Feeney and Yang Enterprises requested Curtis's assistance in a scheme to steal votes by inserting fraudulent code into touch screen voting systems?
Clint Curtis    Gaurav Dhillon    David Maynard    Jack Dorsey

What is an entrepreneur and software designer. An inventor of Heatmaps, trading and risk management systems used by institutional traders, and a news analysis methods for quantitative securities trading?
Cormac Kinney    Michael Holve    Sol Katz    Jon Phillips

What is an American game programme?
Corrinne Yu    William Clinger (computer scientist)    David S. Miller    Mark Pilgrim (software developer)

What is a programmer and original author of the Apache Struts framework for building web applications?
Craig McClanahan    Alan Kay    Gordon Eubanks    Brian Eddy

What is a software developer, user interface designer, writer, and podcaster?
Dan Benjamin    Steven Snyder    Clint Curtis    Douglas Crockford

What is an American programmer, computer scientist, and an advocate of open source software?
Danese Cooper    Silas Warner    Brian Eddy    Jim Hall (programmer)

Whattist in the United States. He was a Professor of Computer Sciences at the City College of New York, and the author of over two dozen textbooks on computer programming?
Daniel D. McCracken    Ken Thompson    Victor A. Vyssotsky    Pito Salas

What is a pioneer of object-oriented computer programming and the principal architect, designer and implementor of five generations of Smalltalk environments?
Daniel Henry Holmes Ingalls, Jr.    Thomas Peterffy    Mark Pilgrim (software developer)    Jack Dorsey

What is a writer, software engineer, and musician. He is best known for his technology books, his work with progressive rock band Gentle Giant, and the imaginary computer game BLAZEMONGER?
Daniel J. Barrett    Greg Skibiski    Corrinne Yu    Ric Weiland

What is a U.S. computer engineer and one of the earliest employees of Apple Inc?
Daniel Kottke    Randal L. Schwartz    Peter Norton    Chris Roberts (game developer)

What is a computer programmer and consultant best known as the founder and former chief architect of the Gentoo Linux project?
Daniel Robbins    Bruce Ableson    Ian Murdock    Jean Sini

Whattist and programmer, with significant work in the Lisp environment?
Daniel Weinreb    Dick Smith (software)    Thomas Peterffy    Dominic Giampaolo

What is a computer programmer, technology consultant, and a well-known, award-winning author of over three dozen books and hundreds of magazine articles on computer-related topics?
Danny Goodman    Daniel Robbins    Steve Wood (entrepreneur)    Darin Adler

What Nightmare Comes True, Uninvited, and Shadowgate?
Darin Adler    Scott Seebass    Jon Schillaci    Ben Forta

What is an American software engineer, designer and developer of several operating systems including RSX-11M, VMS and VAXELN at Digital Equipment Corporation and Windows NT at Microsoft?
Dave Cutler    Death of Kevin Flanagan    David Korn (computer scientist)    Steve Wozniak

What is an American software developer employed by Apple Inc. (since July 15, 2002), where he is part of the development team responsible for the Safari web browser and WebKit framework?
Dave Hyatt    Qi Lu    William Clinger (computer scientist)    Lukas Biewald

What is an American UNIX programmer, who is probably best known for creating the Korn shell (ksh), a command line interface/programming language?
David Korn (computer scientist)    Brian Eddy    Bruce Ableson    Ward Christensen

What is a computer programmer and game programmer who has spent his career working at various companies in the San Francisco Bay Area?
David Maynard    Carl Hewitt    Cem Kaner    Danny Goodman

What is an American author, computer programmer, and pro-animal activist?
David Rolsky    Mark Allen (software developer)    Jeff Bonwick    Mark Davis (Unicode)

What is an American software developer working on the Linux kernel, where he is the primary maintainer of networking and the SPARC implementation, and is also involved in other development work?
David S. Miller    William Clinger (computer scientist)    Delon Dotson    Mike Lesk

Whattist, co-created the Self programming language with Randall Smith?
David Ungar    Patrick J. Hanratty    Daniel D. McCracken    John W. Eaton

WhatKevin Flanagan was a computer programmer who worked for The Bank of America in Concord, California, USA and committed suicide by gunshot in the parking lot of the business?
Death of Kevin Flanagan    Jeremy Sagan    Silas Warner    Warren Gish

What is an American journalist and columnist for CBSNews.com.  He specializes in computer security and privacy issues?
Declan McCullagh    Molly Holzschlag    Mark Jason Dominus    David Rolsky

What is an American software architect, philanthropist,  businessperson, and entrepreneur known as the co-creator of buzzd, FanBridge?
Deepen Shah    Alan Kay    Matthew Haughey    Daniel Robbins

What is a technologist and businessman who has worked in several businesses, including Netscape Communications and MP3.com?
Delon Dotson    Daniel Weinreb    Michael Sperberg-McQueen    Jeff Atwood

What is a Chicago, Illinois-based software engineer, computer consultant and a science fiction fanzine publisher?
Dick Smith (software)    Mike Lesk    Matthew Dillon    Grace Hopper

What is an American software developer. He initiated and maintains the DJGPP project, a port of the GNU C/C++ compiler and tools suite, targeted for PCs running MS-DOS or DOS terminals under Microsoft Windows?
DJ Delorie    John Draper    Marc Andreessen    Craig McClanahan

What is a software developer who helped develop the Be File System for the Be Operating System (BeOS) and currently works at Apple Inc?
Dominic Giampaolo    Chromatic (programmer)    Martin Roesch    Mark Davis (Unicode)

What is a computer scientist and Professor Emeritus at Stanford University?
Donald Knuth    Corrinne Yu    Wil Shipley    Dave Hyatt

WhatDouglas Andrew Bell (born February 24, 196?
Doug Bell    Cormac Kinney    Michael Morrison (author)    Joel McCormack

What is an advocate and creator of open-source search technology. He originated Lucene and, with Mike Cafarella, Nutch, both open-source search technology projects which are now managed through the Apache Software Foundation?
Doug Cutting    Michael Morrison (author)    Daniel Robbins    Mark Davis (Unicode)

What is a professor of computer science at State University of New York at Oswego, where he specializes in concurrent programming and the design of concurrent data structures?
Doug Lea    Ken Arnold    Bruce Carver    Doug Cutting

What is an American computer programmer and entrepreneur who is best known for his ongoing involvement in the development of the JavaScript language, for having popularized the data format JSON (JavaScript Object Notation), and for developing various JavaScript related tools such as JSLint and JSMin?
Douglas Crockford    Kingsley Uyi Idehen    Robby Garner    Gilad Bracha

WhatEarl Judson Isaac (7 August 1921 – 12 December 1983), along with friend Bill Fair, set up the company Fair Isaac in a small studio apartment on Lincoln Ave?
Earl Isaac    Tim Stryker    Benjamin Trott    Gilad Bracha

What is an ACM Fellow, an IEEE Fellow (since 2003), and an AT&T Fellow at Bell Labs for research in software metrics and testing as well as elected to the National Academy of Engineering?
Elaine Weyuker    Eric Sink    Brad Fitzpatrick    Jim Kent

What is the co-founder of FORTH, Inc. and is a leading expert in the Forth programming language?
Elizabeth Rather    Paul Allen    Steven McGeady    Jeremy Sagan

What is a noted computer scientist and educationist?
Elliot Koffman    Richard Stallman    Stu Moment    Ric Weiland

What is an American computer programmer who  developed sendmail and its precursor delivermail in the late 1970s and early 1980s at UC Berkeley?
Eric Allman    Darin Adler    John D. Carmack    Michael Scandizzo

What is an American software engineer, and is an expert in computer graphics, specifically image rendering?
Eric Haines    Joel McCormack    Ken Schwaber    LaFarr Stuart

What is a software developer and writer.  He is the author of  on the Business of Software (2006), a collection of essays from his blog and the "Business of Software" column for the Microsoft Developer Network?
Eric Sink    Sol Katz    David S. Miller    Stepan Pachikov

What is an American software developer and computer technical writer?
Erick Tejkowski    Otavio Good    John Draper    Trung Dung

What is a principal member of the technical staff at Sandia National Laboratories?
Ernest Friedman-Hill    Qi Lu    Eric Sink    Jawed Karim

Whattist and microcomputer entrepreneur who created the CP/M operating system and founded Digital Research, Inc?
Gary Kildall    Marc Andreessen    Mike Filsaime    Kelley Deal

What is an American computer programmer.  He majed in computer science at the University of Kansas, and works as a systems engineer on midrange and mainframe computers in Lawrence, Kansas?
Gary Martin (programmer)    Brendan Eich    Brendan Eich    Ross Cohen

What is the Chairman and CEO of SnapLogic, an enterprise application and data integration software development company that helps organizations connect business applications and Web services?
Gaurav Dhillon    Adele Goldstine    LaFarr Stuart    Jonathan Alexander

What is the creator of the Newspeak programming language, a software engineer at Google and a member of the Dart (programming language) team in Aarhus?
Gilad Bracha    Roger Powell (musician)    Ron Jeffries    Joshua Bloch

What is an American microcomputer industry pioneer who worked with Gary Kildall in the early days of Digital Research?
Gordon Eubanks    Bruce Carver    Jeremie Miller    Betty Holberton

Whathis pseudonym Fyodor Vaskovich) is a network security expert, open source programmer, writer, and a hacker?
Gordon Lyon    Randal L. Schwartz    Henry Burkhardt III    Peter Norton

Whattist and United States Navy Rear Admiral?
Grace Hopper    Monte Davidoff    Jeff Atwood    Patrick J. Hanratty

Whatbiski (born 1973), is an American entrepreneur.  Skibiski is the founder and former Chairman & CEO of Sense Networks, a New York City based company focused on analyzing big data from mobile phones and carrier networks?
Greg Skibiski    Tom Proulx    Angela Byron    Lemuel Davis

What is an American computer engineer and entrepreneur. He is known in the free software community due to his work on HAL, GNOME, Metacity, GConf, and D-BUS?
Havoc Pennington    Paul Buchheit    Michael Morrison (author)    Kelley Deal

What (1945–2000) was born in Ann Arbor, Michigan, USA, grew up in South Hadley, Massachusetts, and was schooled there?
Henry Burkhardt III    Jim Hall (programmer)    Danese Cooper    Larry McVoy

Whatware Co., California, USA in 1987 and was the first to develop software that eases use of Vietnamese language on computers?
Ho Thanh Viet    Jason Rohrer    LaFarr Stuart    Pito Salas

What is the founder of the Debian distribution and Progeny Linux Systems, a commercial Linux company?
Ian Murdock    Angela Byron    Brian d foy    Daniel Kottke

Whatware developer and entrepreneur?
Ilya Zhitomirskiy    Stu Moment    Michael Scandizzo    Richard Green (technologist)

What is an American entertainment law attorney and entrepreneur often referred to as the inventor of the Online music store?
Ivan J. Parron    Tom Proulx    Daniel Kottke    Tim Paterson

What is an American web developer and businessman widely known as the creator of Twitter and as the founder and CEO of Square, a mobile payments company?
Jack Dorsey    Cathy Hudgins    Michael Deering    Nick Gerakines

What is a retired United States Air Force veteran, game artist and game programmer?
James D. Sachs    Alistair Cockburn    Paul Haeberli    Richard Wallace (scientist)

What is a computer programmer, writer, musician, and game designer. He publishes most of his software under the GNU GPL or into the public domain, and charges for the iPhone ports of his games?
Jason Rohrer    Robert Fourer    Tom Proulx    Bob Velke

What is a German, Bangladeshi American internet entrepreneur. He is best known for being the  co-founder of the popular video sharing website YouTube?
Jawed Karim    Corrinne Yu    Ben Forta    Steven McGeady

What (December 27, 1924 – March 23, 201?
Jean Bartik    Mike Lesk    Michael Holve    Mark Jason Dominus

What is a San Francisco-based author, computer scientist, software executive and entrepreneur of French descent, noted for his active role in mobile computing standardization efforts, and profiled for his participation in the web 2.0 movement and ecosystem?
Jean Sini    Victor A. Vyssotsky    Greg Skibiski    Jeff Raikes

What is an American software developer, author, blogger, and entrepreneur. He is mainly known for the programming blog Coding Horror, and as the co-founder of the question-and-answer website Stack Overflow and the Stack Exchange Network?
Jeff Atwood    Donald Knuth    Justin Lewis (entrepreneur)    Gary Kildall

What is a software developer, most notable for leading the team that developed the ZFS file system?
Jeff Bonwick    Vern Paxson    James D. Sachs    David Ungar

What is a global information technology strategist and an author in the field of software development methodology?
Jeff De Luca    Pradeep Tapadiya    Betty Holberton    Elliot Koffman

What is the chief executive officer of the Bill & Melinda Gates Foundation?
Jeff Raikes    Samy Kamkar    Scott A. Jones    Nick Gerakines

What is one of the inventors of the Scrum software development process. Together with Ken Schwaber, he created Scrum as a formal process at OOPSLA'95. They have extended and enhanced Scrum at many software companies and IT organizations?
Jeff Sutherland    Vern Paxson    Phil Katz    Dan Benjamin

What is an American entrepreneur, computer scientist and software developer?
Jeff Wellemeyer    Richard Wallace (scientist)    Richard Brodie (programmer)    Ian Murdock

What is an American technology entrepreneur and Arizona millionaire who is considered to be the pioneer of hispanic Internet in the United States?
Jeffrey Peterson    Scott Meyers    Nathaniel Borenstein    Stu Moment

What is the inventor of Jabber/XMPP technologies and was the primary developer of jabberd 1.0, the first XMPP server?
Jeremie Miller    Paul Allen    Matthew Haughey    David Ungar

What is an American computer programmer. He is the founder of Sagan Technology and author of Metro: an audio, MIDI and video sequencer for Apple Macintosh computers?
Jeremy Sagan    Jeremy Sagan    Daniel J. Barrett    John D. Carmack

What is an American computer programmer at Alcatel-Lucent Bell Labs, USA. Until January 2009, he was the Vice President of Software at the One Laptop per Child project, working on the software for the OLPC XO-1. He is one of the original developers of the X Window System at MIT and worked on it again with X.Org, where he served on the board of directors?
Jim Gettys    Samy Kamkar    Gaurav Dhillon    Jeremie Miller

What is a computer programmer and advocate of free software, best known for his work on FreeDOS?
Jim Hall (programmer)    Lois Haibt    Virgil Griffith    Dominic Giampaolo

What is an American software engineer and author of books in the field of software development methodology?
Jim Highsmith    Erick Tejkowski    Mark Zuckerberg    Mike Filsaime

What is an American research scientist and computer programmer?
Jim Kent    Larry Kaplan    Clint Curtis    Dave Cutler

What is a software programmer who is best known for his work on the Firefox web browser and related software development tools like Firebug and DOM Inspector?
Joe Hewitt (programmer)    Jeff Raikes    David Rolsky    Michael Holve

What is the designer of the NCR Corporation version of the p-code machine which is a kind of Stack machine popular in the 1970s as the preferred way to implement new computing architectures and languages such as Pascal and BCPL?
Joel McCormack    Jim Hall (programmer)    Victor A. Vyssotsky    Bill Gates

What is a software engineer and writer. He is the author of Joel on Software, a blog on software development?
Joel Spolsky    Ho Thanh Viet    Darin Adler    Doug Cutting

What is an American game programmer and the co-founder of id Software?
John D. Carmack    Monte Davidoff    Shawn Fanning    Scott Werndorfer

What is an American computer programmer and former phone phreak?
John Draper    Daniel Kottke    Bill Joy    Michael J. Karels

What is a computer scientist, director and entrepreneu?
John Mashey    Jon Schillaci    Kevin Systrom    Shawn Fanning

Whatdisambiguation?
John W. Eaton    Bill Joy    Joel McCormack    Clint Curtis

What is an American computer scientist best known as the co-founder with Charles Geschke of Adobe Systems Inc., the graphics and publishing software company?
John Warnock    Qi Lu    Steven McGeady    Nick Gerakines

What is considered a founding father of the web browse?
Jon Mittelhauser    Scott Meyers    David Maynard    Stepan Pachikov

What is an open source developer, artist, designer, writer, educator, lecturer, and curator with 12+ years of experience creating communities and working within computing culture?
Jon Phillips    Jason Rohrer    Lukas Biewald    Bram Cohen

What is an American sex offender and a former fugitive who was added to the FBI's Top Ten Most Wanted Fugitives list on September 7, 2007.  Schillaci is the 488th fugitive to be placed on the list?
Jon Schillaci    Jon Mittelhauser    Daniel Weinreb    Lukas Biewald

Whatsohn (; born about the beginning of the 19th century, Grätz in Posen (), then Germany - November 24, 1869, Altofen, Kingdom of Hungary, Austrian Empire) was a German-Hungarian rabbi?
Jonathan Alexander    Charles H. Moore    Jawed Karim    Jeff Raikes

What is an American Internet entrepreneur and designer best known as the founder of [http://www.thebackplane.com Backplane] and Cortex?
Joseph Primiani    David Korn (computer scientist)    David S. Miller    Mitchell Waite

What is a software engineer, formerly employed at Google, and a technology author?
Joshua Bloch    Chuck Lamb    Ben Chiu    Wayne Bell (computer specialist)

Whatwis is a software designer and entrepreneur, and one of the founders of NationalField, a software company that makes private social networks?
Justin Lewis (entrepreneur)    Chuck Lamb    Cem Kaner    Jim Kent

What is an American musician. The identical twin sister of Kim Deal, she is the lead guitarist of The Breeders, besides having a solo career?
Kelley Deal    Leonard Adleman    Gilad Bracha    Scott Seebass

What is an American computer programmer well known as one of the developers of the 1980s dungeon-crawling video game Rogue, for his contributions to the original Berkeley (BSD) distribution of Unix, for his books and articles about C and C++ (e.g?
Ken Arnold    Mark Harris (programmer)    Robert Tappan Morris    Bill Gates

What is a software developer, product manager and industry consultant.  Ken worked with Jeff Sutherland to formulate the initial versions of the Scrum development process and to present Scrum as a formal process at OOPSLA'95. They have extended and enhanced Scrum at many software companies and IT organizations?
Ken Schwaber    Richard Wallace (scientist)    Joe Hewitt (programmer)    Molly Holzschlag

What is an American pioneer of computer science?
Ken Thompson    Andy LoCascio    Michael J. Karels    Ernest Friedman-Hill

What is an American entrepreneur and software engineer best known as the co‑founder and CEO of Instagram?
Kevin Systrom    Trung Dung    Lukas Biewald    Monte Davidoff

What is Founder, President, and CEO of OpenLink Software, a privately held company founded in 1992.  Born in Manchester, England in 1965, of Nigerian heritage, Idehen was raised in both Great Britain and Nigeria?
Kingsley Uyi Idehen    Chuck Lamb    Wayne Bell (computer specialist)    Mark Pilgrim (software developer)

What (born July 6, 1934 in Clarkston, Utah), now retired, was an early computer music pioneer, computer engineer and member of the Homebrew Computer Club?
LaFarr Stuart    Clint Curtis    Chuck Lamb    Matthew Dillon

What is an American video game designer and programmer. He initially worked at Atari and was responsible for a lot of their sales?
Larry Kaplan    David Ungar    Ben Forta    Michael Holve

What is the CEO of BitMover, the company that makes BitKeeper, a version control system that was used from February 2002 to early 2005 to manage the source code of the Linux kernel?
Larry McVoy    Daniel Kottke    David Ungar    Dominic Giampaolo

What is a computer programmer and author, most widely known for his creation of the Perl programming language in 198?
Larry Wall    Chuck Lamb    Steve Wood (entrepreneur)    Jawed Karim

Whatvis (born 1953 in Mississippi)  is an American software enginee?
Lemuel Davis    Daniel D. McCracken    Lemuel Davis    Peter Samson

What is an American theoretical computer scientist and professor of computer science and molecular biology at the University of Southern California?
Leonard Adleman    Daniel Weinreb    Deepen Shah    Silas Warner

What is a Hungarian-American engineer and manager, one of the founding members of Intel Corporation?
Leslie L. Vadász    Alan Kotok    Richard Green (technologist)    Randal L. Schwartz

What is an American computer scientist, and is perhaps most famous for being a member of the ten-person team at IBM that developed FORTRAN, the first successful high level programming language?
Lois Haibt    Andrew C. Stone    Nick Gerakines    Paul Haeberli

What is an American attorney, and Deputy General Counsel at the Wikimedia Foundation. Previously he was an attorney at Greenberg Traurig and Mozilla, where he worked on the revision of the Mozilla Public License (MPL)?
Luis Villa    Steve Wood (entrepreneur)    Bob Scheifler    Peter Norton

What is an entrepreneur living in San Francisco, California. Biewald is CEO of CrowdFlower (formerly Dolores Labs) — an Internet company that breaks large digital projects into small tasks and distributes them to workers around the world — which he co-founded in December 2007 with Chris Van Pelt?
Lukas Biewald    Bill Zeller    Donald Knuth    Michael Deering

What is an American entrepreneur, investor, software engineer, and multi-millionaire?
Marc Andreessen    William Barden, Jr.    William Clinger (computer scientist)    Bill Kendrick

What is a software engineer, game programmer and game designer. As a student at the University of California, San Diego, Allen used UCSD Pascal to develop a 6502 interpreter for the Pascal language in 1978, along with Richard Gleaves?
Mark Allen (software developer)    Eric Haines    William Barden, Jr.    Ward Christensen

Whatrispin (born July 19, 1956 in Camden, New Jersey; died December 28, 2012 in Poulsbo, Washington) is best known as the father of the IMAP protocol, having invented it in 1985 during his time at the Stanford Knowledge Systems Laboratory?
Mark Crispin    Rodnay Zaks    Douglas Crockford    Dominic Giampaolo

Whatvis (born ) is a co-founder of Unicode, Inc registered in the State of California, U.S.A?
Mark Davis (Unicode)    Dan Benjamin    Ho Thanh Viet    Ken Schwaber

Whatris is the Chief Technologist for GPU Computing at NVIDIA. He received a Ph.D. in 2003 from the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill?
Mark Harris (programmer)    Rich Skrenta    Mark Crispin    Larry Wall

What is the author of Higher-Order Perl: Transforming Programs with Programs which was published in 2005 by Morgan Kaufmann?
Mark Jason Dominus    Declan McCullagh    Ron Jeffries    Bill Gates

What is a graphics software engineer working at Nvidi?
Mark Kilgard    Leslie L. Vadász    O. Arthur Stiennon    Earl Isaac

What is a software developer, writer, and advocate of free software.  He authored a popular blog, and has written several books including Dive into Python, a guide to the Python programming language published under the GNU Free Documentation License?
Mark Pilgrim (software developer)    Robert Abbott (game designer)    Charles Simonyi    Chuck Forsberg

What is an American game programmer and the founder, principal technologist, and majority owner of Terminal Reality?
Mark Randel    Samy Kamkar    Charles H. Moore    Jim Hall (programmer)

What is an American computer programmer and Internet entrepreneur?
Mark Zuckerberg    Steve Wood (entrepreneur)    Gilad Bracha    Ward Christensen

What is responsible for the technical direction and product development efforts?
Martin Roesch    Steven Snyder    Brian Eddy    Ward Cunningham

What is a computer scientist living in Berkeley, California. He is best known for his contributions to FreeBSD and for starting the DragonFly BSD project?
Matthew Dillon    Mark Pilgrim (software developer)    Clint Curtis    Steve Wood (entrepreneur)

What is an American programmer, web designer, and  best known as the founder of the community weblog MetaFilter, where he is known as mathowie?
Matthew Haughey    Elliot Koffman    Scott Seebass    Leslie L. Vadász

What is a computer scientist, a former chief engineer for Sun Microsystems in Mountain View, California, and a widely recognized expert on artificial intelligence, computer vision, 3D graphics hardware/software, very-large-scale integration (VLSI) design and virtual reality?
Michael Deering    Richard Brodie (programmer)    Ilya Zhitomirskiy    Ward Christensen

What is an educator, artist and researcher working in the field of digital media?
Michael Hawley    Leslie L. Vadász    Robert Fourer    Ian Murdock

What is an American author, photographer, programmer and systems administrator?
Michael Holve    Daniel Kottke    Dave Cutler    Bill Zeller

WhatKarels is an American Software Engineer and one of the key people in history of BSD UNIX?
Michael J. Karels    Chris Roberts (game developer)    Mark Harris (programmer)    David S. Miller

Whatrison (born August 24, 1970) is an American author, software developer, and toy inventor?
Michael Morrison (author)    Michael Holve    John Draper    Lemuel Davis

What is the president and project lead of Castaway Entertainment, a company formed out of former Blizzard North employees in 2003. He is also responsible for programming on Diablo II and the development of the Battle.net game server network?
Michael Scandizzo    Eric Haines    Chuck Forsberg    Ron Jeffries

What is an American markup specialist. He was co-editor of the Extensible Markup Language (XML) 1.0 spec (1998), and chair of the XML Schema working group?
Michael Sperberg-McQueen    Steven McGeady    Joe Hewitt (programmer)    Ron Jeffries

What is an American author, software developer, personal coach, social media expert and business consultant who specializes in Internet Marketing?
Mike Filsaime    Joel Spolsky    Thomas Peterffy    Tom Van Vleck

What is a computer scientis?
Mike Lesk    Elizabeth Rather    DJ Delorie    David S. Miller

What is an American computer programmer and author of programming books. His first book "Projects in Sight, Sound and Sensation" was published in 1974. He did a physics degree at Sonoma State University during 1971–197?
Mitchell Waite    Lemuel Davis    Cem Kaner    Jawed Karim

What is a US author, lecturer and advocate for the Open Web. She has written or co-authored over 35 books on web design and open standards, including The Zen of CSS Design: Visual Enlightenment for the Web (co-authored with Dave Shea) and Transcending CSS: The Fine Art of Web Design with Andy Clarke?
Molly Holzschlag    Michael Scandizzo    Tom Van Vleck    Ward Christensen

What is an American computer programmer.  He graduated from Nicolet High School in Glendale, Wisconsin in 1974.  He went on to Harvard University, where he majored in applied mathematics, the department at Harvard that, at the time, included computer science?
Monte Davidoff    Joel Spolsky    Richard Stallman    Doug Lea

What is an American entrepreneur, designer, and software enginee?
Narendra Rocherolle    Ernest Friedman-Hill    Daniel Henry Holmes Ingalls, Jr.    Eric Haines

What is an American computer scientis?
Nathaniel Borenstein    Randal L. Schwartz    Mark Kilgard    Steve Wozniak

What is an American author, speaker  and software engineer. He is a contributor to a number of notable open source Erlang projects on GitHub and is the author of the book Facebook Application Developmen?
Nick Gerakines    Gordon Lyon    Paul Allen    Paul Dilascia

WhatWisconsin, November 9, 1919 - Madison, Wisconsin, January 10, 2003) was a clinical radiologist, inventor, radiation treatment pioneer, software and real estate developer in Madison, Wisconsin?
O. Arthur Stiennon    Monte Davidoff    Dave Cutler    Mark Kilgard

What is an American computer programmer and inventor. He is the founder and chief executive officer of Quest Visual Inc?
Otavio Good    Greg Skibiski    DJ Delorie    Adam Leventhal (programmer)

Whatware designer and programmer who pioneered computer operating systems in the 1950s?
Owen Mock    Barry Leiba    Jason Rohrer    Havoc Pennington

Whatware, best known for his creation of DOS-C, a DOS emulator written in the C language and subsequently adapted as the kernel of the FreeDOS operating system and a number of other projects including DOSEMU for Linux?
Pat Villani    Peter Norton    Dominic Giampaolo    Jim Highsmith

What is an American computer scientist and businessperson who is known as the "Father of CAD/CAM"—computer-aided design and computer-aided manufacturing?
Patrick J. Hanratty    Alan Kay    David S. Miller    Jon Schillaci

What is an American inventor, investor and philanthropist, best known as the co-founder, with Bill Gates, of Microsoft Corporation?
Paul Allen    Brian Eddy    Mark Randel    Bill Kendrick

What is an American computer programmer and entrepreneur. He was the creator and lead developer of Gmail?
Paul Buchheit    Michael J. Karels    Joel McCormack    Michael Morrison (author)

Whatware developer, author, web developer and programming journalist and one of the most celebrated columnists for MSDN?
Paul Dilascia    Dominic Giampaolo    Christopher Abad    Molly Holzschlag

What is an American computer graphics programmer and researche?
Paul Haeberli    David Ungar    Wendell Brown    Virgil Griffith

What is an American programmer, software publisher, author, and philanthropist?
Peter Norton    John D. Carmack    Brian d foy    Samuel Genensky

What is an American computer scientist, best known for creating pioneering computer software?
Peter Samson    Thomas Peterffy    Bram Cohen    Clint Curtis

WhatPhillip Walter Katz (November 3, 1962 – April 14, 2000) was a computer programmer best known as the co-creator of the ZIP file format for data compression, and the author of PKZIP, a program for creating zip files which ran under DOS?
Phil Katz    Craig McClanahan    Mark Jason Dominus    Andy Hunt (author)

What is a Curacaoan-American Cambridge, Massachusetts-based software developer. While working with the Lotus Advanced Technology Group in 1986,  invented a next-generation spreadsheet concept which was released by Lotus in 1989 as Lotus Improv?
Pito Salas    Mark Pilgrim (software developer)    Craig McClanahan    Scott A. Jones

Whatware development experience. He is the founder of Software Labs, a data migration/integration/management solution provider?
Pradeep Tapadiya    James D. Sachs    Mark Allen (software developer)    Jon Schillaci

Whatlish (pronounced "chee loo"), is currently an executive at Microsoft working on the Bing search engine?
Qi Lu    Larry Wall    Paul Buchheit    John Mashey

Whatois (born September 10, 1975, Morristown, New Jersey, United States) is an American composer, performer, conceptual new media artist, programmer, record producer and pedagogue based in New York City?
R. Luke DuBois    Ron Jeffries    Elliot Koffman    Vern Paxson

What is an American author, system administrator and programming consultant?
Randal L. Schwartz    Robert Fourer    Martin Roesch    William Barden, Jr.

Whatware pioneer and philanthropist?
Ric Weiland    Robert Abbott (game designer)    Narendra Rocherolle    Dave Cutler

What is a computer programmer and Silicon Valley entrepreneur who created the search engine blekko?
Rich Skrenta    Ben Chiu    Ilya Zhitomirskiy    Benjamin Trott

What is an American computer programmer and author. He was the original creator of Microsoft Word?
Richard Brodie (programmer)    Tim Paterson    Brad Fitzpatrick    Doug Cutting

WhatRichard L Green (born 1955) was Nokia's chief technology officer and an executive vice president from 2010 until 2011. In late 2012 he joined Enlighted as Senior Vice President of Products and Technology?
Richard Green (technologist)    Andy Kessler (author)    LaFarr Stuart    DJ Delorie

Whathis initials, RMS, is an American software freedom activist and computer programmer?
Richard Stallman    Joseph Primiani    Robert Tappan Morris    Chromatic (programmer)

What is the author of AIML and Botmaster of A.L.I.C.E. (Artificial Linguistic Internet Computer Entity)?
Richard Wallace (scientist)    Dick Smith (software)    Robert Iannucci    Mark Pilgrim (software developer)

What is a natural language programmer and software developer. He won the 1998 and 1999 Loebner Prize Contests with the program called Albert One?
Robby Garner    Jim Kent    John D. Carmack    Jeff Bonwick

What is an American game inventor, sometimes referred to by fans as "The Official Grand Old Man of Card Games"?
Robert Abbott (game designer)    Daniel Weinreb    David Maynard    Scott Werndorfer

What is a prominent scientist working in the area of operational research and management science?
Robert Fourer    Cem Kaner    O. Arthur Stiennon    Jean Sini

What is a computer scientist. His areas of expertise include multiprocessing and embedded systems?
Robert Iannucci    Clint Curtis    Jeff Atwood    Matthew Haughey

What is an American computer scientist, best known for creating the Morris Worm in 1988, considered the first computer worm on the Internet—and subsequently becoming the first person convicted under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act?
Robert Tappan Morris    Aaron Swartz    Michael Scandizzo    Jim Highsmith

Whatris) is a French-born American author of many books on computer programming, including the seminal Programming the Z80 and Programming the 6502. He is the founder of independent computer books publisher Sybex and was its president and CEO until it was bought out by John Wiley and Sons in May 200?
Rodnay Zaks    Scott A. Jones    Brad Fitzpatrick    Jack Dorsey

What is a musician, computer programmer and magazine columnist best known for his membership with the rock band Utopia?
Roger Powell (musician)    Tom Proulx    Brian Eddy    Daniel J. Barrett

What is one of the 3 founders of the Extreme Programming (XP) software development methodology circa 1996, along with Kent Beck and Ward Cunningham?
Ron Jeffries    Ward Cunningham    Monte Davidoff    Bill Joy

What is a computer programmer who worked for the Nevada Gaming Control Board in the early 1990s and was responsible for finding flaws and gaffes in software that runs computerized casino games?
Ronald Dale Harris    Ken Schwaber    Gaurav Dhillon    Andrew Koenig (programmer)

What is the cofounder of BitTorrent Inc along with brother Bram Cohen, where among other things he was involved in the Codeville project?
Ross Cohen    Daniel Weinreb    Andy Kessler (author)    Steven Snyder

What is an American computer programmer. He was a founding board member of the Open Source Initiative and briefly served as its president in 200?
Russ Nelson    Elaine Weyuker    Kelley Deal    John Warnock

Whattist, best known as an inventor for devices to assist sight-impaired persons?
Samuel Genensky    Douglas Crockford    Elliot Koffman    Cem Kaner

What is a security researcher, possibly best known for creating the Evercookie and the MySpace worm Samy (XSS), as well as his discovery that the Apple iPhone, Google Android and Microsoft Windows Phone mobile devices transmit GPS and Wi-Fi information to their parent companies?
Samy Kamkar    Ken Schwaber    Larry Wall    Jeff Sutherland

What is an American inventor. Scott graduated with honors from Indiana University in 1984, receiving a bachelor of science degree in computer science?
Scott A. Jones    Gilad Bracha    Stormy Peters    Michael Sperberg-McQueen

What is a corporate vice president in the Microsoft Developer Division. He is best known for his work on ASP.NET, which he and colleague Mark Anders developed while at Microsoft?
Scott Guthrie    Mark Zuckerberg    Paul Buchheit    Michael Scandizzo

What is an American author and software consultant, specializing in the C++ computer programming language?
Scott Meyers    Matthew Haughey    Andrew Koenig (programmer)    Silas Warner

Whathis career in the computer networking industry at the age of 20 when he co-authored the "Unix System Administration Handbook" with Evi Nemeth, Trent R?
Scott Seebass    Robert Abbott (game designer)    Michael J. Karels    Nathaniel Borenstein

What is the co-founder and head developer of Cerulean Studios, a company responsible for creating Trillian, a popular instant messaging client?
Scott Werndorfer    Pradeep Tapadiya    Eric Sink    Mike Filsaime

What is an American law professor.  Before his legal career, he created several widely used computer-software systems and wrote several widely cited books on computer programming?
Shawn Bayern    James D. Sachs    John W. Eaton    Richard Green (technologist)

What is an American computer programmer, serial entrepreneur, and angel investor?
Shawn Fanning    Erick Tejkowski    Michael Sperberg-McQueen    Sol Katz

Whatware?
Silas Warner    Ron Jeffries    Steven Snyder    Michael J. Karels

Whatware developer who pioneered geospatial computer software (a sub-category of GIS) and left behind a large body of work in the form of computer applications and format specifications while at the U.S?
Sol Katz    John Warnock    Scott Meyers    Silas Warner

What is the co-founder of ParaGraph Intl., Parascript, Evernote Corp?
Stepan Pachikov    Bruce Carver    Mike Lesk    Eric Sink

Whathis career, Warshall carried out research and development in operating systems, compiler design, language design, and operations research?
Stephen Warshall    Elizabeth Rather    Doug Bell    Joseph Primiani

What is an American technology-industry programmer, manager, and investor best known as an early Microsoft employee?
Steve Wood (entrepreneur)    Victor A. Vyssotsky    Larry Kaplan    Daniel D. McCracken

What is an American inventor, computer engineer and programmer who co-founded Apple Computer (now Apple Inc.) with Steve Jobs and Ronald Wayne?
Steve Wozniak    Joshua Bloch    Elaine Weyuker    Virgil Griffith

What is a former Intel executive best known as a witness in the Microsoft antitrust trial.  His notes contained colorful quotes by Microsoft executives threatening to "cut off Netscape's air supply" and Bill Gates' guess that "this anti-trust thing will blow over"?
Steven McGeady    Jack Dorsey    Stepan Pachikov    Elaine Weyuker

What is a notable figure in high technology management.  He was an early employee of Microsoft where he was Microsoft's first business unit general manager, leading the Development Tool Business?
Steven Snyder    Charles H. Moore    Jason Rohrer    Gordon Lyon

What is an information technology industry analyst and prominent free and open source software (FOSS) advocate, promoting business use of FOSS?
Stormy Peters    Dan Benjamin    Ken Schwaber    Craig McClanahan

What is a software developer and pilot.  Along with Bruce Artwick, he created the subLOGIC Corporation while he was at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign?
Stu Moment    Robert Tappan Morris    Steve Wood (entrepreneur)    Robert Tappan Morris

What is a Hungarian-born American entrepreneur. He is the founder and head of Interactive Brokers (Nasdaq: IBKR) and played a key role in founding the Boston Options Exchange?
Thomas Peterffy    Gary Kildall    Craig McClanahan    Stepan Pachikov

What is an American computer programmer, best known as the original author of MS-DOS, the most widely used personal computer operating system in the 1980s?
Tim Paterson    Kevin Systrom    Joseph Primiani    Aaron Boucher

Whatware package?
Tim Stryker    Adele Goldstine    Brian Eddy    Scott Seebass

What is a computer scientist dedicated to open source software.  In a 2000 survey he was listed as one of the top 10 contributors to an intended-to-be-representative sample of Open Source software, having contributed 0.782% of the code in the total sampled?
Tom Lane (computer scientist)    Rich Skrenta    John Warnock    Ernest Friedman-Hill

What is an American computer programmer and entrepreneur. He was a co-founder of Intuit and a pioneer of usability testing in the 1980s?
Tom Proulx    Justin Lewis (entrepreneur)    Joe Hewitt (programmer)    Gaurav Dhillon

What is an American computer software enginee?
Tom Van Vleck    Christopher Weaver    Robby Garner    Qi Lu

What is a Vietnamese-American businessman. His life story has been profiled in many leading publications including Forbes, Financial Times, The Wall Street Journal and San Francisco Chronicle, as well as in Dan Rather's book The American Dream?
Trung Dung    Jim Hall (programmer)    Scott Werndorfer    Chuck Lamb

What is a Professor of Computer Science at the University of California, Berkeley. He also works as an Internet researcher based at the International Computer Science Institute in Berkeley, California?
Vern Paxson    Roger Powell (musician)    Tom Lane (computer scientist)    Ric Weiland

What,  (February 26, 1931 - December 24, 2012 in Orleans, Massachusetts)   son of the astronomers Alexander N?
Victor A. Vyssotsky    Kingsley Uyi Idehen    Michael Scandizzo    Joel Spolsky

What is an American hacker, known for his involvement in a 2003 lawsuit with Blackboard Inc?
Virgil Griffith    DJ Delorie    Doug Bell    Doug Lea

WhatWisconsin, U.S., is the co-founder of the CBBS bulletin board, the first bulletin board system (BBS) ever brought online?
Ward Christensen    Mike Filsaime    Douglas Crockford    Ric Weiland

What is an American computer programmer who developed the first wiki?
Ward Cunningham    Jon Phillips    Ward Cunningham    Biz Stone

WhatGish is the owner of Advanced Biocomputing LLC.  He joined Washington University in St?
Warren Gish    Mark Randel    Ian Murdock    Andrew Fluegelman

WhatHis own BBS came to be named Amber, node 1 of the WWIVNet BBS network?
Wayne Bell (computer specialist)    Danese Cooper    Jon Schillaci    Cormac Kinney

What is an American entrepreneur. He is best known for founding Crashlytics that, in a little over a year, was acquired by Twitter for over $100 million in 2013, creating i2hub, a popular filesharing network, and his lawsuit against the Winklevoss brothers, famously depicted in The Social Network movie?
Wayne Chang    Bill Joy    Mark Davis (Unicode)    Greg Skibiski

What is an American computer scientist and entrepreneur best known for his innovations in Internet, entertainment, telecommunications, virtual workforce, and energy efficiency technologies?
Wendell Brown    Ward Cunningham    Mark Allen (software developer)    Tim Stryker

What is a Macintosh software developer, best known for co-founding and heading The Omni Group in 1991, where he did consulting work and developed software for the NeXTSTEP operating system, Rhapsody and later Mac OS X?
Wil Shipley    Adele Goldstine    Alistair Cockburn    Paul Buchheit

What is an author of books and articles on computer programming. Barden's writings mainly covered microcomputers, computer graphics and assembly language and BASIC programming?
William Barden, Jr.    Jean Bartik    Ernest Friedman-Hill    Alistair Cockburn

What is an Associate Professor in the College of Computer and Information Science at Northeastern University?
William Clinger (computer scientist)    Mark Pilgrim (software developer)    Jon Phillips    David S. Miller

