What is a logic puzzle game developed by Teyon for the Nintendo DSiWare. It is available in the Nintendo DSi Shop for 500 Nintendo DSi Points?
1001 Crystal Mazes Collection    The Hardest Logic Puzzle Ever    Keisuke (puzzle)    Category:Sudoku

What is a logic puzzle which on first inspection seems to have insufficient information to solve, but which rewards those who persist and examine the puzzle critically?
Ages of Three Children puzzle    Isolate (puzzle)    LITS    Numberlink

What is a binary-determination puzzle that was originally developed by Quadratic Games for the iPhone platform?
Atsumari (puzzle)    Atsumari (puzzle)    Survo puzzle    Tetsuya Miyamoto

What is a binary-determination logic puzzle published by Nikol?
Bag (puzzle)    Robot Rescue    Takuzu    Ripple Effect (puzzle)

Whatxist that are based on the balancing of similar-looking items, often coins, to determine which one is of a different value within a limited number of uses of the balance scales?
Balance puzzle    MindTrap    Nurikabe    Hashiwokakero

What is a logic puzzle based on the Battleship guessing game?
Battleship (puzzle)    Masyu    Zebra Puzzle    Wason selection task

What is a logic puzzle that deals with four people, a bridge and a torch?
Bridge and torch problem    Bulls and cows    God's algorithm    Fill-In (puzzle)

What is a logic puzzl?
Buchstabensalat (logic puzzle)    Atsumari (puzzle)    Killer sudoku    Sudoku

What is an old code-breaking paper and pencil game for two players, predating the similar commercially marketed board game Mastermind?
Bulls and cows    Battleship (puzzle)    Kakuro    Self-reference puzzle

What?
Category:Nonograms    Light Up    The Hardest Logic Puzzle Ever    Missing dollar riddle

What?
Category:Shunting puzzles    Tatebo-Yokobo    Lights Out (game)    LITS

WhatArticles relating to Sudoku, the logic-based placement puzzl?
Category:Sudoku    Wine/water mixing problem    God's algorithm    Keisuke (puzzle)

What is a single-player variation on the classic board game Clue, where a player is given a series of clues and must deduce where in the mansion each suspect should be and who is the killer?
Clue Suspects    Category:Nonograms    Keisuke (puzzle)    Shikaku

What is a logic puzzle by Nikol?
Country Road (puzzle)    Izukirudo    Slitherlink    KenKen

What is a puzzle similar to a crossword in structure, but with entries which consist of numbers rather than words, with individual digits being entered in the blank cells?
Cross-figure    Battleship (puzzle)    Super Swap    Four glasses puzzle

What is a game that incorporates the popular Japanese number slotting game Sudoku with crossword puzzles?
Crosswordoku    Kakuro    TuxMathScrabble    Shikaku

Whatdissection puzzle, also called a transformation puzzle or Richter Puzzle, is a tiling puzzle where a set of pieces can be assembled in different ways to produce two or more distinct geometric shapes?
Dissection puzzle    Light Up    Izukirudo    Slitherlink

What are a variation of the common crossword puzzle in which words, rather than clues, are given?
Fill-In (puzzle)    Lights Out (game)    Self-reference puzzle    Tetsuya Miyamoto

What is a type of logic puzzle published by many publishers.  Other published titles for the puzzle include Allied Occupation?
Fillomino    Inshi no heya    Tatebo-Yokobo    Yajisan-Kazusan

What is a logic puzzle first publicised by Martin Gardner in his "Mathematical Games" column in the February 1979 edition of Scientific American?
Four glasses puzzle    Inshi no heya    Hidato    Bulls and cows

What is a river crossing puzzle.  It dates back to at least the 9th century, and has entered the folklore of a number of ethnic groups?
Fox, goose and bag of beans puzzle    TuxMathScrabble    Missionaries and cannibals problem    Verbal arithmetic

What?
Futoshiki    Heyawake    Tatebo-Yokobo    Induction puzzles

What is a notion originating in discussions of ways to solve the Rubik's Cube puzzle, but which can also be applied to other combinatorial puzzles and mathematical games?
God's algorithm    Fill-In (puzzle)    Monkey and banana problem    KenKen

What is a binary-determination logic puzzl?
Goishi Hiroi    Theseus and the Minotaur    Knights and Knaves    Navigrid

What is a binary-determination logic puzzle published by Nikol?
Gokigen Naname    Futoshiki    Shinro    Logic puzzle

What is a type of logic puzzle published by Nikoli?
Hashiwokakero    Sudoku    Wine/water mixing problem    Nikoli

What is a computer strategy game that was included in Microsoft Windows. It is similar to the game Chip's Challenge?
Hero's Heart (Windows)    Missionaries and cannibals problem    Ripple Effect (puzzle)    Light Up

What is a binary-determination logic puzzle published by Nikoli?
Heyawake    Zebra Puzzle    1001 Crystal Mazes Collection    Logic puzzle

What is a logic puzzle game invented by Dr. Gyora Benedek, an Israeli mathematician?
Hidato    Tantrix    Kakuro    Str8ts

What is a type of logic puzzle published by Nikoli?
Hitori    Nonogram    Navigrid    KenKen

What is a binary-determination logic puzzle published by Nikol?
Hotaru Beam    Killer sudoku    Stained Glass (puzzle)    Buchstabensalat (logic puzzle)

What are logic puzzles which are solved via the application of the principle of induction?
Induction puzzles    Nonogram    Lasertank    Dissection puzzle

What is a type of logic puzzle published by Nikol?
Inshi no heya    Lights Out (game)    Str8ts    Verbal arithmetic

What is a logic-based line-placement puzzle. The puzzler is provided with a grid containing walls, dots and a set of area sizes?
Isolate (puzzle)    The Hardest Logic Puzzle Ever    Fill-In (puzzle)    Inshi no heya

What is a French logic puzzle and a word puzzle on grid created in 2006 and inspired by Picross?
Izukirudo    Hidato    Monkey and banana problem    Verbal arithmetic

What is a kind of logic puzzle that is often referred to as a mathematical transliteration of the crossword?
Kakuro    Clue Suspects    Futoshiki    Yajilin

Whateisuke is a logic puzzle published by Nikol?
Keisuke (puzzle)    Inshi no heya    Monkey and banana problem    THOG problem

What are trademarked names for a style of arithmetic and logic puzzle invented in 2004 by Japanese math teacher Tetsuya Miyamoto, who intends the puzzles to be an instruction-free method of training the brain?
KenKen    Isolate (puzzle)    Sudoku    Nonogram

What is a puzzle that combines elements of sudoku and kakuro?
Killer sudoku    Nonogram    TuxMathScrabble    Missing dollar riddle

What is a type of logic puzzl?
Knights and Knaves    Kuromasu    LITS    Lights Out (game)

What is a binary-determination logic puzzle published by Nikoli. As of 2005, one book consisting entirely of  puzzles has been published by Nikoli?
Kuromasu    Monkey and banana problem    Missionaries and cannibals problem    Wine/water mixing problem

What is a computer puzzle game requiring logical thinking to solve a variety of levels?
Lasertank    1001 Crystal Mazes Collection    Lights Out (game)    Ripple Effect (puzzle)

What is a binary-determination logic puzzle published by Nikoli?
Light Up    Mastermind (board game)    Navigrid    Hero's Heart (Windows)

What is an electronic game, released by Tiger Toys in 1995. The game consists of a 5 by 5 grid of lights?
Lights Out (game)    Hitori    Hidato    Fill-In (puzzle)

What is a binary determination puzzle published by Nikol?
LITS    River crossing puzzle    Robot Rescue    Logic maze

What are logic puzzles with all the aspects of a tour puzzle that fall outside of the scope of a typical maze?
Logic maze    Category:Shunting puzzles    River crossing puzzle    Kuromasu

What is a puzzle deriving from the mathematics field of deductio?
Logic puzzle    Missionaries and cannibals problem    River crossing puzzle    Country Road (puzzle)

What*Founded in 1983,  specializes in edutainment puzzle designs. All development and manufacturing procedures take place exclusively in Taiwan?
Lonpos    Super Swap    Hero's Heart (Windows)    Bag (puzzle)

What is a code-breaking game for two players. The modern game with pegs was invented in 1970 by Mordecai Meirowitz, an Israeli postmaster and telecommunications expert, but the game resembles an earlier pencil and paper game called Bulls and Cows that may date back a century or more?
Mastermind (board game)    Lonpos    Balance puzzle    Yajilin

What is a type of logic puzzle designed and published by Nikoli?
Masyu    Light Up    Zebra Puzzle    Lonpos

What is a series of lateral thinking puzzle games played by two individuals or teams. Invented in Canada, it is the main product of   Games, Inc., who license the game for manufacture by various companies including Outset Media, Blue Opal, the Great American Puzzle Factory, Pressman Toy Corporation, Spears Games and Winning Moves?
MindTrap    Nonogram    Atsumari (puzzle)    Heyawake

Whatmissing dollar riddle is a famous riddle that involves an informal fallac?
Missing dollar riddle    Lights Out (game)    Heyawake    Nonogram

Whatmissionaries and cannibals problem, and the closely related jealous husbands problem, are classic river-crossing problems?
Missionaries and cannibals problem    Keisuke (puzzle)    Hidato    Category:Nonograms

What is a famous toy problem in artificial intelligence, particularly in logic programming and planning?
Monkey and banana problem    Gokigen Naname    Nikoli    Nikoli

What is a puzzle stated by Douglas Hofstadter and found in Gödel, Escher, Bach. As stated, it is an example of a Post canonical system and can be reformulated as a string rewriting system?
MU puzzle    Robot Rescue    Atsumari (puzzle)    Gokigen Naname

What is a tiling puzzle proposed by philosopher Max Black in his book Critical Thinking (1946)?
Mutilated chessboard problem    Robot Rescue    Ripple Effect (puzzle)    Buchstabensalat (logic puzzle)

What is a logic-based number-placement puzzle. The puzzler is provided with a set of movements which must be used to move between the numbers 1 to 9 in order starting with the number 1. A solved grid will contain each of the numbers 1 to 9. The puzzle setter provides a partially completed grid?
Navigrid    Country Road (puzzle)    Mastermind (board game)    Goishi Hiroi

What is a Japanese publisher that specializes in games and, especially, logic puzzles?
Nikoli    Category:Sudoku    Theseus and the Minotaur    Super Swap

What are picture logic puzzles in which cells in a grid must be colored or left blank according to numbers at the side of the grid to reveal a hidden picture?
Nonogram    Hitori    Sudoku    Hashiwokakero

What is a type of logic puzzle involving finding paths to connect numbers in a gri?
Numberlink    Truel    Logic maze    Knights and Knaves

What is a binary determination puzzle named for an invisible wall in Japanese folklore that blocks roads and delays foot travel?
Nurikabe    Robot Rescue    Bridge and torch problem    Nikoli

Whatrisoners and hats puzzle is an induction puzzle (a kind of logic puzzle) that involves reasoning about the actions of other people, drawing in aspects of Game theory sometimes called the hierarchy of beliefs?
Prisoners and hats puzzle    Sudoku    Robot Rescue    Hero's Heart (Windows)

What is a logic puzzle published by Nikoli. As of 2007, two books consisting entirely of Ripple Effect puzzles have been published by Nikoli?
Ripple Effect (puzzle)    Train shunting puzzle    Four glasses puzzle    KenKen

What is a type of transport puzzle in which the object is to carry items from one river bank to another?
River crossing puzzle    The Hardest Logic Puzzle Ever    Shikaku    Izukirudo

What is a puzzle game developed by Teyon for the Nintendo DSi. It is available for download at the Nintendo DSi Shop for 200 Nintendo DSi Points?
Robot Rescue    Hotaru Beam    Heyawake    Bridge and torch problem

What is a type of logical puzzle where the question in the puzzle refers to the attributes of the puzzle itself?
Self-reference puzzle    Mastermind (board game)    Category:Nonograms    Goishi Hiroi

Whatcised as Divide by Squares or Divide by Box) is a logic puzzle published by Nikoli. As of 2011, two books consisting entirely of  puzzles has been published by Nikoli?
Shikaku    Str8ts    Tantrix    Izukirudo

What is a village in County Offaly, Ireland.  It lies at the junction of the R491 regional road between Cloughjordan and Roscrea where it is joined by the R492.  According to the 2006 census the population is 591 persons?
Shinro    THOG problem    Hidato    LITS

What is a logic puzzle developed by publisher Nikoli?
Slitherlink    Goishi Hiroi    Lonpos    Country Road (puzzle)

Whatis a type of transport puzzle, in which the player pushes boxes or crates around in a warehouse, trying to get them to storage locations?
Sokoban    Lonpos    Cross-figure    Lonpos

What is a binary determination logic puzzle published by Nikol?
Stained Glass (puzzle)    Inshi no heya    Lights Out (game)    Takuzu

What is a logic-based number-placement puzzle, invented by Jeff Widderich in 2008. It is distinct from, but shares some properties and rules with Sudoku?
Str8ts    River crossing puzzle    Missionaries and cannibals problem    Missing dollar riddle

What is a logic-based, combinatorial number-placement puzzle. The objective is to fill a 9×9 grid with digits so that each column, each row, and each of the nine 3×3 sub-grids that compose the grid (also called "boxes", "blocks", "regions", or "sub-squares") contains all of the digits from 1 to 9. The puzzle setter provides a partially completed grid, which typically has a unique solution?
Sudoku    1001 Crystal Mazes Collection    Truel    Induction puzzles

What is an action puzzle game developed by Teyon for the Nintendo DSiWare. It is available in the Nintendo DSi Shop for 500 Nintendo DSi Points?
Super Swap    Yajisan-Kazusan    Survo puzzle    Lights Out (game)

What is a kind of logic puzzle presented (in April 2006) and studied by Seppo Mustone?
Survo puzzle    River crossing puzzle    Hero's Heart (Windows)    Survo puzzle

What is a logic-based number placement puzzle. The objective is to fill a (usually 10×10) grid with 1s and 0s, where there is an equal number of 1s and 0s in each row and column and no more than two of either number adjacent to each other?
Takuzu    Theseus and the Minotaur    Super Swap    MU puzzle

What is a hexagonal tile-based abstract game invented by Mike McManaway from New Zealand.  Each of the 56 different tiles in the set contains three lines, going from one edge of the tile to another?
Tantrix    Shikaku    Super Swap    River crossing puzzle

What is a type of logic puzzle designed and published by Nikoli. The puzzle is based on Japanese tatami mats?
Tatamibari    Atsumari (puzzle)    Cross-figure    Ripple Effect (puzzle)

What is a binary determination logic puzzle published by Niko?
Tatebo-Yokobo    Balance puzzle    Takuzu    Stained Glass (puzzle)

Whatis a Japanese mathematics teacher who invented the numerical logic puzzle KenKen. (It is called Kashikoku-Naru-Puzzle in Japanese, which literally means "a puzzle that makes you smarter.?
Tetsuya Miyamoto    Clue Suspects    Mastermind (board game)    Fill-In (puzzle)

What is a logic puzzle invented by American philosopher and logician George Boolos and published in The Harvard Review of Philosophy in 1996. A translation in Italian was published earlier in the newspaper La Repubblica, under the title L'indovinello più difficile del mondo?
The Hardest Logic Puzzle Ever    Clue Suspects    Kakuro    Battleship (puzzle)

What is a type of logic maze designed by Robert Abbott. In this maze, the player acts as Theseus, the legendary king of Athens who is attempting to escape the Labyrinth?
Theseus and the Minotaur    THOG problem    Lonpos    God's algorithm

What is one of Peter Wason's logic puzzles, constructed to show some of the weaknesses in human thinking?
THOG problem    Missionaries and cannibals problem    Nurikabe    Shinro

What are a type of transport puzzle?
Train shunting puzzle    Mastermind (board game)    Mastermind (board game)    Dissection puzzle

What are logic puzzles created by Alan Fraser-Dackers for Trigon Puzzles Ltd and are published on their own website and by Dell Magazines?
Trigon puzzle    Truel    Sudoku    Ages of Three Children puzzle

What is a neologism for a duel among three opponents, in which players can fire at one another in an attempt to eliminate them while surviving themselves?
Truel    Trigon puzzle    Four glasses puzzle    Atsumari (puzzle)

What is a math version of the classic word game Scrabble (Trademark of Hasbro) which challenges kids to construct compound equations and to consider multiple abstract possibilities?
TuxMathScrabble    Ripple Effect (puzzle)    Izukirudo    Shinro

What is a type of mathematical game consisting of a mathematical equation among unknown numbers, whose digits are represented by letters?
Verbal arithmetic    Missionaries and cannibals problem    Super Swap    Isolate (puzzle)

What is a logic puzzle devised by Peter Cathcart Wason in 1966. It is one of the most famous tasks in the study of deductive reasoning?
Wason selection task    Tatamibari    Hitori    Hidato

WhatIn the wine/water mixing problem, one starts with two barrels, one holding wine and the other an equal volume of water?
Wine/water mixing problem    Clue Suspects    Numberlink    Stained Glass (puzzle)

What is a type of logic puzzle published by Nikoli.  It has been published in English under the name Arrow Ring, such as in the 2005 U.S?
Yajilin    Super Swap    Theseus and the Minotaur    Keisuke (puzzle)

What is a binary determination logic puzzle published by Niko?
Yajisan-Kazusan    Country Road (puzzle)    Tetsuya Miyamoto    Killer sudoku

What is a well-known logic puzzle. It is often called Einstein's Puzzle or Einstein's Riddle because it is said to have been invented by Albert Einstein as a boy; it is sometimes claimed that only 2% of the population can solve it?
Zebra Puzzle    KenKen    Super Swap    Str8ts

