What is the capital and the second largest city of the United Arab Emirates in terms of population and the largest of the seven member emirates of the United Arab Emirates?
Abu Dhabi    Zambian kwacha    Conakry    Bamako

What is the capital city of Nigeria. It is located in the centre of Nigeria, within the Federal Capital Territory (FCT)?
Abuja    Pound sterling    Euro    Rupiah

What is the capital and largest city of Ghana, with an estimated urban population of 2,291,352 .  is also the capital of the Greater  Region and of the  Metropolitan District, with which it is coterminous?
Accra    Czech koruna    Serbian dinar    Yamoussoukro 

Whatdis Abeba (the spelling used by the official Ethiopian Mapping Authority), is the capital city of Ethiopia?
Addis Ababa    Vatican City    Panama City    Conakry

What are two British-administered areas, constituting a British Overseas Territory, on the island of Cyprus administered as Sovereign Base Areas of the United Kingdom?
Akrotiri and Dhekelia      Yemeni rial    Coral Sea Islands    Euro

What is a permanent French scientific station on Île de la Possession (Possession Island) of the subantarctic Crozet Archipelago in the South Indian Ocean?
Alfred Faure     Bandar Seri Begawan    Pound sterling    Malagasy ariary

What is the capital and largest city of Algeria?
Algiers    Kuwaiti dinar    Baht    Prague

What is the capital of the Pacific Ocean island nation of Niue. With a population of 581 (census of 2006),  has the distinction of being the smallest national capital city in terms of population?
Alofi    Paramaribo    Saint Martin     Baku

What is an unincorporated territory of the United States located in the South Pacific Ocean, southeast of the Independent State of Samoa (formerly known as Western Samoa)?
American Samoa    Swiss franc    British West African pound    Niue

What is a Semitic language spoken in Ethiopia. It is the second-most spoken Semitic language in the world, after Arabic, and the official working language of the Federal Democratic Republic of Ethiopia. Thus, it has official status and is used nationwide.  is also the official or working language of several of the states within the federal system. It has been the working language of government, the military, and of the Ethiopian Orthodox Tewahedo Church throughout medieval and modern times. Outside Ethiopia,  is the language of some 2.7 million emigrants. It is written using  Fidel, ፊደል, which grew out of the Ge'ez abugida—called, in Ethiopian Semitic languages, ፊደል fidel ("alphabet", "letter", or "character") and አቡጊዳ abugida (from the first four Ethiopic letters, which gave rise to the modern linguistic term abugida?
Amharic    West African CFA franc    Peso    Tbilisi

What is the capital and largest city of Jordan. It is the country's political, cultural and commercial centre and one of the oldest continuously inhabited cities in the world?
Amman    Luanda    See respective claimants    Freetown

What is the largest city and the capital of the Netherlands. Its principal language is Dutch?
Amsterdam    Euro    Greenland    Romanian leu

What is the capital of the Principality of Andorra, and is located high in the east Pyrenees between France and Spain?
Andorra la Vella    South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands    Official language    Kralendijk

What is a minority language of São Tomé and Príncipe, spoken in the southernmost towns of São Tomé Island and sparsely along the coast?
Angolar    Singapore    Sri Jayawardenapura Kotte    Currency

What is a British overseas territory in the Caribbean. It is one of the most northerly of the Leeward Islands in the Lesser Antilles, lying east of Puerto Rico and the Virgin Islands and directly north of Saint Martin?
Anguilla    Alfred Faure     Brazzaville    Moldovan leu

Whathistorically known as Angora) is the capital of Turkey and the country's second largest city after Istanbul?
Ankara    Jordanian dinar    Ljubljana    Capital

What is the capital and largest city in Madagascar?
Antananarivo    West African CFA franc    Hargeisa    Martinique

What is the capital and the largest city of Samoa. The city is located on the central north coast of Upolu, Samoa's second largest island?
Apia    Aruba    Guernsey    Euro

What is a name applied to the descendants of the Classical  language of the 6th century AD?
Arabic    Name    Euro    Kenyan shilling

What is a name applied to the descendants of the Classical  language of the 6th century AD?
Arabic    Abu Dhabi    Sui generis collectivity     Central African CFA franc

What is a name applied to the descendants of the Classical  language of the 6th century AD?
Arabic    Budju    Dublin    Belgrade

What is a name applied to the descendants of the Classical  language of the 6th century AD?
Arabic    Beijing    Kralendijk    Tegucigalpa

What is a name applied to the descendants of the Classical  language of the 6th century AD?
Arabic    Syrian pound    Ottawa    Suva

What is a quantity that expresses the extent of a two-dimensional surface or shape, or planar lamina, in the plane?
area    Maseru    Dhaka    Bahraini dinar

What is the monetary unit of Armenia. It is subdivided into 100 luma (). The word "dram" translates into English as "money" and is cognate with the Greek drachma and the Arabic dirham?
Armenian dram    Asmara    Official language    Currency

What is a 33-kilometer-long (20 mi) island of the Lesser Antilles in the southern Caribbean Sea, located  north of the coast of Venezuela?
Aruba    Macanese pataca    Overseas collectivity of France    Official language

What is the capital and largest city of Turkmenistan, a country in Central Asia?
Ashgabat    Manila    Kingstown    Official language

What is the capital city and largest settlement in Eritrea?
Asmara    Khartoum    Alfred Faure     Euro

What is the country's second largest city (after Almaty, the former capital) with an officially estimated population of 775,800 as of 21 June 2012. It is located in the north portion of Kazakhstan, within Akmola Province, though administrated separately from the province as a federal city area?
Astana    French Polynesia    Khartoum    Johnston Atoll

Whatharevousa: Ἀθῆναι, Athinai; Ancient Greek: Ἀθῆναι, Athēnai) is the capital and largest city of Greece?
Athens    Akrotiri and Dhekelia      Pretoria     Ashgabat

What is the currency of the Commonwealth of Australia, including Christmas Island, Cocos (Keeling) Islands, and Norfolk Island, as well as the independent Pacific Island states of Kiribati, Nauru and Tuvalu?
Australian dollar    Euro    South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands    Saudi riyal

What is the currency of the Commonwealth of Australia, including Christmas Island, Cocos (Keeling) Islands, and Norfolk Island, as well as the independent Pacific Island states of Kiribati, Nauru and Tuvalu?
Australian dollar    Dili    Official language    Montserrat

What is the currency of the Commonwealth of Australia, including Christmas Island, Cocos (Keeling) Islands, and Norfolk Island, as well as the independent Pacific Island states of Kiribati, Nauru and Tuvalu?
Australian dollar    Boliviano    Tunisian dinar    Pakistani Rupee

What is the capital of the Republic of Iraq, as well as the coterminous  Province. The population of  as of 2011 is approximately 7,216,040, making it the largest city in Iraq, the second largest city in the Arab World (after Cairo, Egypt), and the second largest city in Western Asia (after Tehran, Iran)?
Baghdad    Ouguiya    Minsk    Somoni

What is the currency of Bahrain. It is divided into 1000 fils (فلس)?
Bahraini dinar    Euro    Kathmandu    Boliviano

What is the currency of Thailand. It is subdivided into 100 satang (). The issuance of currency is the responsibility of the Bank of Thailand?
Baht    Kuwait City    Yerevan    Pound sterling

What is an uninhabited atoll located just north of the equator in the central Pacific Ocean about  southwest of Honolulu?
Baker Island    Beijing    Bamako    Norwegian krone

What is the capital and largest city of Azerbaijan, as well as the largest city on the Caspian Sea and of the Caucasus region?
Baku    Saint Pierre and Miquelon    Liberian dollar    Islamabad

What is the capital and largest city of Mali, with a population of 1.8 million (2009 Census, provisional)?
Bamako    Mauritian rupee    Port of Spain    Dili

What is the capital and largest city of the Sultanate of Brunei?
Bandar Seri Begawan    Sarajevo    Pyongyang    Algiers

What is the capital and the most populous city of Thailand. It is known in Thai as Krung Thep Maha Nakhon (, pronounced ) or simply ?
Bangkok    Lari    Svalbard    Ugandan shilling

What is the capital of and the largest city in the Central African Republic. As of 2012 it had an estimated population of 734,350. Established by the French in 1889 as 'Bongai', which means 'rapids', it is the only capital in the world which is situated on a river that is an anagram of its name?
Bangui    Seoul    ChiÅŸinÄƒu    Kabul

What is the capital of the Gambia, and is in the division of the same name?
Banjul    Egyptian gineih    See respective claimants    Zagreb

What is the capital of the Federation of Saint Kitts and Nevis in the West Indies?
Basseterre    Overseas collectivity of France    Guernsey    Rome

What is the capital of the People's Republic of China and one of the most populous cities in the world?
Beijing    West African CFA franc    Surinamese dollar    The Bottom

What is the capital and largest city of Lebanon. As there has been no recent population census, the exact population is unknown; estimates in 2007 ranged from slightly more than 1 million to slightly less than 2 million?
Beirut    South African rand    Bissau    Name

What is the currency of Belarus. The symbol for the ruble is Br and the ISO 4217 code is BYR?
Belarusian ruble    Caracas    time    Kigali

What is the capital and largest city of Serbia. It is located at the confluence of the Sava and Danube rivers, where the Pannonian Plain meets the Balkans?
Belgrade    Peso    Tripoli    Official language

What is the capital city of Beliz?
Belmopan    Kampala    Mayotte    Funafuti

What is the capital city of Germany and one of the 16 states of Germany. With a population of 3.5 million people,  is Germany's largest city and is the second most populous city proper and the ninth most populous urban area in the European Union?
Berlin    Havana    Pound sterling    United States dollar

What is a British overseas territory in the North Atlantic Ocean, located off the east coast of the United States?
Bermuda    Euro    Euro    Capital

What is the Bundesstadt (federal city, de facto capital) of Switzerland, and, with (as of ) a population of , the fifth most populous city in Switzerland?
Bern    Ouguiya    Central African CFA franc    Papeete

What is subdivided into 100 chhertum (called chetrums on coins until 1979)?
Bhutanese ngultrum    Tokelau    Malabo    Cook Islands

What is a town in County Offaly, Ireland. It was formerly called Parsonstown, after the Parsons family who were local landowners and hereditary Earls of Rosse, and renamed at some time between 1891 and 1901. The town lies within a parish of the same name in the Roman Catholic Diocese of Killaloe?
Birr    Peso    Capital    Central African CFA franc

WhatPishpek and Frunze, is the capital and the largest city of Kyrgyzstan?
Bishkek    Pound sterling    Juba    population

What is the capital city of Guinea-.  The city's borders are conterminous with the  Autonomous Sector?
Bissau    Suva    Skopje    Niamey

What is the currency of Bolivia.  It is divided into 100 cents or centavos in Spanish?
Boliviano    Malagasy ariary    Pitcairn Islands    Namibian dollar

What is a Caribbean island that, with the uninhabited islet of Klein  nestled in its western crescent, forms a special municipality (officially public body) of the Netherlands?
Bonaire    Palikir    Niamey    Stockholm

What is the capital of Slovakia and, with a population of about 460,000, the country's largest city?
Bratislava    Moscow    Rupiah    Vientiane

What is the capital and largest city of the Republic of the Congo and is located on the Congo River?
Brazzaville    Doha    Guam    Ouguiya

What is the capital and largest city of the nation of Barbados?
Bridgetown    Australian dollar    Tehran    Baghdad

What is an overseas territory of the United Kingdom situated in the Indian Ocean halfway between Africa and Indonesia?
British Indian Ocean Territory    Astana    Guadeloupe    Arabic

What is a British overseas territory located in the Caribbean to the east of Puerto Rico?
British Virgin Islands    Navassa Island    Euro    Oslo

Whattish West African Pound was once the currency of British West Africa, a group of British colonies, protectorates and mandate territories?
British West African pound    CFA franc    Ukrainian hryvnia    Niamey

Whattish West African Pound was once the currency of British West Africa, a group of British colonies, protectorates and mandate territories?
British West African pound    French Polynesia    Lithuanian litas    Port Vila

What is normally abbreviated with the dollar sign $, or alternatively B$ to distinguish it from other dollar-dominated currencies, It is divided into 100 sen (Malay) or cents (English)?
Brunei dollar    Currency    Wellington    Lisbon

What is the capital of Belgium and the de facto capital of the European Union (EU)?
Brussels    Vaduz    Moscow    Pound sterling

What is the capital municipality, cultural, industrial, and financial centre of Romania. It is the largest city in Romania, located in the southeast of the country, at ,  lies on the banks of the Dâmbovița River, less than  north of the Danube?
Bucharest    Pyongyang    Taka    Alofi

What is the capital and the largest city of Hungary, the largest in East-Central Europe and the seventh largest in the European Union?
Budapest    Euro    North Korean won    Port Vila

What is a plant native to eastern Australia. Other names include Narrow-leaved Paperbark, Flax-leaved Paperbark and the Gadigal r?
Budju    Euro    Banjul    Kampala

What is the capital and largest city of Argentina, and the second-largest metropolitan area in South America, after Greater São Paulo?
Buenos Aires    Prague    Notes    British Virgin Islands

What is the capital and largest city and main port of Burundi and ships most of the country's chief export, coffee, as well as cotton, skins, and tin ore?
Bujumbura    Moldovan leu    Norwegian krone    Euro

What is the capital of Egypt and the largest city in the Arab world and Africa. Its metropolitan area is the 16th largest in the world?
Cairo    Birr    Ouguiya    Aruba

What ( or?
Canberra    Overseas collectivity of France    Djiboutian franc    Malagasy ariary

What is the currency of the Republic of Cape Verd?
Cape Verdean escudo    Vienna    Euro    Saba

What is the municipality enjoying primary status in a state, country, province, or other region as its seat of government?
Capital    Willemstad    Euro    Bissau

What is the municipality enjoying primary status in a state, country, province, or other region as its seat of government?
Capital    Bonaire    Euro    Serbian dinar

What is the municipality enjoying primary status in a state, country, province, or other region as its seat of government?
Capital    Liberian dollar    Euro    Seoul

What is the municipality enjoying primary status in a state, country, province, or other region as its seat of government?
Capital    Valletta    Euro    Algiers

What is the municipality enjoying primary status in a state, country, province, or other region as its seat of government?
Capital    Ashgabat    Pound sterling    Quito

What is the municipality enjoying primary status in a state, country, province, or other region as its seat of government?
Capital    Euro    East Jerusalem     CFA franc

What is the municipality enjoying primary status in a state, country, province, or other region as its seat of government?
Capital    Copenhagen    Liberian dollar    Euro

What is the capital and largest city of Venezuela; natives or residents are known as Caraquenians in English ()?
Caracas    Lesotho loti    Saudi riyal    Surinamese dollar

What is the capital city of Saint Lucia, a country in the Caribbean?
Castries    Kathmandu    Bonaire    Euro

What are a British Overseas Territory  located in the western Caribbean Sea. The territory comprises the three islands of Grand Cayman, Cayman Brac, and Little Cayman, located south of Cuba and northwest of Jamaica?
Cayman Islands    Jordanian dinar    Dublin    Euro

What is the currency of six independent states in central Africa, Cameroon, Central African Republic, Chad, Republic of the Congo, Equatorial Guinea and Gabon?
Central African CFA franc    Christmas Island    Santo Domingo    Montserrat

What is the currency of six independent states in central Africa, Cameroon, Central African Republic, Chad, Republic of the Congo, Equatorial Guinea and Gabon?
Central African CFA franc    Currency    French Polynesia    Euro

What is the currency of six independent states in central Africa, Cameroon, Central African Republic, Chad, Republic of the Congo, Equatorial Guinea and Gabon?
Central African CFA franc    Navassa Island    Central African CFA franc    Russian ruble

What is the currency of six independent states in central Africa, Cameroon, Central African Republic, Chad, Republic of the Congo, Equatorial Guinea and Gabon?
Central African CFA franc    Norwegian krone    Dili    Euro

What is the currency of six independent states in central Africa, Cameroon, Central African Republic, Chad, Republic of the Congo, Equatorial Guinea and Gabon?
Central African CFA franc    Euro    Nicosia    Euro

What is the name of two  currencies used in Africa which are guaranteed by the French treasury?
CFA franc    Doha    Asmara    US Dollar

What is the name of two  currencies used in Africa which are guaranteed by the French treasury?
CFA franc    Euro    Freetown    Yamoussoukro 

Whathistorically also known as Kishinev, from ) is the capital and largest city of Moldova. It is also its main industrial and commercial centre, and is located in the middle of the country, on the river Bîc?
ChiÅŸinÄƒu    Euro    Pound sterling    South Tarawa

What is a territory of Australia in the Indian Ocean. It has a population of 2,072 residents who live in a number of "settlement areas" on the northern tip of the island: Flying Fish Cove (also known as Kampong), Silver City, Poon Saan, and Drumsite?
Christmas Island    list_countries    Malabo    Maseru

What is an uninhabited  coral atoll in the eastern Pacific Ocean, south-west of Mexico, west of Costa Rica and 2420 km north-west of Galapagos Islands, Ecuador, at ?
Clipperton Island    Dinar    Paris    Central African CFA franc

What is the capital city of the Turks and Caicos Island?
Cockburn Town    Macedonian denar    Arabic    area

What is a territory of Australia, located in the Indian Ocean, southwest of Christmas Island and approximately midway between Australia and Sri Lanka?
Cocos     lthough myths and speculation about a Terra Australis     Praia    Martinique

What is the official currency of Comoros. It is nominally subdivided into 100 centimes, although no centime denominations have ever been issued?
Comorian franc    Kinshasa    Somaliland shilling    Guatemala City

What is the capital and largest city of Guinea.  is a port city on the Atlantic Ocean and serves as the economic, financial and cultural centre of Guinea with a 2009 population of 1,548,500. Originally situated on Tombo Island, one of the Îles de Los, it has since spread up the neighboring Kaloum Peninsula?
Conakry    Kuwait City    Pound sterling    Baku

What is the currency of the Democratic Republic of Congo. It is subdivided into 100 centime?
Congolese franc    Kampala    Nepalese rupee    Christmas Island

What is a parliamentary democracy in the South Pacific Ocean in free association with New Zealand?
Cook Islands    Yen    Bratislava    Capital

What is the capital of Denmark and its most populous city, with an urban population of 1,213,822 () and a metropolitan population of 1,950,522 ()?
Copenhagen    Monrovia    Cairo    Australian dollar

What islands and reefs in the Coral Sea, northeast of Queensland, Australia?
Coral Sea Islands    Funafuti    Bermuda    Ugandan shilling

Whathis is a list of sovereign states giving an overview of states around the world with information on the status and recognition of their sovereignty?
countries    Euro    Tirana    Australian dollar

Whatlish curraunt, meaning in circulation) in the most specific use of the word refers to money in any form when in actual use or circulation, as a medium of exchange, especially circulating paper money?
Currency    Pound sterling    r biogeographically as a synonym for either the Australasian ecozone     Sri Jayawardenapura Kotte

Whatlish curraunt, meaning in circulation) in the most specific use of the word refers to money in any form when in actual use or circulation, as a medium of exchange, especially circulating paper money?
Currency    Ringgit    Euro    Luanda

Whatlish curraunt, meaning in circulation) in the most specific use of the word refers to money in any form when in actual use or circulation, as a medium of exchange, especially circulating paper money?
Currency    Name    Birr    Cockburn Town

Whatlish curraunt, meaning in circulation) in the most specific use of the word refers to money in any form when in actual use or circulation, as a medium of exchange, especially circulating paper money?
Currency    Czech koruna    Standard Chinese    Tallero

Whatlish curraunt, meaning in circulation) in the most specific use of the word refers to money in any form when in actual use or circulation, as a medium of exchange, especially circulating paper money?
Currency    Rome    Somali shilling    Currency

Whatlish curraunt, meaning in circulation) in the most specific use of the word refers to money in any form when in actual use or circulation, as a medium of exchange, especially circulating paper money?
Currency    Moroccan dirham    Sui generis collectivity     Norwegian krone

Whatlish curraunt, meaning in circulation) in the most specific use of the word refers to money in any form when in actual use or circulation, as a medium of exchange, especially circulating paper money?
Currency    Tokelau    Taka    Bishkek

WhatThe  or Czech crown (sign: Kč; code: CZK) has been the currency of the Czech Republic since 8 February 1993 when, together with its Slovak counterpart, it replaced the Czechoslovak koruna at par?
Czech koruna    Norwegian krone    lthough myths and speculation about a Terra Australis     Hanoi

What is the capital and largest city of Senegal. It is located on the Cap-Vert Peninsula on the Atlantic coast and is the westernmost city on the African mainland?
Dakar    French Guiana    Peso    Martinique

What is the capital and the second largest city of Syria after Aleppo?
Damascus    Boliviano    Brussels    United States dollar

What is its mass per unit volume. The symbol most often used for  is ρ (the lower case Greek letter rho)?
density    Bonaire    Capital    South Sudanese pound

What is the capital of Bangladesh and the principal city of  Division?
Dhaka    languages    Port Vila    Baghdad

What is the capital, largest city, chief port and commercial center of East Timo?
Dili    Martinique    Peso    Hargeisa

What are known as the dinar or dena?
Dinar    Name    Sudanese pound    Lima

What is the currency of Djibouti. The ISO 4217 currency code is DJF. Historically it was subdivided into 100 centimes?
Djiboutian franc    Yerevan    Puerto Rico    Equatorial Guinean peseta

WhatDistrict, population 324,347 (2002 census), is the national capital of Tanzania, and the capital of the region?
Dodoma     Euro    Sarajevo    Euro

What is the capital city of the state of Qatar. Located on the coast of the Persian Gul?
Doha    South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands    Saipan    Dhaka

What is the capital and most populous city of Ireland?
Dublin    Euro    Jarvis Island    Amman

What is the capital and largest city of Tajikistan?
Dushanbe    various    Beijing    Damascus

Whator Eastern Jerusalem refer to the parts of Jerusalem captured and annexed by Jordan after the 1948 Arab-Israeli War  and then captured and annexed by Israel in the 1967 Six-Day War?
East Jerusalem     Kuwait City    Iraqi dinar    Notes

What is the currency of Egypt?
Egyptian gineih    Wellington    Kuala Lumpur     West African CFA franc

What is the capital of Akrotiri and Dhekelia, a British Overseas Territory on the island of Cyprus, administered as a Sovereign Base Area?
Episkopi Cantonment    Egyptian gineih    Bishkek    Ouguiya

Whatnish peseta at par and was replaced, at par, by the ekwele?
Equatorial Guinean peseta    Arabic    Euro    Beirut

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Cairo    Antananarivo    Budju

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Currency    Euro    Amman

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Nukunonu     Notes    Riga

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Basseterre    Arabic    Transnistrian ruble

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Central African CFA franc    Euro    Gibraltar

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Overseas collectivity of France    South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands    Romanian leu

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Singapore dollar    Malagasy ariary    Norfolk Island

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Sofia    Baghdad    Euro

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Riga    North Korean won    Honiara

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Madrid    Port Moresby    Norfolk Island

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    None    Dinar    London

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Currency    Overseas collectivity of France    r biogeographically as a synonym for either the Australasian ecozone 

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Beirut    Ashgabat    Beijing

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Abu Dhabi    Euro    Lari

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Macanese pataca    Funafuti    Gibraltar

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Pound sterling    Rupiah    Buenos Aires

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Niamey    Nepalese rupee    Euro

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Tokyo    countries    Saipan

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Lima    Falkland Islands pound    Wallis and Futuna

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Svalbard    Lisbon    Paramaribo

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Norwegian krone    Brazzaville    Turkish lira

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Brazzaville    Lima    Saba

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Jakarta    Vientiane    Norwegian krone

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Niamey    Mozambican metical    Rupiah

What is the currency used by the Institutions of the pean Union and is the official currency of the eurozone, which consists of 17 of the 27 member states of the pean Union: Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Portugal, Slovakia, Slovenia, and Spain?
Euro    Ottawa    Singapore dollar    Christmas Island

What are an archipelago located in the South Atlantic Ocean on the Patagonian Shelf?
Falkland Islands    Budju    Euro    Port Moresby

What is the currency of the Falkland Islands, a British Overseas Territory in the South Atlantic Ocean?
Falkland Islands pound    Ulaanbaatar    Amsterdam    Sudanese pound

What are an island group and archipelago under the sovereignty of the Kingdom of Denmark, situated between the Norwegian Sea and the North Atlantic Ocean, approximately halfway between Norway and Iceland?
Faroe Islands    Currency    time    Bermuda

What is the capital and largest city of Sierra Leone. It is a major port city in the Atlantic Ocean and is located in the Western Area of Sierra Leone?
Freetown    Euro    population    Anguilla

What is an overseas region of France on the North Atlantic coast of South America?
French Guiana    Phnom Penh    Riyadh    Euro

What is an overseas country (') of the French Republic. It is made up of several groups of Polynesian islands, the most famous island being Tahiti in the Society Islands group, which is also the most populous island and the seat of the capital of the territory (Papeetē)?
French Polynesia    Saipan    Currency    Nairobi

Whatsist o?
French Southern Territories    Iraqi dinar    Guatemala City    Capital

What is an atoll that forms the capital of the island nation of Tuvalu. It has a population of 4,492 (2002 Census), making it the most populated atoll in the country?
Funafuti    merica     Guadeloupe    Taka

Whatlish  ) is the capital and largest city of Botswana with a population of 231,626 based on the 2011 census, about 10% of the total population of Botswana?
Gaborone    Name    Euro    Sint Maarten

What is a British Overseas Territory located on the southern end of the Iberian Peninsula at the entrance of the Mediterranean?
Gibraltar    Martinique    Zambian kwacha    Angolar

What is the currency of Gibraltar. It is exchangeable with the British pound sterling at par value?
Gibraltar pound    Managua    Currency    Jerusalem

What is an autonomous country within the Kingdom of Denmark, located between the Arctic and Atlantic Oceans, east of the Canadian Arctic Archipelago?
Greenland    Nairobi    Euro    Amsterdam

What is a Caribbean island located in the Leeward Islands, in the Lesser Antilles, with a land area of 1,628 square kilometres (629 sq?
Guadeloupe    Currency    United States Virgin Islands    Kuwait City

What is an organized, unincorporated territory of the United States in the western Pacific Ocean?
Guam    Sri Jayawardenapura Kotte    Hargeisa    Currency

What is the capital and largest city of the Republic of Guatemala and Central America?
Guatemala City    Seychellois rupee    Seychellois rupee    Rupiah

What is a British Crown dependency in the English Channel off the coast of Normandy?
Guernsey    r biogeographically as a synonym for either the Australasian ecozone     Pitcairn Islands    Central African CFA franc

What is the currency of Guine?
Guinean franc    Euro    Somali shilling    Euro

Whattish Guiana) since 29 January 1839. Originally it was intended as a transitionary unit to facilitate the changeover from the Dutch guilder system of currency to the British pound sterling system?
Guyanese dollar    Central African CFA franc    density    Kenyan shilling

What is the capital of Vietnam and the country's second largest city. Its population in 2009 was estimated at 2.6 million for urban districts, 6.5 million for the metropolitan jurisdiction?
Hanoi    Ankara    New Taiwan dollar    Vatican City

What ?
Harare    Sri Lankan rupee    Freetown    population

What is the second-largest city in Somalia, located in the Woqooyi Galbeed region?
Hargeisa    Antananarivo    Pitcairn Islands    time

Whatnish: La Habana, ) is the capital city, province, major port, and leading commercial centre of Cuba?
Havana    Baku    Singapore    Lesotho loti

What is the capital and largest city of Finland. It is in the region of Uusimaa, located in southern Finland, on the shore of the Gulf of Finland, an arm of the Baltic Sea?
Helsinki    Nicosia    Boliviano    Kathmandu

Whatnistrative Region of the People's Republic of China, is a Special Administrative Region of the People's Republic of China?
Hong Kong    Euro    merica     Euro

What is the currency of Hong Kong. It is the eighth most traded currency in the world?
Hong Kong dollar    Birr    Montserrat    Yamoussoukro 

What is the capital city of the Solomon Islands, administered as a provincial town on the northwestern coast of Guadalcanal Island?
Honiara    US Dollar    Puerto Rico    Monrovia

What is an uninhabited coral island located just north of the equator in the central Pacific Ocean, about  southwest of Honolulu?
Howland Island    Belgrade    South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands    New Delhi

What is an artifact that depicts or records visual perception, for example a two-dimensional picture, that has a similar appearance to some subject–usually a physical object or a person, thus providing a depiction of it?
image    Norfolk Island    Coral Sea Islands    Capital

What is the official currency of the Republic of India. The issuance of the currency is controlled by the Reserve Bank of India?
Indian rupee    Paris    Euro    Windhoek

Whatdish: دینار) (sign: د.ع; code: IQD) is the currency of Iraq. It is issued by the Central Bank of Iraq and is subdivided into 1,000 fils (فلس), although inflation has rendered the fils obsolete?
Iraqi dinar    Willemstad    Melekeok    Port Moresby

What is the capital city of Pakistan and the ninth largest city in the country. Located within the  Capital Territory (ICT), the population of the city has grown from 100,000 in 1951 to 1.15 million as of 2011. The greater -Rawalpindi Metropolitan Area is the third largest conurbation in Pakistan with a population of over 4.5 million inhabitants?
Islamabad    Baghdad    image    Name

Whatwise known simply as Mann (, ), is a self-governing British Crown Dependency, located in the Irish Sea between the islands of Great Britain and Ireland within the British Isles?
Isle of Man    Pyongyang    Serbian dinar    Overseas collectivity of France

What is the capital and largest city of Indonesia?
Jakarta    Euro    Pound sterling    Zambian kwacha

What is an uninhabited 1.75 square mile (4.5 sq kilometer) coral island located in the South Pacific Ocean at , about halfway between Hawaii and the Cook Islands?
Jarvis Island    Euro    British Indian Ocean Territory    Name

Whatais: Jèrri [ʒɛri], officially the Bailiwick of  (), is a British Crown Dependency just off the coast of Normandy, France?
Jersey    Romanian leu    Abu Dhabi    East Jerusalem 

What (;  ' ;  '?
Jerusalem    Anguilla    Baghdad    Paramaribo

What is a  atoll in the North Pacific Ocean about  west of Hawaii. The atoll, which is located on the coral reef platform, comprises four islands?
Johnston Atoll    Kingstown    Banjul    Swiss franc

What is the currency of Jordan. The dinar is divided into 10 dirham, 100 qirsh (also called piastres) or 1000 fils?
Jordanian dinar    Hargeisa    Prague    Mamoudzou

What is the capital and largest city of the Republic of South Sudan. It also serves as the capital of Central Equatoria, the smallest of the ten states of South Sudan?
Juba    Belarusian ruble    Jersey    Lilangeni

Whathistorical contexts, is the capital and largest city of Afghanistan?
Kabul    Port Vila    Havana    Lima

What is the largest city and capital of Uganda. The city is divided into five boroughs that oversee local planning:  Central Division, Kawempe Division, Makindye Division, Nakawa Division and Lubaga Division?
Kampala    list_countries    Norwegian krone    Name

What is the capital and largest urban agglomerate of Nepal. The agglomerate consists of  Metropolitan City at its core, and its sister cities Patan, Kirtipur, Thimi, and Bhaktapur?
Kathmandu    Port of Spain    Cook Islands    British West African pound

What is the currency of Kenya. It is divisible into 100 cent?
Kenyan shilling    Port Moresby    Guernsey    Road Town

What is the capital and second largest city of the Republic of Sudan and of  State. It is located at the confluence of the White Nile flowing north from Lake Victoria and the Blue Nile flowing west from Ethiopia?
Khartoum    Euro    New Caledonia    Alofi

What is the capital and the largest city of Ukraine, located in the north central part of the country on the Dnieper River?
Kiev    Montevideo    Seychellois rupee    Paris

What is the capital and largest city of Rwanda. It is situated near the geographic centre of the nation?
Kigali    Andorra la Vella    Sui generis collectivity     Coral Sea Islands

What is a largely submerged, uninhabited triangular shaped reef,  east-west and  north-south, located in the North Pacific Ocean, roughly half way between the Hawaiian Islands and American Samoa at ?
Kingman Reef    Tirana    Oslo    Dakar

What is the capital, chief port, and main commercial centre of Saint Vincent and the Grenadines. With a population of 25,418 (2005),  is the most populous as well as the largest settlement by area in Saint Vincent and the Grenadines?
Kingstown    Euro    Maseru    Kinshasa

What is the capital and the largest city of the Democratic Republic of the Congo?
Kinshasa    Standard Chinese    Panama City    Ouguiya

What is the capital city and main port of the island of Bonaire in the Caribbean Netherlands?
Kralendijk    Athens    Nukunonu     Hargeisa

What is the federal capital and most populous city in Malaysia. The city covers an area of  and has an estimated population of 1.6 million as of 2012. Greater Kuala Lumpur, also known as the Klang Valley, is an urban agglomeration of 7.2 million?
Kuala Lumpur     CFA franc    Niue    Euro

What is the capital of Kuwait. It has a population of 2.38 million in the metropolitan area?
Kuwait City    Maldivian rufiyaa    Skopje    Madrid

What is the currency of Kuwait. It is sub-divided into 1,000 fils?
Kuwaiti dinar    Zagreb    Arabic    Russian ruble

What is the currency of Burma (Myanmar). It is often abbreviated as "K" (singular or plural) or "Ks" (plural), which is placed before or after the numerical value, depending on author preference?
Kyat    Bridgetown    Euro    Peso

What is the human capacity for acquiring and using complex systems of communication, and a language is any specific example of such a system?
languages    Ulaanbaatar    British Virgin Islands    London

What is the part of the order Charadriiformes which includes the gulls, terns, skuas and skimmers, with the waders and snipes making up the rest of the order?
Lari    Sudanese pound    Somaliland shilling    Ulaanbaatar

What is the currency unit of Lebanon?
Lebanese pound    Somoni    Bahraini dinar    Monrovia

What is the currency of the Kingdom of Lesotho. It is subdivided into 100 lisente (sg?
Lesotho loti    Currency    Sofia    Pound sterling

What is normally abbreviated with the dollar sign $, or alternatively L$ or LD$ to distinguish it from other dollar-denominated currencies?
Liberian dollar    Copenhagen    Central African CFA franc    Bangui

What is the capital and largest city of Gabon, in west central Africa. The city is a port on the Komo River, near the Gulf of Guinea, and a trade center for a timber region?
Libreville    Bridgetown    Swiss franc    Mayotte

What is the currency of Swaziland and is subdivided into 100 cents?
Lilangeni    Libreville    Official language    Prague

What is the capital and largest city of Malawi. The city is located in the central region of Malawi, near the borders with Mozambique and Zambia?
Lilongwe    Guatemala City    Belgrade    Yamoussoukro 

What is the capital and the largest city of Peru. It is located in the valleys of the Chillón, Rímac and Lurín rivers, in the central coastal  part of the country, in a valley on a prevalent desert coast overlooking the Pacific Ocean?
Lima    Palikir    Arabic    Yamoussoukro 

What is the capital city and largest city of Portugal with a population of 547,631 within its administrative limits on a land area of ?
Lisbon    Caracas    Angolar    Singapore dollar

What is the currency of Lithuania?
Lithuanian litas    Kuala Lumpur     Rome    Falkland Islands pound

What is the capital and largest city of Slovenia and its only centre of international importance?
Ljubljana    Minsk    Gibraltar pound    Hong Kong dollar

What is the capital city of England and the United Kingdom, and the largest city, urban zone and metropolitan area in the United Kingdom, and the European Union by most measures?
London    Vilnius    Yerevan    Svalbard

What is the capital and largest city of Angola, in Southern Africa?
Luanda    Praia    Currency    Monrovia

What is the capital and largest city of Zambia. One of the fastest-developing cities in Southern Africa,  is located in the southern part of the central plateau at an elevation of about 1,300 metres (4,265 feet)?
Lusaka    Somoni    Vientiane    Saudi riyal

What is the currency of Macau. It is subdivided into 100 avos (Cantonese: 仙; sin), with 10 avos called ho (毫) in Cantonese?
Macanese pataca    New Caledonia    Euro    Northern Mariana Islands

What is one of the two special administrative regions of the People's Republic of China (PRC), the other being Hong Kong?
Macau    Jarvis Island    Suva    Capital

What is 807) is the currency of the Republic of Macedonia?
Macedonian denar    Currency    Oslo    Ouguiya

What is the capital and largest city of Spain. The population of the city is roughly 3.3 million and the entire population of the  metropolitan area is calculated to be around 6.5 million?
Madrid    Wellington    Mogadishu    Anguilla

What is a large coral atoll of 64 islands in the Pacific Ocean, and forms a legislative district of the Ratak Chain of the Marshall Islands?
Majuro    Macau    Capital    Russian ruble

What is the capital of Equatorial Guinea, located on the northern coast of Bioko Island (formerly Fernando Pó) on the rim of a sunken volcano?
Malabo    US Dollar    Nukunonu     Arabic

What is the currency of Madagascar. It is subdivided into 5 iraimbilanja and is one of only two non-decimal currencies currently circulating (the other is the Mauritanian ouguiya)?
Malagasy ariary    r biogeographically as a synonym for either the Australasian ecozone     Sarajevo    area

What is the currency of the Maldives. Determining the rate for the US Dollar and the issuance of the currency is controlled by the Maldives Monetary Authority (MMA)?
Maldivian rufiyaa    Hargeisa    Overseas collectivity of France    South African rand

What is the capital of the French overseas region and department of Mayotte, in the Indian Ocean?
Mamoudzou    Peso    Capital    Tallero

What is the capital city of  Nicaragua as well as the department and municipality by the same name?
Managua    Overseas collectivity of France    Praia    Iraqi dinar

What is the capital and largest city of Bahrain, with an approximate population of 155,000 people?
Manama    Capital    Mexico City    Bucharest

What are large, fully aquatic, mostly herbivorous marine mammals sometimes known as sea cows?
Manat     Cayman Islands    Bahraini dinar    Ringgit

Whatlish: ; , ) is the capital city of the Philippines. It is one of the sixteen cities (along with the municipality of Pateros) that comprise the national capital region called Metro ?
Manila    Gibraltar pound    Rupiah    Capital

What is the capital and largest city of Mozambique. It is known as the City of Acacias in reference to acacia trees commonly found along its avenues and the Pearl of the Indian Ocean?
Maputo    Nuevo sol    Cocos     Belarusian ruble

What is an island in the Lesser Antilles in the eastern Caribbean Sea, with a land area of . Like Guadeloupe, it is an overseas region of France, consisting of a single overseas department?
Martinique    Overseas collectivity of France    Name    Singapore

What is the capital of Lesotho. It is also the capital of the  District. Located on the Caledon River,  lies directly on the Lesotho-South Africa border?
Maseru    Gibraltar pound    Kralendijk    Somaliland shilling

What is the currency of Mauritiu?
Mauritian rupee    Bamako    Sarajevo    Nepalese rupee

What is an overseas department and region of France consisting of a main island, Grande-Terre (or Maore), a smaller island, Petite-Terre (or Pamanzi), and several islets around these two?
Mayotte    Malabo    Baghdad    Bujumbura

What is the capital and second largest city in Swaziland?
Mbabane     Pula    Comorian franc    None

What is a state of the Republic of Palau located on the central east coast of Babeldaob Island. The new capital of the Republic of Palau, Ngerulmud, is also located in this state?
Melekeok    Saudi riyal    Port of Spain    Palmyra Atoll

What is a genus of sea snails, marine gastropod mollusks in the family Cancellariidae, the nutmeg snails?
merica     Euro    Montevideo    Ugandan shilling

What is the Federal District (Distrito Federal), capital of Mexico and seat of the federal powers of the Mexican Union?
Mexico City    Dili    San Salvador    Addis Ababa

What (; also called Midway Island and Midway Islands; Hawaiian: Pihemanu Kauihelan?
Midway Atoll    Tallinn    Euro    Bangui

What is the capital and largest city of Belarus, situated on the Svislach and Niamiha rivers?
Minsk    Amharic    Nairobi    Swiss franc

What is the largest city in Somalia and the nation's capital?
Mogadishu    Tallinn    Bermuda    Nairobi

What is the currency of Moldova. Like the Romanian leu, the  (pl. lei) is subdivided into 100 bani (singular: ban)?
Moldovan leu    various    Podgorica    Baku

What is a sovereign city-state, located on the French Riviera in Western Europe?
Monaco    American Samoa    Euro    Pound sterling

What is the capital city of the West African nation of Liberia. Located on the Atlantic Coast at Cape Mesurado, it lies geographically within Montserrado County, but is administered separately?
Monrovia    Armenian dram    Name    US Dollar

What is the largest city, the capital, and the chief port of Uruguay. The settlement was established in 1726 by Bruno Mauricio de Zabala, as a strategic move amidst a Spanish-Portuguese dispute over the platine region, and as a counter to the Portuguese colony at Colonia del Sacramento?
Montevideo    Seychellois rupee    Oslo    Liberian dollar

What is a Caribbean island that is a British Overseas Territory. It is located in the Leeward Islands, part of the chain of islands known as the Lesser Antilles, in the West Indies?
Montserrat    Yemeni rial    Kingstown    Sukhumi

What is the currency of Morocco. The plural form is pronounced darahim, although in French and English "dirhams" is commonly used?
Moroccan dirham    British Indian Ocean Territory    Montserrat    Arabic

What is the capital city and the most populous federal subject of Russia. The city is a major political, economic, cultural and scientific center in Russia and in Europe?
Moscow    list_countries    Falkland Islands pound    Official language

Whatais) is the currency  of Mozambique, abbreviated with the symbol MZN or MTn?
Mozambican metical    Capital    Jarvis Island    Saudi riyal

What is the currency of Nigeria. It is subdivided into 100 kob?
Naira    See respective claimants    Lisbon    British Indian Ocean Territory

What is the capital and largest city of Kenya. The city and its surrounding area also forms the  County?
Nairobi    Pound sterling    Athens    Comorian franc

What is a word or term used for identification. s can identify a class or category of things, or a single thing, either uniquely, or within a given context?
Name    Pound sterling    Notes    Warsaw

What is a word or term used for identification. s can identify a class or category of things, or a single thing, either uniquely, or within a given context?
Name    Name    Sarajevo    Madrid

What is a word or term used for identification. s can identify a class or category of things, or a single thing, either uniquely, or within a given context?
Name    Martinique    Russian ruble    Harare

What is a word or term used for identification. s can identify a class or category of things, or a single thing, either uniquely, or within a given context?
Name    Wake Island    Currency    West African CFA franc

What is a word or term used for identification. s can identify a class or category of things, or a single thing, either uniquely, or within a given context?
Name    Willemstad    Kuala Lumpur     Bonaire

What is a word or term used for identification. s can identify a class or category of things, or a single thing, either uniquely, or within a given context?
Name    Maseru    Tegucigalpa    Swiss franc

What is a word or term used for identification. s can identify a class or category of things, or a single thing, either uniquely, or within a given context?
Name    Currency    Tanzanian shilling    Alfred Faure 

What is normally abbreviated with the dollar sign $, or alternatively N$ to distinguish it from other dollar-denominated currencies?
Namibian dollar    Somali shilling    Hong Kong    Rupiah

What is a small, uninhabited island in the Caribbean Sea, claimed as an unorganized unincorporated territory of the United States, which administers it through the U.S?
Navassa Island    Ugandan shilling    Roseau    Euro

What is the capital city of Burma, also known as Myanmar?
Naypyidaw    Euro    Conakry    Stockholm

What is the official currency of Nepal. The present rupee has the ISO 4217 code NPR and is normally abbreviated with the sign ₨?
Nepalese rupee    Name    Euro    Managua

What is a special collectivity of France located in the southwest Pacific Ocean,  east of Australia and  east of Metropolitan France?
New Caledonia    Pound sterling    Bahraini dinar    Andorra la Vella

What is the capital  of the Republic of India, and the seat of executive, legislative, and judiciary branches of the Government of India?
New Delhi    Majuro    Iraqi dinar    Official language

What is the official currency of the Taiwan Area of the Republic of China (ROC) since 1949, when it replaced the Old Taiwan dollar?
New Taiwan dollar    French Guiana    New Delhi    Saipan

What is the capital and largest city of the West African country Niger.  lies on the Niger River, primarily situated on the east bank?
Niamey    Ouagadougou    Manat     Belarusian ruble

What is the capital and largest city on the island of Cyprus, as well as its main business center?
Nicosia    Overseas collectivity of France    Central African CFA franc    Wallis and Futuna

What is an island country in the South Pacific Ocean,  northeast of New Zealand and within the triangle formed by Tonga (to the southwest), the Samoas (to the northwest) and the Cook Islands (to the southeast)?
Niue    Overseas collectivity of France    Djiboutian franc    Name

What is an American record label, owned by Warner Music Group and distributed by Warner Bros?
None    Doha    Lusaka    Caracas

What is a small island in the Pacific Ocean located between Australia, New Zealand and New Caledonia (France),  directly east of mainland Evans Head, and about  from Lord Howe Island?
Norfolk Island    ChiÅŸinÄƒu    Tripoli    Currency

What is the official currency of North Korea. It is subdivided into 100 chon?
North Korean won    Central African CFA franc    Official Language    Andorra la Vella

What is one of two Commonwealths of the United States; the other is Puerto Rico?
Northern Mariana Islands    Cockburn Town    Currency    Moldovan leu

What is the currency of Norway and its dependent territories. The plural form is kroner?
Norwegian krone    Maseru    Guatemala City    Turkish lira

What is the currency of Norway and its dependent territories. The plural form is kroner?
Norwegian krone    Kuwait City    Dili    Guernsey

What is a long-running quarterly scholarly journal that publishes short articles related to "English language and literature, lexicography, history, and scholarly antiquarianism"?
Notes    Beirut    Amman    Lisbon

What is a long-running quarterly scholarly journal that publishes short articles related to "English language and literature, lexicography, history, and scholarly antiquarianism"?
Notes    Cocos     Tanzanian shilling    East Jerusalem 

What is the capital and by far the largest city of Mauritania?
Nouakchott    Congolese franc    Budju    Swiss franc

What is the currency of Peru. It is subdivided into 100 cents, called céntimos in Spanish?
Nuevo sol    Ouguiya    Currency    Moscow

Whatis a group of coral islets within Tokelau in the south Pacific Ocean. Covering 5.5 km², it is the largest of the three islands that constitute Tokelau, and is composed of an atoll surrounding a central lagoon, which itself covers some 90 km²?
Nukunonu     Euro    None    Vientiane

What is the capital of Greenland and the largest city in Greenland. It is the seat of the Government of Greenland?
Nuuk    Damascus    Euro    Somoni

What is a language that is given a special legal status in a particular country, state, or other jurisdiction?
Official language    Euro    Maldivian rufiyaa    Capital

What is a language that is given a special legal status in a particular country, state, or other jurisdiction?
Official language    Saipan    Euro    r biogeographically as a synonym for either the Australasian ecozone 

What is a language that is given a special legal status in a particular country, state, or other jurisdiction?
Official language    Northern Mariana Islands    British Indian Ocean Territory    Gaborone

What is a language that is given a special legal status in a particular country, state, or other jurisdiction?
Official language    countries    Bonaire    Budapest

What is a language that is given a special legal status in a particular country, state, or other jurisdiction?
Official language    Castries    Conakry    Uruguayan peso

What is a language that is given a special legal status in a particular country, state, or other jurisdiction?
Official language    Name    Montserrat    Currency

What is a language that is given a special legal status in a particular country, state, or other jurisdiction?
Official Language    Berlin    area    Niue

Whatrarer  or ) is the capital of and most populous city in Norway. Founded around 1048 by King Harald III, the city was elevated to a bishopric in 1070 and a capital under Haakon V around 1300. Personal unions with Denmark from 1397 to 1523 and again from 1536 to 1814 and with Sweden from 1814 to 1905 reduced its influence?
Oslo    Transnistrian ruble    Windhoek    Rabat

What is the capital of Canada, and the fourth largest city in the country. The city is located on the south bank of the  River in the eastern portion of Southern Ontario?
Ottawa    Guam    Manat     Islamabad

What is the capital of Burkina Faso and the administrative, communications, cultural and economic centre of the nation?
Ouagadougou    Kuwaiti dinar    Tallero    Norwegian krone

What is the currency of Mauritania. It is the only circulating currency other than the Malagasy ariary whose division units are not based on a power of ten, each ouguiya comprising five khoums (singular and plural in English, , meaning "one fifth")?
Ouguiya    Nepalese rupee    Episkopi Cantonment    Aruba

Whatkistani rupee () (sign: ₨; code: PKR) is the official currency of Pakistan. The issuance of the currency is controlled by the State Bank of Pakistan, the central bank of the country?
Pakistani Rupee    Bangkok    Bhutanese ngultrum    Pula

What is a settlement that serves as the capital of the Federated States of Micronesi?
Palikir    ChiÅŸinÄƒu    Euro    Phnom Penh

What is an unoccupied equatorial Northern Pacific atoll administered as an unorganized incorporated territory by the United States federal government?
Palmyra Atoll    Prague    Name    Pyongyang

What is the capital and largest city of the Republic of Panama. It has a population of 880,691, with a total metro population of 1,272,672, and it is located at the Pacific entrance of the Panama Canal, in the province of Panama?
Panama City    Turkish lira    Yemeni rial    Amsterdam

What is the capital of French Polynesia, an overseas collectivity of France in the Pacific Ocean?
Papeete    Port Moresby    Lilongwe    Amsterdam

What is the capital and largest city of Suriname, located on banks of the Suriname River in the  District?
Paramaribo    Notes    r biogeographically as a synonym for either the Australasian ecozone     area

What is the capital and largest city of France. It is situated on the river Seine, in the north of the country, at the heart of the Île-de-France region?
Paris    Port Louis    British West African pound    Dinar

Whatnish) was the name of a coin that originated in Spain and became of immense importance internationally?
Peso    Christmas Island    Kabul    Martinique

Whatnish) was the name of a coin that originated in Spain and became of immense importance internationally?
Peso    Jarvis Island    Jersey    Santo Domingo

Whatnish) was the name of a coin that originated in Spain and became of immense importance internationally?
Peso    Euro    Canberra    Dhaka

Whatnish) was the name of a coin that originated in Spain and became of immense importance internationally?
Peso    Prague    Norwegian krone    Stockholm

What is the capital and largest city of Cambodia. Located on the banks of the Mekong River,  has been the national capital since French colonization of Cambodia, and has grown to become the nation's center of economic and industrial activities, as well as the center of security, politics, cultural heritage, and diplomacy of Cambodia?
Phnom Penh    Basseterre    Basseterre    Beirut

What are a group of four volcanic islands in the southern Pacific Ocean that form a British Overseas Territory?
Pitcairn Islands    Central African CFA franc    Guinean franc    Dakar

What is the capital and largest city of Montenegro?
Podgorica    Maseru    Guinean franc    Kyat

What is all the organisms of the same group or species who live in the same geographical area and are capable of interbreeding?
population    Swiss franc    Yemeni rial    Yerevan

What is a city in Mauritius, located in the  District, the western part also lies in the Rivière Noire District?
Port Louis    Pound sterling    Official language    Arabic

What.?
Port Moresby    Harare    Somoni    Bonaire

What is the capital of the Republic of Trinidad and Tobago and the country's third-largest municipality, after San Fernando and Chaguanas?
Port of Spain    Naira    Tegucigalpa    British Indian Ocean Territory

What is the capital and largest city of Vanuatu.  Its population in the last census (2009) was 44,040, an increase of 50% on the previous census result (29,356 in 1999)?
Port Vila    Sarajevo    Tallinn    Papeete

What is the official currency of the United Kingdom, the British Crown dependencies of Jersey, Guernsey and the Isle of Man, the British Overseas Territories of South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands, the British Antarctic Territory and Saint Helena, Ascension and Tristan da Cunha (in Tristan da Cunha only)?
Pound sterling    Clipperton Island    San Salvador    Thimphu

What is the official currency of the United Kingdom, the British Crown dependencies of Jersey, Guernsey and the Isle of Man, the British Overseas Territories of South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands, the British Antarctic Territory and Saint Helena, Ascension and Tristan da Cunha (in Tristan da Cunha only)?
Pound sterling    Tunisian dinar    Hong Kong dollar    Juba

What is the official currency of the United Kingdom, the British Crown dependencies of Jersey, Guernsey and the Isle of Man, the British Overseas Territories of South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands, the British Antarctic Territory and Saint Helena, Ascension and Tristan da Cunha (in Tristan da Cunha only)?
Pound sterling    Lithuanian litas    Capital    Gibraltar

What is the official currency of the United Kingdom, the British Crown dependencies of Jersey, Guernsey and the Isle of Man, the British Overseas Territories of South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands, the British Antarctic Territory and Saint Helena, Ascension and Tristan da Cunha (in Tristan da Cunha only)?
Pound sterling    Capital    None    Guyanese dollar

What is the official currency of the United Kingdom, the British Crown dependencies of Jersey, Guernsey and the Isle of Man, the British Overseas Territories of South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands, the British Antarctic Territory and Saint Helena, Ascension and Tristan da Cunha (in Tristan da Cunha only)?
Pound sterling    UAE dirham    Khartoum    Guatemala City

What is the capital and largest city of the Czech Republic. It is the fourteenth-largest city in the European Union?
Prague    See respective claimants    Capital    Rome

What is the capital and largest city of Cape Verde, an island nation in the Atlantic Ocean west of Senegal?
Praia    Seoul    Falkland Islands    Khartoum

Whatis a city in the northern part of Gauteng Province, South Africa. It is one of the country's three capital cities, serving as the executive (administrative) and de facto national capital; the others are Cape Town, the legislative capital, and Bloemfontein, the judicial capital?
Pretoria     Mayotte    Panama City    Road Town

What is an unincorporated territory of the United States, located in the northeastern Caribbean, east of the Dominican Republic and west of both the United States Virgin Islands and the British Virgin Islands?
Puerto Rico    Pula    Vientiane    Euro

What is the largest city in Istria County, Croatia, situated at the southern tip of the Istria peninsula, with a population of 62,080 (2006)?
Pula    Bonaire    Buenos Aires    Pretoria 

What is the  capital of the Democratic People's Republic of Korea, commonly known as North Korea, and the largest city in the country?
Pyongyang    population    Euro    Cocos 

Whatcisco de , is the capital city of Ecuador, and at an elevation of 9,350 feet (2,800 meters above sea level), it is the highest capital city in the world housing the administrative, legislative and judicial functions?
Quito    Jakarta    Western Sahara    Name

Whatnish Ciudad de ), is the capital and third largest city of the Kingdom of Morocco with a population of approximately 1 million (2012)?
Rabat    Funafuti    North Korean won    Willemstad

What is the capital and largest city of Latvia. With 658,640 inhabitants (2012),  is the largest city of the Baltic states and home to more than one third of Latvia's population?
Riga    Anguilla    Guyanese dollar    Singapore

What is the local currency in Malaysia, but it can also refer to the Brunei dollar or Singapore dollar in the Malay language?
Ringgit    Notes    Minsk    Antananarivo

What is one of the four biggest cities in Saudi Arabia, is the capital and largest city of Saudi Arabia?
Riyadh    Ouguiya    Kyat    Hargeisa

What is the capital of the British Virgin Islands. It is situated on the horseshoe-shaped Road Harbour in the centre of the island's south coast?
Road Town    Ringgit    Russian ruble    population

What is the currency of Romania. It is subdivided into 100 bani (singular: ban)?
Romanian leu    Guam    Yen    Mayotte

What is a city and special comune ("Roma Capitale") in Italy.  is the capital of Italy and also of Lazio (Latin: Latium)?
Rome    Czech koruna    Overseas collectivity of France    Belarusian ruble

What is the capital and largest city of Dominica. With a   population of 16,582. it is a small and compact urban settlement, located within the Saint George parish and surrounded by the Caribbean Sea, the  River and Morne Bruce?
Roseau    Brazzaville    Capital    Kiev

What is the official currency of Indonesia. Issued and controlled by the Bank of Indonesia, the ISO 4217 currency code for the Indonesian rupiah is IDR?
Rupiah    Bamako    Gaborone    Amman

Whatrish, Jamaica) is a Jamaican reggae singer and record producer?
Rupie    Northern Mariana Islands    Lari    Euro

Whatlish spelling and Russian plurals with numbers) (code: RUB) is the currency of the Russian Federation and the two partially recognized republics of Abkhazia and South Ossetia?
Russian ruble    Canberra    Majuro    Kuwait City

Whatlish spelling and Russian plurals with numbers) (code: RUB) is the currency of the Russian Federation and the two partially recognized republics of Abkhazia and South Ossetia?
Russian ruble    Saint Pierre and Miquelon    Kiev    Moldovan leu

What is the currency of Rwanda. It is subdivided into 100 centimes?
Rwandan franc    Saba    Roseau    Warsaw

What is a Caribbean island and the smallest special municipality (officially public body) of the Netherlands?
Saba    Notes    Transnistrian ruble    Bridgetown

What is an island in the northeast Caribbean, approximately  east of Puerto Rico. The 87 km2 island is divided roughly 60/40 between France (53 km2) and the Kingdom of the Netherlands (34 km2); they are roughly equal in population. It is one of the smallest sea islands divided between two nations, a division dating to 1648. The southern Dutch part comprises Sint Maarten and is one of four constituent countries that form the Kingdom of the Netherlands. The northern French part comprises the Collectivité de Saint-Martin (Collectivity of St. Martin) and is an overseas collectivity of Franc?
Saint Martin     Pound sterling    Bahraini dinar    lthough myths and speculation about a Terra Australis 

What is a self-governing territorial overseas collectivity of France, situated in the northwestern Atlantic Ocean near Canada?
Saint Pierre and Miquelon    Vientiane    Guam    Hanoi

What is the largest island of the Commonwealth of the Northern Mariana Islands (CNMI),  an unincorporated territory of the United States?
Saipan    Andorra la Vella    Euro    Euro

Whatlish: Holy Savior) is the capital city of the Republic of El Salvador, and the capital of the  department?
San Salvador    Overseas collectivity of France    Cairo    Euro

What is the capital and largest city in the Dominican Republic?
Santo Domingo    Lisbon    Congolese franc    Kralendijk

What is the capital and largest city of Bosnia and Herzegovina, with an estimated population of over 321,000 people within its administrative limits?
Sarajevo    Melekeok    various    American Samoa

What is the currency of Saudi Arabia. It is abbreviated as ر.س or SR (Saudi Riyal)?
Saudi riyal    Saint Martin     Addis Ababa    Bamako

What is the capital and largest metropolis of South Korea?
Seoul    Pound sterling    Macau    Vienna

What is the currency of Serbia. An earlier dinar was used in Serbia between 1868 and 1918. The earliest use of the dinar dates back to 121?
Serbian dinar    Ulaanbaatar    West African CFA franc    Euro

What is the currency of the Seychelles. It is subdivided into 100 cents. In the local Seychellois Creole (Seselwa) language, it is called the roupi?
Seychellois rupee    Budju    Name    Congolese franc

What is a Southeast Asian island city-state off the southern tip of the Malay Peninsula,  north of the equator?
Singapore    Naira    Norfolk Island    Rome

What is the official currency of Singapore. It is normally abbreviated with the dollar sign $, or alternatively S$ to distinguish it from other dollar-denominated currencies?
Singapore dollar    West African CFA franc    Islamabad    Bangui

What is a Caribbean island and a special municipality (officially public body) of the Netherlands?
Sint Eustatius    Valletta    Brazzaville    Yamoussoukro 

What is a constituent country () of the Kingdom of the Netherlands. It encompasses the southern half of the Caribbean island of Saint Martin, while the northern half of the island constitutes the French overseas collectivity of Saint-Martin?
Sint Maarten    Nukunonu     Namibian dollar    Bissau

What is the capital and largest city of the Republic of Macedonia. It is the country's political, cultural, economic, and academic center?
Skopje    Abuja    list_countries    Faroe Islands

What is the capital and largest city of Bulgaria.  is located at the foot of Mount Vitosha in the western part of the country?
Sofia    Brussels    Euro    Comorian franc

What is the official currency of Somalia?
Somali shilling    Belarusian ruble    Currency    Somali shilling

What is the official currency of Somaliland, a self-declared republic that is internationally recognized as an autonomous region of Somalia?
Somaliland shilling    Vaduz    Standard Chinese    Tirana

What is the currency of Tajikistan. It is subdivided into 100 diram (). The currency is named after the father of the Tajik nation, Ismail Samani (also spelled Ismoil )?
Somoni    Arabic    Abuja    Mozambican metical

What is the currency of South Africa. It takes its name from the Witwatersrand (White-waters-ridge in English), the ridge upon which Johannesburg is built and where most of South Africa's gold deposits were found?
South African rand    Melekeok    Amman    image

What is a British overseas territory in the southern Atlantic Ocean?
South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands    Arabic    Syrian pound    r biogeographically as a synonym for either the Australasian ecozone 

What is the currency of South Korea. A single won is divided into 100 jeon, the monetary subunit?
South Korean won    Bandar Seri Begawan    Beirut    Melekeok

What is the official currency of the Republic of South Sudan. It is subdivided into 100 piasters?
South Sudanese pound    Mbabane     Maldivian rufiyaa    Sint Eustatius

What is the capital and hub of the Republic of Kiribati and home to approximately half of Kiribati's total population?
South Tarawa    Gaborone    Navassa Island    Sint Eustatius

What is a large suburb of the capital Colombo and  is the parliament site of Sri Lanka?
Sri Jayawardenapura Kotte    Anguilla    British West African pound    Isle of Man

What is the currency of Sri Lanka, divided into 100 cents?
Sri Lankan rupee    Warsaw    Port of Spain    Alofi

What is a standardized variety of Chinese and the official language of the People's Republic of China and the Republic of China (Taiwan), and is one of the four official languages of Singapore?
Standard Chinese    New Caledonia    Saba    Ouagadougou

What is a standardized variety of Chinese and the official language of the People's Republic of China and the Republic of China (Taiwan), and is one of the four official languages of Singapore?
Standard Chinese    Bern    Arabic    French Guiana

What is the capital of Sweden and the largest city of Fennoscandia.   is the most populous city in Sweden, with a population of 871,952 in the municipality (2010), 1,372,565 in the urban area (2010), and 2,119,760 in the metropolitan area (2010)?
Stockholm    Howland Island    Notes    Russian ruble

Whathistorically as Charcas , La Plata  and Chuquisaca  (population 247,300 in 2006) is the constitutional capital of Bolivia, the capital of the department of Chuquisaca and the 5th most populated city in Bolivia?
Sucre     Swedish krona    Turkish lira    Iraqi dinar

What is the currency of Sudan and also used in South Sudan until finalization of the introduction of the South ?
Sudanese pound    Mamoudzou    image    Belmopan

Whatsist broadly of all French-administered territory outside of the European continent?
Sui generis collectivity     Name    Name    Pound sterling

What is the capital of Abkhazia, a disputed region on the Black Sea coast?
Sukhumi    Guernsey    Tunisian dinar    Harare

What is divided into 100 cents?
Surinamese dollar    Seoul    New Delhi    Saipan

What is the capital and the second most populated municipality of Fiji, after Nasinu. It is located on the southeast coast of the island of Viti Levu, in the  Rewa Province, Central Division?
Suva    Indian rupee    Pyongyang    Nukunonu 

What is an archipelago in the Arctic Ocean, constituting the northernmost part of Norway. Located north of mainland Europe, it is about midway between mainland Norway and the North Pole?
Svalbard    Akrotiri and Dhekelia      Tunis    Peso

What are in common use; the former precedes or follows the value, the latter usually follows it, but especially in the past, it sometimes preceded the value?
Swedish krona    Ljubljana    Bamako    Equatorial Guinean peseta

What is the currency and legal tender of Switzerland and Liechtenstein; it is also legal tender in the Italian exclave Campione d'Italia?
Swiss franc    Moldovan leu    Uruguayan peso    Currency

What is the currency and legal tender of Switzerland and Liechtenstein; it is also legal tender in the Italian exclave Campione d'Italia?
Swiss franc    Praia    United States dollar    Somali shilling

What is the currency of Syria and is issued by the Central Bank of Syria?
Syrian pound    Honiara    Panama City    Lesotho loti

What is the currency of Bangladesh. Bangladesh Bank, the central bank of the country, controls the issuance of the currency, except one taka and two taka notes, which are the responsibility of the  Ministry of Finance of the government of Bangladesh?
Taka    Rupiah    Overseas collectivity of France    Naypyidaw

WhatThe tallero was the currency of Eritrea between 1890 and 1921. It was subdivided into 5 lire, each of 100 centesimi?
Tallero    Iraqi dinar    Sri Jayawardenapura Kotte    Central African CFA franc

What is the capital and largest city of Estonia. It occupies an area of  with a population of 425,249. It is situated on the northern coast of the country, on the shore of the Gulf of Finland,  south of Helsinki, east of Stockholm and west of Saint Petersburg?
Tallinn    Phnom Penh    Kingstown    Midway Atoll

Whatlish: shilling) is the currency of Tanzania, although widespread use of U.S?
Tanzanian shilling    Panama City    Name    Serbian dinar

What is the capital of Uzbekistan and of the  Province. The officially registered population of the city in 2008 was about 2.2 million?
Tashkent    Notes    Serbian dinar    Capital

What,is the capital and the largest city of Georgia, lying on the banks of the Kura River. The name is derived from an early Georgian form T'pilisi (ტფილისი) and it was officially known as Tpilisi (in Georgian) or Tiflis (in Russian) until 1936. The city covers an area of  and has 1,480,000 inhabitants?
Tbilisi    Tallero    population    Euro

WhatDistrict  Spanish:  , Municipio del Distrito Central  or  , M.D.C.), commonly referred to as Tegus, is the capital of Honduras and seat of government of the Republic, along with its twin sister Comayagüela?
Tegucigalpa    population    Helsinki    Pound sterling

What is the capital of Iran and  Province. With a population of 12,223,598 it is Iran's largest urban area and city, one of the largest cities in Western Asia?
Tehran    Australian dollar    Guernsey    South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands

What is the capital and largest town of the island of Saba, the Caribbean Netherlands, and is the first stop on the way from Saba's Port in Fort Bay towards the rest of the island?
The Bottom    Bissau    Warsaw    Lari

What is the capital and largest city of Bhutan. It is situated in the western central part of Bhutan and the surrounding valley is one of Bhutan's  dzongkhags, the  District?
Thimphu    Svalbard    Stockholm    Ottawa

What is a dimension in which events can be ordered from the past through the present into the futur?
time    Tokelau    West African CFA franc    Cook Islands

What is the capital and the largest city of Albania. Modern  was founded as an Ottoman town in 1614 by Sulejman Bargjini, a local ruler from Mullet?
Tirana    Turkish lira    Anguilla    United States dollar

What is a territory of New Zealand in the South Pacific Ocean that consists of three tropical coral atolls with a combined land area of 10 km² (3.86 mi²) and a population of approximately 1,400. The atolls lie north of the Samoan Islands, east of Tuvalu, south of the Phoenix Islands, southwest of the more distant Line Islands, and northwest of the Cook Islands?
Tokelau    Cayman Islands    Zambian kwacha    Tokyo

What is one of the 47 prefectures of Japan.  is the capital of Japan, the center of the Greater  Area, and the largest metropolitan area in the world?
Tokyo    Kingman Reef    Euro    Lari

What is the official currency of Transnistria. It is divided into 100 kopecks. Since Transnistria is a state with limited international recognition, its currency has no ISO 4217 code?
Transnistrian ruble    Bucharest    Seoul    Lusaka

What is the capital city and the largest city of Libya. As of 2011, the  metropolitan area (district area) had a population of 2.2 million people?
Tripoli    Lilongwe    Ugandan shilling    Bridgetown

What is the capital of both the ian Republic and the  Governorate. It is ia's largest city, with a population of 2,256,320 as of 2011; the greater metropolitan area holds some 2,412,500 inhabitants?
Tunis    Australian dollar    Surinamese dollar    Conakry

What is the currency of Tunisia. It is subdivided into 1000 milim or millimes (مليم)?
Tunisian dinar    Maldivian rufiyaa    Palmyra Atoll    Euro

What is the currency of Turkey and the Turkish Republic of Northern Cyprus (recognised only by Turkey)?
Turkish lira    Pyongyang    Peso    Euro

What is the currency of Turkey and the Turkish Republic of Northern Cyprus (recognised only by Turkey)?
Turkish lira    Roseau    Equatorial Guinean peseta    Tallero

What are a British Overseas Territory consisting of the larger Caicos Islands and smaller Turks Islands, two groups of tropical islands in the Lucayan Archipelago, part of the larger Antilles island grouping?
Turks and Caicos Islands    Pound sterling    Sri Jayawardenapura Kotte    Navassa Island

What is the currency of the United Arab Emirates. The ISO 4217 code (currency abbreviation) for the United Arab Emirates dirham is AED?
UAE dirham    Tegucigalpa    Saint Pierre and Miquelon    Niamey

What is the currency of Uganda. Officially, the shilling is subdivided into 100 cents but no subdivisions have been issued since the revaluation of the shilling in 198?
Ugandan shilling    Nairobi    Port Moresby    Rupiah

What is subdivided into 100 kopiyok?
Ukrainian hryvnia    Currency    Panama City    Port Louis

What is the capital and the largest city of Mongolia?
Ulaanbaatar    Howland Island    Dodoma     Bamako

What is the official fiat currency of the United States of America and its overseas territories?
United States dollar    density    Turks and Caicos Islands    Mozambican metical

What is the official fiat currency of the United States of America and its overseas territories?
United States dollar    Euro    Official language    Antananarivo

What are a group of islands in the Caribbean that are an insular area of the United States?
United States Virgin Islands    Euro    Sarajevo    Yemeni rial

What is subdivided into 100 centésimos?
Uruguayan peso    Kigali    Hargeisa    Euro

What is the official fiat currency of the United States of America and its overseas territories?
US Dollar    Ulaanbaatar    Capital    Euro

What is the capital of the principality of Liechtenstein and the seat of the national parliament?
Vaduz    Notes    Jerusalem    Port Louis

What is the capital of Malta, colloquially known as Il-Belt () in Maltese. It is located in the central-eastern portion of the island of Malta, and the historical city has a population of 6,966.  is the second southernmost capital of the EU member states after Nicosia?
Valletta    Andorra la Vella    Port Louis    Lari

What is an English dubstep/electronic music duo formed in 2002. The group blends samples, acoustic and electronic instrumentation, and singing from a revolving cast of vocalists?
various    Swedish krona    Dinar    Alofi

What is a landlocked sovereign city-state whose territory consists of a walled enclave within the city of Rome?
Vatican City    Tegucigalpa    Tirana    ChiÅŸinÄƒu

What is the capital and largest city of Austria, and one of the nine states of Austria?
Vienna    Gibraltar pound    South African rand    Capital

What is the capital and largest city of Laos, situated on the Mekong River near the border with Thailand?
Vientiane    Macedonian denar    Bern    Jersey

What is the capital of Lithuania, and its largest city, with a population of 535,091 (809,225 together with  County) as of 2011. It is located in the southeast of the country?
Vilnius    Clipperton Island    Lithuanian litas    Russian ruble

What is a coral atoll having a coastline of  in the North Pacific Ocean, located about two-thirds of the way between Honolulu,  to the east, and Guam,  to the west?
Wake Island    Pound sterling    Kenyan shilling    Nuevo sol

What is a French island collectivity in the South Pacific between Tuvalu to the northwest, Rotuma of Fiji to the west, the main part of Fiji to the southwest, Tonga to the southeast, Samoa to the east, the New Zealand-associated state of Tokelau to the northeast and to a more distant north the Phoenix Islands (Kiribati)?
Wallis and Futuna    Sri Jayawardenapura Kotte    Howland Island    Arabic

Whatlish as Warszawa ( (also [varˈʃava]); see also other names), is the capital and largest city of Poland?
Warsaw    New Delhi    Kingstown    Honiara

What is the capital city and second most populous urban area of New Zealand. It is at the southwestern tip of the North Island, between Cook Strait and the Rimutaka Range?
Wellington    Euro    Official language    Mexico City

What is the currency of eight independent states in West Africa: Benin, Burkina Faso, Côte d'Ivoire, Guinea-Bissau, Mali, Niger, Sénégal and Togo?
West African CFA franc    Kathmandu    Nicosia    Djiboutian franc

What is the currency of eight independent states in West Africa: Benin, Burkina Faso, Côte d'Ivoire, Guinea-Bissau, Mali, Niger, Sénégal and Togo?
West African CFA franc    Zambian kwacha    Guam    Minsk

What is the currency of eight independent states in West Africa: Benin, Burkina Faso, Côte d'Ivoire, Guinea-Bissau, Mali, Niger, Sénégal and Togo?
West African CFA franc    Norfolk Island    Helsinki    Official Language

What is the currency of eight independent states in West Africa: Benin, Burkina Faso, Côte d'Ivoire, Guinea-Bissau, Mali, Niger, Sénégal and Togo?
West African CFA franc    Moldovan leu    Kigali    Pyongyang

What is the currency of eight independent states in West Africa: Benin, Burkina Faso, Côte d'Ivoire, Guinea-Bissau, Mali, Niger, Sénégal and Togo?
West African CFA franc    South African rand    Wellington    West African CFA franc

What is the currency of eight independent states in West Africa: Benin, Burkina Faso, Côte d'Ivoire, Guinea-Bissau, Mali, Niger, Sénégal and Togo?
West African CFA franc    Sofia    United States Virgin Islands    Doha

What is a disputed territory in North Africa, bordered by Morocco to the north, Algeria to the extreme northeast, Mauritania to the east and south, and the Atlantic Ocean to the west?
Western Sahara    Syrian pound    Port of Spain    Pakistani Rupee

What is the capital city of Curaçao, an island in the southern Caribbean Sea that forms a constituent country of the Kingdom of the Netherlands?
Willemstad    Moldovan leu    Tokelau    Windhoek

What is the capital and largest city of the Republic of Namibia. It is located in central Namibia in the Khomas Highland plateau area, at around  above sea level?
Windhoek    Bahraini dinar    Cayman Islands    Euro

WhatDistrict of  is the official political capital and administrative capital city of Côte d'Ivoire, while the economic capital of the country is Abidjan?
Yamoussoukro     Johnston Atoll    Dili    Skopje

What is the currency of Yemen. It is technically divided into 100 fils, although coins denominated in fils have not been issued since Yemeni unification?
Yemeni rial    None    Moroccan dirham    Czech koruna

What is the official currency of Japan. It is the third most traded currency in the foreign exchange market after the United States dollar and the euro?
Yen    Oslo    Ulaanbaatar    Cockburn Town

What is the capital and largest city of Armenia and one of the world's oldest continuously inhabited cities?
Yerevan    Tokyo    Madrid    Pyongyang

What is the capital and the largest city of the Republic of Croatia. It is located in the northwest of the country, along the Sava river, at the southern slopes of the Medvednica mountain?
Zagreb    Svalbard    Name    Basseterre

What is the currency of Zambia. It is subdivided into 100 ngwe?
Zambian kwacha    Birr    Capital    Yen

