What is a 1931 American film adaptation of Mark Twain's 1889 novel A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court?
A Connecticut Yankee (1931 film)    Thunder Birds (1942 film)    Ramona (1936 film)    Dragonwyck (film)

What is a silent film. The film was controversial because of the sequences of what was regarded as superfluous nudity by the main character, Nydia, played by Australian swimming star Annette Kellerman?
A Daughter of the Gods    A Message to Garcia (1936 film)    Under Your Spell (film)    Kiss of Death (1947 film)

What is a 1936 American war film directed by George Marshall and starring Wallace Beery and Barbara Stanwyck, John Boles and Alan Hale, Sr.?
A Message to Garcia (1936 film)    Alexander's Ragtime Band (film)    Doctors' Wives (1931 film)    The Song of Bernadette (film)

What is a 1945 film, the first film directed by Greek-American director Elia Kazan, starring James Dunn (who won the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor), Dorothy McGuire, Joan Blondell, and Peggy Ann Garner  (who won the Academy Juvenile Award)?
A Tree Grows in Brooklyn (film)    The Gang's All Here (1943 film)    The Little Princess (1939 film)    Berkeley Square (film)

What is a World War II war film released in 1945, based on the novel by Harry Brown, who was a writer for Yank, the Army Weekly based in England?
A Walk in the Sun (1945 film)    Happy Days (1929 film)    The Song of Bernadette (film)    Laura (1944 film)

What is a film released by Twentieth Century Fox that takes its name from the 1911 Irving Berlin (1888-1989) song "Alexander's Ragtime Band" to tell a story of a society boy who scandalizes his family by pursuing a career in Ragtime instead of in "serious" music?
Alexander's Ragtime Band (film)    Stowaway (1936 film)    Lloyd's of London (film)    Dante's Inferno (1935 film)

What is a 1946 drama film directed by John Cromwell.  An adaptation of the 1944 novel by Margaret Landon, it was based on the fictionalized diaries of Anna Leonowens, an Anglo-Indian woman who claimed to be British and became governess in the Royal Court of Siam (now modern Thailand) during the 1860s?
Anna and the King of Siam (film)    Jesse James (film)    Lloyd's of London (film)    The Little Princess (1939 film)

What is a 1939 adventure film directed by Gregory Ratoff and starring Alice Faye, Warner Baxter, Charles Winninger, Arthur Treacher, and Keye Luke?
Barricade (1939 film)    Pin Up Girl (film)    Greenwich Village (film)    The Razor's Edge (1946 film)

Whatuare (1933) is a drama film produced by Fox Film Corporation, directed by Frank Lloyd, and starring Leslie Howard and Heather Angel?
Berkeley Square (film)    Coney Island (1943 film)    Gateway (film)    Fallen Angel (1945 film)

What is a 1934 musical comedy film made by Fox Film Corporation, and was directed by David Butler who co-wrote original story and screenplay with producer Buddy G?
Bottoms Up (1934 film)    Heaven Can Wait (1943 film)    Suez (film)    Heidi (1937 film)

What is a 1934 American comedy drama film directed by David Butler.  The screenplay by William Conselman is based on a story by David Butler and Edwin Burke, and focuses on the relationship between bachelor aviator James 'Loop' Merritt (James Dunn) and his orphaned godchild, Shirley Blake (Shirley Temple)?
Bright Eyes (1934 film)    Tess of the Storm Country (1932 film)    Leave Her to Heaven {{blue ribbon}} (1945) - Fox's highest grossing film of the 1940s    Leave Her to Heaven {{blue ribbon}} (1945) - Fox's highest grossing film of the 1940s

What is a 1936 American comedy drama film directed by David Butler.  The screenplay by Sam Hellman, Gladys Lehman, and Harry Tugend is based on the story The Lighthouse at Cape Tempest by Laura E?
Captain January (1936 film)    Second Fiddle (1939 film)    Guadalcanal Diary (film)    Stowaway (1936 film)

What is a 1933 American drama film directed by Frank Lloyd. The screenplay by Reginald Berkeley and Sonya Levien is based on the 1931 play of the same title by Noël Coward?
Cavalcade (1933 film)    A Tree Grows in Brooklyn (film)    Heidi (1937 film)    Sally

What is a 1942 drama film which follows the exploits of a newsreel photographer in China and Burma against the backdrop of World War II?
China Girl (1942 film)    Wake Up and Dream (film)    A Daughter of the Gods    Wilson (film)

Whathistorical drama film based on H. Rider Haggard's 1889 novel Cleopatra and the plays Cleopatre by Émile Moreau and Victorien Sardou and William Shakespeare's Antony and Cleopatra?
Cleopatra (1917 film)    Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm (1938 film)    The Black Swan (film)    Under the Yoke (film)

What is a 1943 American Technicolor musical film released by Twentieth Century Fox and starring Betty Grable in one of her biggest hits?
Coney Island (1943 film)    China Girl (1942 film)    A Tree Grows in Brooklyn (film)    Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm (1938 film)

What is a 1935 motion picture loosely based on Dante Alighieri's The Divine Comedy. It is primarily remembered for a 10-minute depiction of hell realised by director Harry Lachman, himself an established post-impressionist painter?
Dante's Inferno (1935 film)    Bright Eyes (1934 film)    Sunny Side Up (film)    Fallen Angel (1945 film)

What is a Gershwin musical romantic comedy film starring Janet Gaynor and Charles Farrell, directed by David Butler,  with color sequences in Multicolor (now lost)?
Delicious (1931 film)    Tess of the Storm Country (1932 film)    Sunny Side Up (film)    Stowaway (1936 film)

What is a 1936 American musical film directed by William A. Seiter.  The screenplay was written by Nat Perrin and Arthur Sheekman?
Dimples (film)    Dante's Inferno (1935 film)    Heaven Can Wait (1943 film)    Fallen Angel (1945 film)

What is a 1931 romantic drama film made by Fox Film Corporation, directed by Frank Borzage. The film stars Warner Baxter and Joan Bennett?
Doctors' Wives (1931 film)    Hearts in Dixie (film)    The Luck of the Irish (1948 film)    State Fair (1945 film)

What is a 1946 American period drama film made by Twentieth Century-Fox. It was directed by Joseph L?
Dragonwyck (film)    China Girl (1942 film)    Stowaway (1936 film)    None But the Brave (1928 film)

WhatA film version of East Lynne. The movie was adapted from the novel by Tom Barry and Bradley King and directed by Frank Lloyd?
East Lynne (1931 film)    None But the Brave (1928 film)    A Message to Garcia (1936 film)    Heidi (1937 film)

What is a 1945 black-and-white film noir directed by Otto Preminger, with cinematography by Joseph LaShelle, who had also worked with Preminger on Laura a year before?
Fallen Angel (1945 film)    Second Fiddle (1939 film)    Street Angel (1928 film)    Ramona (1936 film)

What is an independent London based production company, specialising in crime and youth films?
Gateway (film)    Tess of the Storm Country (1932 film)    Sing    Bottoms Up (1934 film)

What is a 1942 comedy film made by 20th Century Fox, directed by Harold D. Schuster, and starring Don Ameche and Joan Bennett?
Girl Trouble (1942 film)    Ramona (1936 film)    Leave Her to Heaven {{blue ribbon}} (1945) - Fox's highest grossing film of the 1940s    Liliom (1930 film)

What is a 1934 Fox film of A. J. Cronin's novel of the same title. The film was produced by Jesse L?
Grand Canary (film)    The Little Princess (1939 film)    Under the Yoke (film)    One in a Million (1936 film)

What is a 1944 film from Twentieth Century Fox  directed by Walter Lang. It stars Carmen Miranda and Don Ameche?
Greenwich Village (film)    Thunder Birds (1942 film)    A Message to Garcia (1936 film)    Doctors' Wives (1931 film)

What is a 1943 World War II war film starring Preston Foster, Lloyd Nolan, William Bendix, Richard Conte, Anthony Quinn and the film debut of Richard Jaeckel?
Guadalcanal Diary (film)    Sing    East Lynne (1931 film)    Whirlpool (film)

What is an 80 minute musical film, notable for being the first feature film shown entirely in widescreen anywhere in the world?
Happy Days (1929 film)    Bottoms Up (1934 film)    A Connecticut Yankee (1931 film)    Suez (film)

What is a film directed by Irving Pichel and starring Don Amech?
Happy Land (film)    The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes (film)    Kiss of Death (1947 film)    Under the Yoke (film)

WhatHearts in Dixie (1929) was one of the first all-"talkie", big-studio production to boast a predominantly African-American cast?
Hearts in Dixie (film)    Kiss of Death (1947 film)    State Fair (1933 film)    One in a Million (1936 film)

What is a 1943 American comedy film produced and directed by Ernst Lubitsch. The screenplay was by Samson Raphaelson based on the play Birthday by Leslie Bush-Fekete?
Heaven Can Wait (1943 film)    Thunderhead    The Iron Horse (film)    Greenwich Village (film)

What is a 1937 American dramatic film directed by Allan Dwan.  The screenplay by Julien Josephson and Walter Ferris was based on the 1880 children's story of the same name by Swiss author Johanna Spyri?
Heidi (1937 film)    Lloyd's of London (film)    Barricade (1939 film)    Sunrise (film)

What is a salutation or greeting in the English language. It is attested in writing as early as the 1860s?
Hello    Ramona (1936 film)    One in a Million (1936 film)    Happy Days (1929 film)

What may refer t?
In the Meantime    A Message to Garcia (1936 film)    Heaven Can Wait (1943 film)    Anna and the King of Siam (film)

What is an American film adaptation of Charlotte Brontë's 1847 novel of the same name, released by 20th Century Fox?
Jane Eyre (1944 film)    China Girl (1942 film)    Cleopatra (1917 film)    Gateway (film)

What is a western movie directed by Henry King and starring Tyrone Power, Henry Fonda, Nancy Kelly, and Randolph Scott?
Jesse James (film)    Dimples (film)    Hearts in Dixie (film)    Jesse James (film)

WhatKiss of Death is a 1947 film noir movie directed by Henry Hathaway and written by Ben Hecht and Charles Lederer from a story by Eleazar Lipsky?
Kiss of Death (1947 film)    Sunny Side Up (film)    Kiss of Death (1947 film)    The Keys of the Kingdom (film)

What is an American film noir directed by Otto Preminger. It stars Gene Tierney, Dana Andrews and Clifton Webb?
Laura (1944 film)    Laura (1944 film)    Midnight (1939 film)    Laura (1944 film)

What is a 1909 play by the Hungarian playwright Ferenc Molnár. It was very famous in its own right during the early to mid-20th century, but is best known today as the basis for the Rodgers and Hammerstein musical Carousel?
Liliom (1930 film)    One in a Million (1936 film)    Jane Eyre (1944 film)    A Message to Garcia (1936 film)

What is a 1936 American drama film directed by Henry King. It stars Tyrone Power, Madeleine Carroll, and Guy Standing?
Lloyd's of London (film)    Seventh Heaven (1927 film)    The Pied Piper (1942 film)    Gateway (film)

What is a 1939 romantic comedy (with some elements of screwball comedy) directed by Mitchell Leisen and written by Charles Brackett and Billy Wilder based on a story by Edwin Justus Mayer and Franz Schulz?
Midnight (1939 film)    Sally    Guadalcanal Diary (film)    Whirlpool (film)

Whatmare Alley is a 1947 20th Century Fox film noir starring Tyrone Power and Joan Blondell, and directed by Edmund Goulding?
Nightmare Alley (film)    Ramona (1936 film)    Second Honeymoon (film)    Second Honeymoon (film)

What is a feature film released by Fox Film Corporation, directed by Albert Ray and starring Charles Morton, Sally Phipps, J?
None But the Brave (1928 film)    Charlie Chan Carries On (film)    Hearts in Dixie (film)    The Poor Little Rich Girl (1936 film)

What is a 1937 American film which marked the Hollywood debut of Sonja Henie. It features footage from the 1936 Winter Olympic Games?
One in a Million (1936 film)    The Black Swan (film)    Happy Land (film)    Midnight (1939 film)

What is a 1933 American drama film directed by John For?
Pilgrimage (1933 film)    The Three Musketeers (1939 film)    Second Honeymoon (film)    The Razor's Edge (1946 film)

What is a 1944 20th Century Fox Technicolor musical romantic comedy motion picture starring Betty Grable, John Harvey, Martha Raye, and Joe E?
Pin Up Girl (film)    Thin Ice (1937 film)    Thunderhead    The Keys of the Kingdom (film)

What is a 1949 film adapted from Samuel Shellabargers novel Prince of Foxes.  The movie starred Tyrone Power as Orsini and Orson Welles as Cesare Borgia?
Prince of Foxes (film)    Laura (1944 film)    Pin Up Girl (film)    Anna and the King of Siam (film)

What is a 1936 American Technicolor drama film directed by Henry King, based on Helen Hunt Jackson's 1884 novel Ramona?
Ramona (1936 film)    One in a Million (1936 film)    Stowaway (1936 film)    Dragonwyck (film)

What is a 1932 film based on the 1903 children's classic novel by Kate Douglas Wiggin?
Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm (1932 film)    Street Angel (1928 film)    Lloyd's of London (film)    Greenwich Village (film)

What is a 1938 American musical film directed by Allan Dwan and starring Shirley Temple, Randolph Scott, and Bill Robinson?
Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm (1938 film)    The Poor Little Rich Girl (1936 film)    Under Your Spell (film)    Sing

What is a 1915 American silent film which tells the story of a poor orphan who rises to control the mob, until he meets a woman for whom he wants to change?
Regeneration (1915 film)    Suez (film)    Thunder Birds (1942 film)    State Fair (1933 film)

Whatgaret Field (born November 6, 1946) is an American actress, singer, producer, director, and screenwriter?
Sally    A Walk in the Sun (1945 film)    In the Meantime    A Walk in the Sun (1945 film)

What is a 1939 American musical romance film directed by Sidney Lanfield and starring Sonja Henie, Tyrone Power, Rudy Vallee and Lyle Talbot?
Second Fiddle (1939 film)    Berkeley Square (film)    Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm (1938 film)    Pilgrimage (1933 film)

What is a 1937 screwball romantic comedy, starring Tyrone Power and Loretta Young about a newly-remarried woman who finds her businessman husband boring and runs into her wealthy playboy first husband?
Second Honeymoon (film)    Second Fiddle (1939 film)    Anna and the King of Siam (film)    A Connecticut Yankee (1931 film)

What is a silent film and one of the first films to be nominated for the Academy Award for Best Picture (then called "Best Picture, Production")?
Seventh Heaven (1927 film)    Pin Up Girl (film)    Under Your Spell (film)    Barricade (1939 film)

What is the act of producing musical sounds with the voice, and augments regular speech by the use of both tonality and rhythm?
Sing    Guadalcanal Diary (film)    Pilgrimage (1933 film)    The Pied Piper (1942 film)

What is a movie directed by Henry King and starring Janet Gaynor, Will Rogers, and Lew Ayres?
State Fair (1933 film)    Prince of Foxes (film)    Sally    Liliom (1930 film)

What is a 1945 American film directed by Walter Lang and is a musical adaptation of the 1933 film of the same name, with original music by Rodgers and Hammerstein?
State Fair (1945 film)    Delicious (1931 film)    Dante's Inferno (1935 film)    Greenwich Village (film)

What is a 1936 American musical film directed by William A. Seiter.  The screenplay by William M. Conselman, Nat Perrin, and Arthur Sheekman is based on a story by Samuel Engel?
Stowaway (1936 film)    Dante's Inferno (1935 film)    Berkeley Square (film)    Sally

What is a 1928 silent film about a spirited young woman (Janet Gaynor) who finds herself involved in illegal ways of gaining money to help pay for her ill mother's medicine?
Street Angel (1928 film)    Sunny Side Up (film)    The Pied Piper (1942 film)    Charlie Chan Carries On (film)

What is an American film released on October 28, 1938 by 20th Century Fox, with Darryl F. Zanuck in charge of production, directed by Allan Dwan and starring Tyrone Power, Loretta Young and Annabella?
Suez (film)    Happy Days (1929 film)    Gateway (film)    In the Meantime

What is a Fox Movietone movie musical starring Janet Gaynor and Charles Farrell, with original songs, story, and dialogue by B. G?
Sunny Side Up (film)    Dante's Inferno (1935 film)    Alexander's Ragtime Band (film)    Jesse James (film)

Whatrise: A Song of Two Humans, also known as Sunrise, is a 1927 American silent film directed by German film director F. W?
Sunrise (film)    The Keys of the Kingdom (film)    The Luck of the Irish (1948 film)    Doctors' Wives (1931 film)

What is an English-language remake of the 1922 silent film of the same name?
Tess of the Storm Country (1932 film)    The Little Princess (1939 film)    The Keys of the Kingdom (film)    Happy Days (1929 film)

What is a 1939 mystery-adventure film?
The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes (film)    Girl Trouble (1942 film)    The Iron Horse (film)    Liliom (1930 film)

What is a 1942 swashbuckler Technicolor film by Henry King, based on a novel by Rafael Sabatini, and starring Tyrone Power and Maureen O'Hara?
The Black Swan (film)    Anna and the King of Siam (film)    Wake Up and Dream (film)    Sunrise (film)

What is a 1943 American Twentieth Century Fox Technicolor musical film starring Alice Faye, James Ellison, and Carmen Miranda in a story about a soldier and a nightclub singer?
The Gang's All Here (1943 film)    Charlie Chan Carries On (film)    Heidi (1937 film)    Under the Yoke (film)

What is a 1948 black-and-white thriller film starring Dana Andrews and Gene Tierney.  The film was supposedly based on the memoirs of Igor Gouzenko (1919–1982)?
The Iron Curtain (film)    Leave Her to Heaven {{blue ribbon}} (1945) - Fox's highest grossing film of the 1940s    Greenwich Village (film)    Happy Days (1929 film)

What is a 1924 American silent film directed by John Ford and produced by Fox Film. In 2011, this film was deemed "culturally, historically, or aesthetically significant" by the United States Library of Congress and selected for preservation in the National Film Registry?
The Iron Horse (film)    Coney Island (1943 film)    None But the Brave (1928 film)    Suez (film)

What is a 1944 American film based on the 1941 novel, The Keys of the Kingdom, by A. J?
The Keys of the Kingdom (film)    Hearts in Dixie (film)    The Pied Piper (1942 film)    Greenwich Village (film)

What is a 1939 American drama film directed by Walter Lang.  The screenplay by Ethel Hill and Walter Ferris is loosely based on the novel A Little Princess by Frances Hodgson Burnett?
The Little Princess (1939 film)    Jesse James (film)    Hearts in Dixie (film)    Sunrise (film)

Whatrish is a 1948 film with Tyrone Power, Anne Baxter, Lee J. Cobb, Cecil Kellaway, and Jayne Meadows?
The Luck of the Irish (1948 film)    Hello    Girl Trouble (1942 film)    The Gang's All Here (1943 film)

What is a 1942 film in which an Englishman on vacation in France is caught up in the German invasion of that country, and finds himself taking an ever-growing group of children to safety?
The Pied Piper (1942 film)    Regeneration (1915 film)    Happy Land (film)    The Song of Bernadette (film)

Whattised as The Poor Little Rich Girl, is a 1936 American musical film directed by Irving Cummings?
The Poor Little Rich Girl (1936 film)    Seventh Heaven (1927 film)    Nightmare Alley (film)    State Fair (1945 film)

What is the first film version of W. Somerset Maugham's 1944 novel. It was released in 1946 and stars Tyrone Power, Gene Tierney, John Payne, Anne Baxter, Clifton Webb, Herbert Marshall, supporting cast Lucile Watson, Frank Latimore and Elsa Lanchester?
The Razor's Edge (1946 film)    Sally    Suez (film)    The Gang's All Here (1943 film)

What is a 1943 drama film which tells the true story of Saint Bernadette Soubirous, who from February to July 1858 in Lourdes, France, reported eighteen visions of the Blessed Virgin Mary?
The Song of Bernadette (film)    Captain January (1936 film)    Thin Ice (1937 film)    Hello

What is a 1939 musical comedy film adaptation of Alexandre Dumas, père's novel of the same name?
The Three Musketeers (1939 film)    The Little Princess (1939 film)    Captain January (1936 film)    Bright Eyes (1934 film)

What is a United States comedy/romance film directed by Sidney Lanfield starring Tyrone Power and figure skater Sonja Henie?
Thin Ice (1937 film)    The Razor's Edge (1946 film)    Ramona (1936 film)    Liliom (1930 film)

What is a Technicolor film directed by William A. Wellman and starring Gene Tierney, Preston Foster, and John Sutton?
Thunder Birds (1942 film)    Dante's Inferno (1935 film)    The Razor's Edge (1946 film)    Wake Up and Dream (film)

What can refer t?
Thunderhead    Alexander's Ragtime Band (film)    A Connecticut Yankee (1931 film)    Pin Up Girl (film)

What is a 1918 American silent drama film directed by J. Gordon Edwards and starring Theda Bara?
Under the Yoke (film)    Street Angel (1928 film)    Leave Her to Heaven {{blue ribbon}} (1945) - Fox's highest grossing film of the 1940s    Wilson (film)

What is a 1936 American romantic comedy film with music directed by Otto Preminger. The screenplay by Frances Hyland and Saul Elkins is based on a story by Sy Bartlett and Bernice Mason?
Under Your Spell (film)    Thunder Birds (1942 film)    Jane Eyre (1944 film)    Leave Her to Heaven {{blue ribbon}} (1945) - Fox's highest grossing film of the 1940s

What is a 1946 Technicolor film unrelated to the 1930s musical of the same name.  June Haver and John Payne star?
Wake Up and Dream (film)    Rebecca of Sunnybrook Farm (1938 film)    The Three Musketeers (1939 film)    None But the Brave (1928 film)

What is a thriller film noir directed by Otto Preminger and written by Ben Hecht (under the blacklist pseudonym Lester Barstow) and Andrew Solt, adapted from Guy Endore's novel Methinks the Lady?
Whirlpool (film)    State Fair (1945 film)    Leave Her to Heaven {{blue ribbon}} (1945) - Fox's highest grossing film of the 1940s    Second Fiddle (1939 film)

What is a 1944 biographical film in Technicolor about President Woodrow Wilson. It stars Charles Coburn, Alexander Knox, Geraldine Fitzgerald, Thomas Mitchell and Sir Cedric Hardwicke?
Wilson (film)    The Luck of the Irish (1948 film)    Nightmare Alley (film)    The Razor's Edge (1946 film)

