What is the main armament of the ?
16 Inch    Hybrid codes    Swordfighting    Kickboxing

What is the controlled descent down a rock face using a rope. Climbers use this technique when a cliff or slope is too steep and/or dangerous to descend without protection?
Abseiling    Slow Pitch    Hunter    Sprint football

What is the practice of flying maneuvers involving aircraft attitudes that are not used in normal flight?
Aerobatics    Mountainboarding    Shoot boxing    kung fu

Whatis a Japanese martial art developed by Morihei Ueshiba as a synthesis of his martial studies, philosophy, and religious beliefs?
Aikido    Ba game    Muay Thai    Savate

What is a motorsport that involves airplanes competing over a fixed course, with the winner either returning the shortest time, the one to complete it with the most points, or to come closest to a previously estimated time?
Air racing    Clout archery    Hwa Rang Do    Kickboxing

What is a sport   or recreational activity in which participants eliminate opponents by hitting each other with spherical non-metallic pellets launched via replica firearms?
Airsoft    Artistic billiards    Rodeo    International rules football

What is a team sport. It is played by two teams, eleven players to a side, who advance an oval ball  over a rectangular field that is 120 yards long by 53.3 yards wide and has goalposts at both ends?
American football    Sandboarding    Horse racing    Flight archery

What is a method of fishing by means of an "angle" (fish hook). The hook is usually attached to a fishing line and the line is often attached to a fishing rod?
Angling    Disc golf    Trick shot competition    Sumo

What is a variety of gridiron football played by the Arena Football League (AFL). It is a proprietary game, the rights to which are owned by Gridiron Enterprises, and is played indoors on a smaller field than American or Canadian outdoor football, resulting in a faster and higher-scoring game?
Arena football    Harpastum    Equestrian vaulting    Street football

Whataisie classique, is a carom billiards discipline in which players compete at performing 76 preset shots of varying difficulty?
Artistic billiards    Pato    Taido    Pehlwani

What is a form of competitive indoor cycling in which athletes perform tricks (called exercises) for points on specialized, fixed-gear bikes in a format similar to ballet or gymnastics?
Artistic cycling    Test cricket		 	    Obstacle variations    A Bracciuta

What is a shot played on a billiards table (most often a pool table, though snooker tables are also used), which seems unlikely or impossible or requires significant skill?
Artistic pool    Kuk Sool Won    Artistic billiards    Western Pleasure

What is a sport played between two teams of typically eleven players, though other variations in player numbers such as 5 and 7 are also played, with a spherical ball?
Association football    Haidong Gumdo    Flag football    Harness racing

What is marketed as AFL, after the Australian Football League, the only fully professional  league) is a sport played between two teams of 18 players on the field on either an Australian Football ground, a modified cricket field or similar sized sports venue?
Australian football    Kurash    Eton College    Beach basketball

What is a sport which was started in Australia during World War II when U.S. soldiers wanted to play a form of football against the Australians?
Austus    Zui Quan    Unicycle hockey    Surf fishing

What is a version of medieval football played in Scotland, perhaps most notably in Orkney and the Scottish Borders, around Christmas and New Year?
Ba game    Klootschieten    Metro footy    Dumog

What is a billiards-derived indoor table game, the object of which is to get a number of balls (set at nine in the 19th century) past wooden pins (which act as obstacles) into holes?
Bagatelle    Fistball    Airsoft    Kickball

What is one of the three main Chinese martial arts of the Wudang school, the other two being Taijiquan and Xingyiquan?
Baguazhang    Haidong Gumdo    Duckpin bowling    Hopper ballooning

What is the overarching title of a large array of carom billiards games generally played with two  and a third, red , on a -covered, 5 foot × 10 foot, less table that is divided by  on the cloth into marked regions called ?
Balkline and straight rail    Jianzi    Canadian football    Water basketball

What is a sport native to India. It is a racket game, played with a yellow ball made of wool, on a court of fixed dimensions (12 by 24 metres) divided by a net?
Ball badminton    Polo    Haidong Gumdo    Bocce

What is a defensive style of thaing focusing on animal-based techniques. The earliest meanings of the word were self-discipline, self-development and self-improvement?
Bando    Yubi lakpi    Wakeboarding    Systema

What is a pool (pocket billiards) game that has as its most fundamental requirement that all scoring shots in the game must be made by  a called ball off a  and into a called pocket?
Bank pool    Tapball    Bujinkan    Wireball	

WhatThe sport of banzai skydiving involves throwing a parachute out of a plane and then jumping after it, the aim being to freefall with the parachute, strap it on and deploy the parachute before hitting the ground?
Banzai skydiving    Sandboarding    Powered hang glider    Gungdo

What is a form of billiards which is often thought to be based on the traditional game of bagatelle?
Bar billiards    Limited overs cricket    Pato    Gungdo

What is a rodeo event in which a horse and rider attempt to complete a clover-leaf pattern around preset barrels in the fastest time?
Barrel Racing    Association football    Campdrafting    Beach soccer

What is an eclectic martial art and self-defence method originally developed in England during the years 1898–1902. In 1901 it was immortalised (as "baritsu") by Sir Arthur Conan Doyle, author of the Sherlock Holmes mystery stories?
Bartitsu    Cluster ballooning    Dodge disc    Yoga

What is an activity where participants jump from fixed objects and use a parachute to break their fall?
BASE jumping    Zui Quan    Target archery    San shou

What is a pocket billiards (pool) game suitable for multiple players that borrows phraseology and even some aspects of form from the game of baseball?
Baseball pocket billiards    Longboarding    Fly Fishing    Sumo

What is a team sport, the objective being to shoot a ball through a horizontally positioned basket to score points, while following a set of rules?
Basketball    Bottle pool    Kendo    Friskee

What is a modified version of basketball, played on beaches. It was invented in the USA by Philip Bryant?
Beach basketball    Modern Arnis    Baguazhang    Swordfighting

What is a variant of association football played on a beach or some form of sand?
Beach soccer    A Bracciuta    Sandboarding    Universal football

What is an Olympic team sport played by two teams of two players on a sand court divided by a net?
Beach volleyball    Dressage    Lawn bowling    Friskee

What is the name of a sport, which resembles an aquatic variation of Volleyball. It has originated in Brazil, in the city of Birigüi, in the 60's by Prof?
Biribol    Dirt jumping    Beach soccer    Show Jumping

What is a ball sport belonging to the boules sport family, closely related to bowls and pétanque with a common ancestry from ancient games played in the Roman Empire?
Bocce    Taekwondo    Slow Pitch    Throwball

What is a precision ball sport, similar to bocce, and related to bowls and pétanque. The name  is derived from the Latin word for boss – bottia?
Boccia    Target archery    Sikaran    Gliding

What is a surface water sport in which the surfer rides a bodyboard on the crest, face, and curl of a wave which is carrying the surfer towards the shore?
Bodyboarding    Bicycle Motocross or BMX    Fly Fishing    Bar billiards

What is a Cambodian martial art that includes weapons technics?
Bokator    Eskrima    Disc dog    Unicycling

What is a sport invented in Spain by Filip Eyckmans who developed the concept 2004.  It is similar to volleyball, but also includes elements of football (soccer), gymnastics and capoeira?
Bossaball    Wing Chun    Polo    Kickball

What is a hybrid billiards game combining aspects of both carom billiards and pocket billiards?
Bottle pool    Hooverball    Hwa Rang Do    Netball

What is a style of rock climbing undertaken without a rope and normally limited to very short climbs over a padded mat called a crash pad or bouldering mat so that a fall will not result in serious injury?
Bouldering    Adi Murai    Shaolin kung fu    Polo

Whataise) is a popular French form of boule?
Boule lyonnaise    Newcomb ball    Boccia    Mountaineering

What is a pool game often used as a training . The game borrows aspects of ten-pin bowling. The game is divided into ten frames where a player gets a maximum of two innings to  ten balls?
Bowlliards    Kneeboarding    Lethwei    Varpa

What is a sport in which the objective is to roll biased balls so that they stop close to a smaller ball called a  "jack" or "kitty"?
Bowls    Indoor soccer    Slamball    Novuss

Whatlism, prize fighting, the sweet science or in Greek pygmachia) is a martial art and combat sport in which two people engage in a contest of strength, speed, reflexes, endurance and will by throwing punches  with gloved hands?
Boxing    Shuffleboard    Wing Tsun    Bokator

What is an international Ninja organization based in Japan and headed by Masaaki Hatsumi?
Bujinkan    Danish longball    Biribol    Bank pool

What is a pocket billiards game played on an octagonal or rectangular table fitted with an array of fixed cushioned obstacles, called bumpers, at the center of its surface?
Bumper pool    Sport climbing    Powerchair Football    MCMAP

What is the Central Asian sport played among Kazakhs, Afghans, Uzbeks, Hazaras, Tajiks, Kyrgyz, Turkmens and Pashtuns?
Buzkashi    Jokgu    Air racing    Boxing

What is a unique Australian sport involving a horse and rider working cattle. The riding style is like that of Western riding and the event is somewhat related to the American events such as cutting, working cow horse, team penning, and ranch sorting?
Campdrafting    Dressage    Endurance riding    Sprint football

What is a form of gridiron football played  in Canada in which two teams of 12 players each compete for territorial control of a field of play  long and  wide attempting to advance a pointed prolate spheroid ball into the opposing team's scoring area (end zone)?
Canadian football    Volata    American football    Artistic pool

What is a variation of bowling that is played primarily in the Canadian Maritime provinces, Ontario, Quebec, and the New England states of Maine, Massachusetts, New Hampshire, and Vermont?
Candlepin bowling    Horse racing    Surfing    Beach volleyball

Whatlish cap-oh-ay-ra)) is a Brazilian martial art that combines elements of dance and music?
Capoeira    Shorinji Kempo    Cuju    Goaltimate

What is the overarching title of a family of billiards games generally played on cloth-covered, 5 by 10 feet (approximately 1.5 × 3 m) pocketless tables, which often feature heated slate beds?
Carom billiards    Ball badminton    Dodgeball    Peteca

What is a two-wheeled, human-powered land vehicle that is closely related to the skateboard and the snakeboard?
Casterboarding    Equitation    Fujian White Crane    Chilean rodeo

What is a classical hybrid grappling style that was developed in Britain circa 1870 by Mr. J. G?
Catch wrestling    Ice Climbing    Peteca    Kurash

What is a competitive event similar to rodeo and was developed from animal husbandry practices used on the haciendas of old Mexico?
Charreada    Jeet Kune Do    Laser tag    Durango boot

What is a hybrid sport that combines chess with boxing in alternating rounds. The sport was invented by French artist and filmmaker Enki Bilal in his comic book Froid Équateur in 1992. The first real event of chess-boxing was organized by Dutch artist Iepe Rubingh in 2003. Chess boxing is a fast growing sport, with large followings in Berlin and London, where most events take place?
Chessboxing    Skysurfing    Savate    Laser tag

What is a traditional sport in Chile. It was declared the national sport in 1962. It has since thrived, especially in the more rural areas of the country?
Chilean rodeo    Horseball    Mountain unicycling    Shurikenjutsu

What is the traditional sport of Burma (Myanmar).  is a combination of sport and dance, a team sport with no opposing team?
Chinlone    Angling    Laser tag    Rock fishing

What is a form of archery in which archers shoot arrows at a flag (known as "the Clout") from a relatively long distance and score points depending on how close each arrow lands to the flag?
Clout archery    Kemari    Footvolley    Surfing

What is a form of ballooning where a harness attaches a balloonist to a cluster of helium-inflated rubber balloons?
Cluster ballooning    Skateboarding    Modern Arnis    Kinomichi

Whatlish and Australian English), or crab football (British English), is an informal sport for two teams?
Crab soccer    Taido    American football    Volleyball

What is an informal variant on football originating spontaneously in different parts of the world?
Cubbies    Kickball    A Brazzos    Shootfighting

What is an ancient ball game with similarities to association football. It is seen by FIFA as the earliest form of football for which there is evidence, being first mentioned as a military training exercise in the 2nd-3rd century BCE?
Cuju    Sikaran    Bounceball    Swordfighting

What is an unincorporated community in Jennings Township, Crawford County, Indiana. It is a populated place that is not incorporated and has no legal boundaries?
Curby    Horse racing    Kinomichi    Fast Pitch

What is a sport in which players slide stones across a sheet of ice towards a target area which is segmented into four rings?
Curling    Fujian White Crane    Air racing    Futsal

What is a carom billiards discipline generally played on a cloth-covered, 5 foot × 10 foot, pocketless table with two cue balls and a third red-colored ball?
Cushion caroms    Northern Praying Mantis    Snooker plus    Shaolin kung fu

Whatnish Longball (sometimes called Swedish longball) is a bat-and-ball game founded in Denmark.  It is popular in British secondary schools, and is played recreationally by scouts, the Air Training Corps and by the British Navy and Australian Navy?
Danish longball    Lawn bowling    Bouldering    Eventing

What is basketball played by deaf people.  Sign language is used to communicate whistle blows and communication between players?
Deaf basketball    Kenjutsu    Zui Quan    Dodgeball

What is one of the names given to the practice of riding bikes over cement type jumps of dirt or soil and becoming airborne?
Dirt jumping    Freestyle BMX    Rock Climbing    Powered paragliding

What is the more generic name for what is commonly called  Frisbee dog.  In disc dog competitions, dogs and their human flying disc throwers compete in events such as distance catching and somewhat choreographed freestyle catching?
Disc dog    Powerchair Football    Mixed martial arts    Twenty20	

What is a flying disc game in which individual players throw a flying disc at a target. According to the Professional Disc Golf Association, "The object of the game is to traverse a course from beginning to end in the fewest number of throws of the disc." The number of disc golf courses has more than doubled in 8 years from 2000 to 2008. The game is played in about 40 countries around the world?
Disc golf    Snowkiting    Klootschieten    Skateboarding

Whatrisbee after the brand name) is a flying disc game, based on dodgeball but using a disc in place of the ball or balls?
Dodge disc    Rec footy    Matball    Novuss

What is a game in which players on two teams try to throw large balls at each other while avoiding being hit themselves?
Dodgeball    Mountaineering    Wallyball    Kuk Sool Won

Whatdisc games are games played with flying discs (sometimes called by the trademarked name Frisbees)?
Double disc court    Krav Maga    Aikido    MCMAP

What is a time trial event held on a steep, rough terrain that often features jumps, rock gardens and other obstacles?
Downhill mountain biking    Pradal Serey    16 Inch    Balkline and straight rail

What is a competitive equestrian sport, defined by the International Equestrian Federation as "the highest expression of horse training", where "horse and rider are expected to perform from memory a series of predetermined movements."  Competitions are held at all levels from amateur to the World Equestrian Games?
Dressage    Indoor cricket    Pradal Serey    Klootschieten

What is a variation of 10-pin bowling. The balls used in duckpin bowling are 4-3/4 in (12 cm) to 5 in (12.7 cm) in diameter (which is slightly larger than a softball), weigh 3 lb 6 oz  (1.5 kg) to 3 lb 12 oz (1.7 kg) each, and lack finger holes?
Duckpin bowling    Football tennis    Taekwondo    Kurash

What is the Filipino style of wrestling while standing upright and refers to the grappling aspect of Filipino martial arts?
Dumog    Beach volleyball    Cuju    Hybrid codes

What is a competitive, non-contact sport that makes use of a flying disc (known popularly by the trademark Frisbee), somewhat similar to Ultimate?
Durango boot    Chilean rodeo    Gatka    Ancient games

What is the Modern Egyptian term for a traditional form of Egyptian folk dance involving a wooden stick, also known as "stick dance" or "cane dance"?
Egyptian stick fencing    Pradal Serey    Boule lyonnaise    Eskrima

What is an equestrian sport based on controlled long-distance races.  It is one of the international competitions recognized by the FEI?
Endurance riding    Ba game    Banzai skydiving    Metro footy

Whattish colonies and in Great Britain where it originated, is a game for two players or teams?
English billiards    Water basketball    Netball    Yukigassen

Whatlish pleasure is generic term for a number of different English riding classes seen at horse shows in the United States, where the horse is ridden in either hunt seat or saddle seat tack?
English Pleasure    Kronum    Polo    International rules football

What (Greek: ἐπίσκυρος) was an ancient Greek ball game also called έφηβική ephebike, "adolescence", and ἐπίκοινος epikoinos, "commonball")?
Episkyros    Shaolin kung fu    Aikido    Surfing

What is most often described as gymnastics and dance on horseback?
Equestrian vaulting    Casterboarding    Adi Murai    BoÃŸeln

What is the art or practice of horse riding or horsemanshi?
Equitation    Shidokan    Sprint football    Yukigassen

Whatnis and Kali are umbrella terms for the traditional martial arts of the Philippines ("Filipino Martial Arts," or FMA) that emphasize weapon-based fighting with sticks, knives and other bladed weapons, and various improvised weapons?
Eskrima    Campdrafting    Trick shot competition    Aikido

What is a British independent boarding school located in Eton, near Windsor in England?
Eton College    Boule lyonnaise    Flutterguts    Rock fishing

What is an equestrian event where a single horse and rider combination compete against other combinations across the three disciplines of dressage, cross-country, and show jumping?
Eventing    Gaelic football    Rec footy    Equestrian vaulting

What is a form of softball played commonly by women and men, though coed fast-pitch leagues also exist?
Fast Pitch    Footbag net    Juttejutsu    Casterboarding

What is typically divided into olympic fencing, Classical fencing and historical fencing,. The sport of fencing (commonly called olympic fencing or competitive fencing) is divided into three weapons: foil, sabre and épée?
Fencing    Modern Arnis    Unicycle trials    Slow Pitch

Whatdistance, often in woodland and rough terrain?
Field archery    Cushion caroms    Jianzi    Volata

What is a sport of European origin. It is similar to volleyball in that players try to hit a ball over a net?
Fistball    Yubi lakpi    Savate    Gungdo

What is a version of American football or Canadian football where the basic rules of the game are similar to those of the mainstream game (often called "tackle football" for contrast), but instead of tackling players to the ground, the defensive team must remove a flag or flag belt from the ball carrier ("deflagging") to end a down?
Flag football    Ball badminton    Ultralight aviation    Aba Guresi

What is the art, practice, or skill of propelling arrows with the use of a bow, from Latin arcus. Historically, archery has been used for hunting and combat, while in modern times, its main use is that of a recreational activity?
Flight archery    Austus    Muay Thai    Surf fishing

Whatdisc (sometimes guts Frisbee in reference to the trademarked brand name) is a disc game inspired by dodgeball, involving teams throwing a flying disc (rather than balls) at members of the opposing team?
Flutterguts    Punchball    Unicycle trials    Chinlone

Whatfishing is an angling method in which an artificial "fly" is used to catch fish. The fly is cast using a fly rod, reel, and specialized weighted line?
Fly Fishing    Eventing    Jokgu    Kurash

What is a sport in which players kick a footbag over a five-foot-high net. Players may use only the feet?
Footbag net    Angling    Kemari    Dirt jumping

Whatnis, also known as futnet (in German [http://de.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fu%C3%9Fballtennis Fußballtennis], in French [http://fr.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tennis-ballon tennis-ballon] or futnet, in Hungarian [http://hu.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%C3%A1btenisz lábtenisz], in Czech and Slovak [http://cs.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nohejbal nohejbal] etc.) is a sport originating in 1920s in Central Europe?
Football tennis    Durango boot    Twenty20	    Shuffleboard

Whatnis, also known as futnet (in German [http://de.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fu%C3%9Fballtennis Fußballtennis], in French [http://fr.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tennis-ballon tennis-ballon] or futnet, in Hungarian [http://hu.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%C3%A1btenisz lábtenisz], in Czech and Slovak [http://cs.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nohejbal nohejbal] etc.) is a sport originating in 1920s in Central Europe?
Football tennis    Taekwondo    Model aircraft    Unicycle trials

What is a sport which combines aspects of beach volleyball and association football (also known as soccer in some English-speaking countries)?
Footvolley    Road bicycle racing    Casterboarding    Candlepin bowling

What is a sport which combines aspects of beach volleyball and association football (also known as soccer in some English-speaking countries)?
Footvolley    Double disc court    Bottle pool    Bartitsu

What is a discipline of mountain biking closely related to downhill cycling and dirt jumping focused on tricks, style, and technical trail features?
Freeride mountain biking    Association football    Wheelchair basketball    Lethwei

What is a synonym for BMX stunt riding, a sport branch that hails from extreme sports. It consists of five disciplines: street, park, vert, trails, and  flatland?
Freestyle BMX    Carom billiards    Shootfighting    Bartitsu

Whatdisc games are games played with flying discs (sometimes called by the trademarked name Frisbees)?
Friskee    Muay Thai    Bartitsu    Yubi lakpi

What is a Southern Chinese martial art which originated in Fujian (福建) province and is now practiced throughout the world?
Fujian White Crane    Abseiling    Bar billiards    Sanshou

What is a variant of association football that is played on a smaller pitch and mainly played indoors?
Futsal    Surfing    Powered paragliding    Silambam

Whatrish: Peil Ghaelach; short name Peil or Caid), commonly referred to as football or Gaelic, is a sport played between two teams of 15 players on a rectangular grass pitch?
Gaelic football    Bank pool    Air racing    A Brazzos

What is a weapon-based martial art associated with the Punjab region. It has also traditionally been practiced by other ethno-cultural groups in India and Pakistan?
Gatka    Pato    Kurash    Horse racing

What is a recreational activity and competitive air sport in which pilots fly unpowered aircraft known as gliders or sailplanes using naturally occurring currents of rising air in the atmosphere to remain airborne?
Gliding    Lawn bowling    Western Pleasure    Lethwei

What is the Old Norse word that covers several types of Scandinavian folk wrestlin?
Glima    Buzkashi    Bicycle Motocross or BMX    Bokator

What is a half-court disc game derived from ultimate, similar to hot box. The object is to score points by throwing a flying disc to a teammate in a small scoring area, through a large semicircular hoop called the goal?
Goaltimate    Jianzi    Goaltimate    Samoa Rules

What is football primarily played in the United States and Canada?
Gridiron football    Sport fishing    Snooker plus    Indoor soccer

What is a water buffalo horn-based composite reflex bow, standardized about 1900 AD from the variety of such weapons in earlier use?
Gungdo    Shuai Jiao    Obstacle variations    Wiffleball

What is a typical Anglo-Indian expression, which is derived from the Hindi-Urdu word Jamat-khana, is an Indian term which referred to a place of assembly?
Gymkhana    Pehlwani    Beach volleyball    Savate

What (Haedong Gumdo, 海東劍道 "Korean way of the sword") arose in April of 1983 as the Hai Dong Gumdo Association with its main office in Seocho-gu, Seoul and, in November, 1996 was incorporated as the World Hai Dong Gumdo Federation (WHDGF)?
Haidong Gumdo    Indoor archery    Hybrid codes    Hapkido

What is an air sport in which a pilot flies a light and non-motorized foot-launch aircraft called a hang glider that is of a delta wing design?
Hang gliding    Dodge disc    Downhill mountain biking    Sport climbing

What is a dynamic and also  eclectic Korean martial art?
Hapkido    Akroteri Punching    Adi Murai    Trick shot competition

What is a form of horse racing in which the horses race at a specific gait (a trot or a pace)?
Harness racing    Boule lyonnaise    Newcomb ball    Bujinkan

What, also known as Harpustum, was a form of ball game played in the Roman Empire. The Romans also referred to it as the small ball game?
Harpastum    Campdrafting    Muay Thai    Mountaineering

What is a code of football played between two teams of eleven players, each attempting to win by scoring more bases (goals) than their opponent?
Harrow Football    Powered hang glider    Kickball    A Bracciuta

What is an outdoor activity which consists of walking in natural environments, often in mountainous or other scenic terrain?
Hiking    16 Inch    Abseiling    Noodling

What is a medicine ball game invented by President Herbert Hoover's personal physician to help keep then-President Hoover fit?
Hooverball    Western Pleasure    Bokator    San shou

What is an equestrian sport that has a long history. Archaeological records indicate that horse racing occurred in ancient Greece, Babylon, Syria, and Egypt?
Horse racing    Durango boot    Carom billiards    English billiards

What is a game played on horseback where a ball is handled and points are scored by shooting it through a high net (approximately 1.5m×1.5m)?
Horseball    Dressage    BASE jumping    Arena football

What is an aircraft belonging to the human-powered vehicles. It is powered by direct human energy and the force of gravity; the thrust provided by the human may be the only source; however, a hang glider that is partially powered by pilot power is a human-powered aircraft where the flight path can be enhanced more than if the hang glider had not been assisted by human power?
Human powered aircraft    Snooker plus    Human powered aircraft    Twenty20	

What is the practice of pursuing any living thing, usually wildlife or feral animals, by humans for food, recreation, or trade?
Hunter    Egyptian stick fencing    Chilean rodeo    Basketball

What is a Korean martial art that was created by Joo Bang Lee and his brother Joo Sang Lee. This martial art teaches fighting techniques, weapons, spiritual training, intellectual enhancement, and artistic pursuits?
Hwa Rang Do    Aerobatics    Equestrian vaulting    Rec footy

What is one of the Japanese koryū martial art disciplines in the education of the classical warrior (bushi)?
Iaijutsu    Sepak takraw    Bossaball    Baseball pocket billiards

What is the activity of ascending inclined ice formations. Usually, ice climbing refers to roped and protected climbing of features such as icefalls, frozen waterfalls, and cliffs and rock slabs covered with ice refrozen from flows of water?
Ice Climbing    Cushion caroms    Eventing    Sikaran

What was contested at the 2009 Asian Indoor Games in Hai Phong, Vietnam from 3 November to 6 November 2009. The competition took place at Haiphong Youth Gymnasium?
Indoor archery    Laser tag    Parachuting    Casterboarding

What is a variant of and shares many basic concepts with cricket. The game is most often played between two teams each consisting of six or eight players?
Indoor cricket    Surfing    Balkline and straight rail    Biribol

What is a variation of netball, played exclusively indoors, in which the playing court is surrounded on each side and overhead by a net?
Indoor netball    Wheelchair basketball    Pehlwani    Baseball pocket billiards

What arena soccer, or six-a-side football in the United Kingdom, is a game derived from association football adapted for play in an indoor arena such as a turf-covered ice hockey arena or skating rink?
Indoor soccer    Baseball pocket billiards    Kalarippayattu    Episkyros

Whatmise rules in Ireland) is a team sport consisting of a hybrid of football codes, which was developed to facilitate international representative matches between Australian rules football players and Gaelic football players?
International rules football    Pradal Serey    Wireball	    Baguazhang

What is an eclectic/hybrid system and philosophy of life founded by martial artist Bruce Lee  with direct, non classical, and straightforward movements?
Jeet Kune Do    Krav Maga    Sikaran    Unicycle basketball

What is a traditional Asian game in which players aim to keep a heavily weighted shuttlecock in the air by using their bodies, apart from the hands, unlike in similar games peteca and indiaca?
Jianzi    Swing boarding    Freeride mountain biking    Capoeira

What is a Portuguese martial art which developed in the northern regions of Portugal (Minho and Trás-os-Montes), focusing on the use of a staff of fixed measures and characteristics?
Jogo do Pau    Dodgeball    Three sided football    Hapkido

What is a sport which combines aspects of volleyball and football (soccer?
Jokgu    Keep Away    Pato    Chinlone

Whatis a modern martial art, combat and Olympic sport created in Japan in 1882 by Jigoro Kano. Its most prominent feature is its competitive element, where the objective is to either throw or takedown an opponent to the ground, immobilize or otherwise subdue an opponent with a pin, or force an opponent to submit with a joint lock or a choke?
Judo    Fast Pitch    Dressage    Taekkyeon

What is a Japanese martial art and a method of close combat for defeating an armed and armored opponent in which one uses no weapon or only a short weapon?
Jujutsu    Kinomichi    Sandboarding    Street football

Whatis the Japanese martial art of using the Japanese weapon jutte (also known as jitte).  was evolved mainly for the law enforcement officers of the Edo period to enable non-lethal disarmament and apprehension of criminals who were usually carrying a sword?
Juttejutsu    Western Pleasure    Savate    Laser tag

What is a hybrid martial art that combines Western Boxing, Judo, Jujutsu, Kenpo Karate, Eskrima, Tang Soo Do, and Kung Fu?
Kajukenbo    Bar billiards    Hiking    Aikido

What is an Indian martial art from the southern state of Kerala. One of the oldest fighting systems in existence, it was originally practiced in northern and central parts of Kerala and the Tulunadu region of Karnataka?
Kalarippayattu    Unicycle trials    Subak    Sipa

What is a martial art developed in the Ryukyu Islands in what is now Okinawa, Japan. It was developed partially from the indigenous martial arts of Ryukyu Islands called  and from Chinese kenpo?
Karate    Snowboarding    Bumper pool    San shou

WhatDish, or Pickle in the Middle, is a children's game in which two or more players must pass a ball to one another, while a player in the middle attempts to intercept it?
Keep Away    Spearfishing    Football tennis    Field archery

What is a pocket billiards game played on a standard pool table using fifteen numbered markers called peas or pills, and a standard set of sixteen pool balls?
Kelly pool    Ninjutsu    Charreada    Goaltimate

What is a ball game that was popular in Japan during the Heian Period.  has been revived in modern times?
Kemari    Candlepin bowling    Gliding    Western Pleasure

What is a modern Japanese  martial art/sport, which descended from traditional swordsmanship (kenjutsu) and uses bamboo swords (Shinai), and protective armor?
Kendo    Medieval football    English billiards    Shootfighting

Whatis the umbrella term for all traditional (koryū) schools of Japanese swordsmanship, in particular those that predate the Meiji Restoration and the modern styles of kendo and iaido that emerged from the traditional schools in the late 19th century?
Kenjutsu    Slopestyle    Friskee    Horse racing

What is a playground game and league game, similar to baseball, invented in the United States in the first half of the 20th Century?
Kickball    Twenty20	    Paragliding    Gungdo

What is a playground game and league game, similar to baseball, invented in the United States in the first half of the 20th Century?
Kickball    Curling    Modern Arnis    Silambam

What is a group of martial arts and stand-up combat sports based on kicking and punching, historically developed from Karate, Muay Thai and Western boxing?
Kickboxing    Jeet Kune Do    Sanshou    Disc dog

Whatis a martial art in the tradition of budō, developed from the Japanese art aikido by Masamichi Noro and founded in Paris, France, in 1979. Masamichi Noro was one of the live-in students (uchideshi) of Morihei Ueshiba, the founder of aikido?
Kinomichi    Kneeboarding    Iaijutsu    Footvolley

Whatlish) is a sport in the Netherlands and East Frisia, Germany. In the game, participants try to throw a ball (the kloot) as far as they can?
Klootschieten    Tent pegging    Volata    Kickball

What is an aquatic sport where the participant is towed on a buoyant, convex, and hydrodynamically shaped board at a planing speed, most often behind a motorboat?
Kneeboarding    Hooverball    Indoor netball    Sanshou

What is a mixed gender team sport, with similarities to netball and basketball. A team consists of eight players; four female and four male?
Korfball    Pradal Serey    Pradal Serey    Fencing

What is a non-competitive tactical self-defense system developed in Israel that consists of a wide combination of techniques sourced from boxing, Muay Thai, Wing Chun, Judo, jiu-jitsu, wrestling, and grappling, along with realistic fight training?
Krav Maga    Test cricket		 	    Reining    Ba game

What is a sport which was invented in 2008 by Bill Gibson in Villanova, Pennsylvania. It is played only in the United States, with professional league games taking place in Philadelphia?
Kronum    Kalarippayattu    Flutterguts    Footvolley

What is a Korean martial arts system founded by Suh In-Hyuk (; the Kuk Sa Nim or Grandmaster) in 1958. The name  translates to "National Martial Art Association" and despite often being shortened to 'Kuk Sool,' the name kuk sool (국술; 國術) is a non-trade marked name used to denote similar Korean martial arts developed prior to or about the same time as the formation of ?
Kuk Sool Won    Taekwondo    Goaltimate    Iaijutsu

What are a number of fighting styles that have developed over the centuries in China?
kung fu    Snooker plus    Equestrian vaulting    Artistic pool

What is the Turkic term for "wrestling" (from Old Turkic keriš, c.f?
Kurash    Mountaineering    Aba Guresi    Casterboarding

What is a team or individual sport or recreational activity where players attempt to score points by tagging targets, typically with a hand-held infrared-emitting targeting device?
Laser tag    Gridiron football    MCMAP    Model aircraft

What is a sport in which the objective is to roll biased balls so that they stop close to a smaller ball called a  "jack" or "kitty"?
Lawn bowling    Wallyball    Footvolley    Netball

What is an unarmed Burmese martial art. It is similar to related styles of Indochinese kickboxing, namely Muay Thai from Thailand, pradal serey from Cambodia, Muay Lao from Laos and tomoi from Malaysia?
Lethwei    Ba game    Bar billiards    Shurikenjutsu

WhatList A cricket, is a version of the sport of cricket in which a match is generally completed in one day, whereas Test and first-class matches can take up to five days to complete?
Limited overs cricket    Airsoft    Equestrian vaulting    Iaijutsu

What is the act of riding on a longboard skateboard. A longboard is greater in size (both length and width) than its smaller counterpart, the skateboard, and has more stability, traction and durability due to lower wheel durometers?
Longboarding    Indoor cricket    Bounceball    Streetball

What is a collective name given to a number of traditional Indigenous Australian recreational pastimes believed to have been played at gatherings and celebrations of up to fifty players?
Marn Grook    Aerobatics    Beach soccer    Powered paragliding

What areas it is known as Big Base, is a sport, usually played indoors but also sometimes outdoors, played in schools throughout the United States?
Matball    Baseball pocket billiards    Abseiling    Water basketball

What areas it is known as Big Base, is a sport, usually played indoors but also sometimes outdoors, played in schools throughout the United States?
Matball    Fistball    Shorinji Kempo    Dodgeball

What is a combat system developed by the United States Marine Corps to combine existing and new hand-to-hand and close quarters combat (CQC) techniques with morale and team-building functions and instruction in the Warrior Ethos?
MCMAP    Horse racing    Modern Arnis    Football tennis

What is a modern term sometimes used for a wide variety of localised football games which were invented and played in Europe of the Middle Ages?
Medieval football    Snowboarding    Sandboarding    Bokator

What is a modified version of Australian rules football rules played on gridiron football, rugby or Association football fields, predominantly in the United States of America?
Metro footy    Equestrian vaulting    English Pleasure    Unicycling

What is a full contact combat sport that allows the use of both striking and grappling techniques, both standing and on the ground, from a variety of other combat sports?
Mixed martial arts    Fast Pitch    Akroteri Punching    Tapball

What are flying or non-flying small sized replicas of existing or imaginary aircraft using a variety of materials including paper, plastic, metal, synthetic resins, wood, foam and fibreglass?
Model aircraft    Bodyboarding    Savate    Flutterguts

What is the system of Filipino martial arts founded by the late Remy Presas as a self-defense system?
Modern Arnis    Road bicycle racing    Ssireum    Mountainboarding

What is the folk wrestling style of Mongols in Mongolia, Inner Mongolia (China) and other regions?
Mongolian wrestling    Eton College    Indoor soccer    Akroteri Punching

What is an adventure sport that consists of traversing rough terrain on a unicycle.  ('muni') is undertaken on similar terrain to mountain biking?
Mountain unicycling    Trick shot competition    Horseball    Cubbies

What is a well established if little-known action sport, derived from snowboarding?
Mountainboarding    Muay Thai    Skysurfing    Campdrafting

What is the sport, hobby or profession of hiking, skiing, and climbing mountains?
Mountaineering    Gliding    Kelly pool    Yukigassen

What is a combat sport from the muay martial arts of Thailand that uses stand-up striking along with various clinching techniques?
Muay Thai    Deaf basketball    Austus    Sprint football

Whatis the  Japanese martial art of wielding the . This is a weapon resembling the medieval European glaive?
Naginatajutsu    Flight archery    Krav Maga    Shurikenjutsu

What is a ball sport played by two teams of seven players. Its development, derived from early versions of basketball, began in England in the 1890s?
Netball    Duckpin bowling    Dodgeball    Gatka

What is a ball game played as a variation of volleyball?
Newcomb ball    Ninjutsu    Shaolin kung fu    A Bracciuta

What is the martial art, strategy, and tactics of unconventional warfare and guerrilla warfare as well as the art of espionage purportedly practiced by the shinobi (commonly known outside of Japan as ninja)?
Ninjutsu    Kickball    Boccia    BoÃŸeln

What is fishing for catfish using only bare hands, practiced primarily in the southern United States?
Noodling    Water basketball    Tang Soo Do    Gungdo

What is a style of Chinese martial arts, sometimes called Shandong Praying Mantis after its province of origin?
Northern Praying Mantis    Footvolley    Harpastum    Candlepin bowling

What is a two-player (or four-player, doubles) game of physical skill which is closely related to carrom and pocket billiards?
Novuss    Freeride mountain biking    Abseiling    English Pleasure

What is a form of limited overs cricket, played between two teams with international status, in which each team faces a fixed number of overs, usually fifty?
One Day International	    Cubbies    Kickboxing    Bowls

What is a sport in which players compete, in teams or individually, to eliminate opponents by tagging them with capsules containing water soluble dye and gelatin shell outside (referred to as paintballs) propelled from a device called a paintball marker (commonly referred to as a paintball gun)?
Paintball    Bicycle Motocross or BMX    Charreada    Volata

What ( or ) was a martial art introduced into the Greek Olympic Games in 648 BC and founded as a blend of boxing and wrestling but with scarcely any rules?
Pankration    Wiffleball    Unicycle trials    Slamball

What is the action sport of exiting an aircraft and returning to earth with the aid of gravity while using a parachute to slow down during the terminal part of the descent?
Parachuting    Universal football    Bagatelle    Wing Chun

What is the recreational and competitive adventure sport of flying paragliders: lightweight, free-flying, foot-launched glider aircraft with no rigid primary structure?
Paragliding    Association football    Spearfishing    Catch wrestling

What is volleyball for disabled athletes entered the Paralympic Games as a demonstration sport for amputees in 1976 in Toronto Canada and played as a medal sport thereafter?
Paralympic volleyball    Matball    Hunter    Matball

What is a game played on horseback that combines elements from polo and basketball?
Pato    Cuju    Punchball    Sandboarding

What is a form of wrestling from South Asia?
Pehlwani    Airsoft    Haidong Gumdo    English Pleasure

What is an umbrella term  martial arts  in Indonesia parenthood from Bokator in Cambodia?
Pencak Silat    Barrel Racing    Pato    Trick shot competition

What is a traditional sport in Brazil, played with a "hand shuttlecock" from indigenous origins and reputed to be as old as the country itself?
Peteca    Slamball    Aikido    Bar billiards

What is a team sport played on horseback in which the objective is to score goals against an opposing team?
Polo    Snowkiting    Team penning    Artistic billiards

What is a competitive team sport for people with disabilities who use power wheelchairs?
Powerchair Football    Kronum    BASE jumping    Abseiling

What is a powered hang glider harness with a motor and propeller in pusher configuration?
Powered hang glider    Mountain unicycling    Bottle pool    Association football

What is a form of ultralight aviation where the pilot wears a motor on his back (a paramotor) which provides enough thrust to take off using an adapted paraglider or [http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Paramotor_Reflex_Wing_Profile paramotor wing]?
Powered paragliding    Hybrid codes    Pehlwani    Snowkiting

What is an unarmed martial art from Cambodia. In Khmer the word pradal means fighting or boxing and serey means free?
Pradal Serey    Chinlone    Model aircraft    Austus

What is a ball game played as a variation of volleyball?
Prisoner Ball    Bounceball    Three sided football    Austus

What is a sport spawned by and similar to baseball, but without a pitcher, catcher, or ba?
Punchball    Capoeira    Skimboarding    Wingsuit flying

What is a non-contact version of the Australian rules football game sanctioned by the Australian Football League?
Rec footy    Ninjutsu    Biribol    Flight archery

What is a western riding competition for horses where the riders guide the horses through a precise pattern of circles, spins, and stops?
Reining    Matball    Casterboarding    Biribol

What is a boardsport in which the participant lies prone on their board with fins on their feet for propulsion and steering?
Riverboarding    Taekwondo    Aikido    Laser tag

What is a bicycle racing sport held on paved roads. The term "road racing" is usually applied to events where competing riders start simultaneously (unless riding a handicap event) with the winner being the first to the line at the end of the course (individual and team time trials are another form of cycle racing on roads)?
Road bicycle racing    Airsoft    Bujinkan    Three sided football

What is an activity in which participants climb up, down or across natural rock formations or artificial rock walls?
Rock Climbing    Road bicycle racing    Bicycle Motocross or BMX    Campdrafting

What is fishing from rocky outcrops into the sea. It is a popular pastime in Australia and New Zealand?
Rock fishing    Unicycle hockey    Klootschieten    Rodeo

What is a competitive sport which arose out of the working practices of cattle herding in Spain, Mexico, and later the United States, Canada, South America and Australia?
Rodeo    Canadian football    Wing Tsun    Egyptian stick fencing

What is a cue sport that has several differences from Western pool, although game play is still dominated by attempts to  () billiard balls?
Russian pyramid    Kickball    Slamball    Akroteri Punching

What is a game derived from Australian rules football and rugby union that is occasionally played in Samoa?
Samoa Rules    Twenty20	    Speed pool    Snowkiting

What is a Chinese hand-to-hand self-defense system and combat sport?
San shou    Cubbies    Volleyball    Shuffleboard

What is a board sport similar to snowboardin?
Sandboarding    Streetluge    Mountaineering    Deaf basketball

What is a Chinese hand-to-hand self-defense system and combat sport?
Sanshou    Beach volleyball    Carom billiards    Sikaran

Whataise,  French boxing, French kickboxing or French footfighting, is a traditional French martial art which uses the hands and feet as weapons combining elements of western boxing with graceful kicking techniques?
Savate    San shou    Wing Chun    Trick shot competition

What is a sport native to the Malay-Thai Peninsula?
Sepak takraw    Tent pegging    Sanshou    BoÃŸeln

WhatShaolin Kung Fu refers to a collection of Chinese martial arts that claim affiliation with the Shaolin Monastery?
Shaolin kung fu    Kickball    Harpastum    Kajukenbo

Whatis the main branch of Shorin-ryū style of Okinawan karate, started by Katsuya Miyahira, Hanshi 10th Dan?
Shidokan    Ultralight aviation    Kickball    Jianzi

What is both a combat sport and a stand-up fighting promotion company based in Tokyo, Japan?
Shoot boxing    Target archery    Danish longball    Gliding

What is a combat sport and martial art, with competitions governed by the International  Association (ISFA)?
Shootfighting    Freeride mountain biking    A Bracciuta    Spearfishing

Whatdiscipline) with many similarities to Shaolin kungfu, including using the same first three kanji?
Shorinji Kempo    Reining    Basketball    Fly Fishing

What is a member of a family of English riding equestrian events that also includes dressage, eventing, hunters, and equitation?
Show Jumping    Equestrian vaulting    Pato    Goaltimate

What is the general Mandarin Chinese term for wrestling. As a generic name, it may be used to cover various styles of wrestling practised in China in the form of a martial arts system or a sport?
Shuai Jiao    Fencing    Paragliding    Bank pool

Whatcisely deck shuffleboard, and also known  as shuffle-board, shovelboard, shovel-board and shove-board [archaic], is a game in which players use broom-shaped paddles to push weighted pucks, sending them gliding down a narrow and elongated court, with the purpose of having them come to rest within a marked scoring area?
Shuffleboard    Slamball    Capoeira    Matball

Whatis a general term describing the traditional Japanese martial arts of throwing shuriken, which are small, hand-held weapons used primarily by the shinobi in feudal Japan, such as metal spikes bō shuriken, circular plates of metal known as hira shuriken, and knives (tantō)?
Shurikenjutsu    Pehlwani    Model aircraft    Unicycling

What is a distinct Filipino Martial Art that involves hand and foot fightin?
Sikaran    Hooverball    Catch wrestling    Lethwei

What is a weapon-based Dravidian martial art from Tamil Nadu in south India but also practised by the Tamil community of Sri Lanka and Malaysia?
Silambam    Snooker plus    Episkyros    Dirt jumping

What is a collective word for indigenous martial arts that originates from Indonesia and Malaysia. It is traditionally practiced in Indonesia, Southern Thailand, Singapore, Vietnam, Brunei, Malaysia and the Philippines?
Silat    Boule lyonnaise    Zui Quan    Gungdo

What is the Philippines' traditional native sport which predates Spanish rule. The game is related to Sepak Takraw?
Sipa    Laser tag    Zui Quan    Eskrima

What is an action sport which involves riding and performing tricks using a skateboard.  can also be considered a recreational activity, an art form, a job, or a method of transportation?
Skateboarding    Footvolley    Football tennis    Riverboarding

What is a winter sport  The actual picture used is not at all a skibob. It is a Lenz Sport Ski Bike in which the user does not use foot skis?
Skibobbing    Goaltimate    Kalarippayattu    Mountain unicycling

What is a boardsport in which a skimboard (a smaller counterpart to a surfboard without fins) is used to glide across the water's surface?
Skimboarding    Hunter    Horseball    Bando

What is a type of skydiving in which the skydiver wears a board attached to his or her feet and performs surfing-style aerobatics during freefall?
Skysurfing    Hunter    Horseball    Fast Pitch

What is a type of skydiving in which the skydiver wears a board attached to his or her feet and performs surfing-style aerobatics during freefall?
Skysurfing    Kneeboarding    Metro footy    Balkline and straight rail

What is a form of basketball played with 4 trampolines in front of each net. It is played "full contact" and has boards around the court?
Slamball    Ancient games    San shou    Cluster ballooning

What is a type of winter sporting event where the goal is to perform the most difficult tricks while getting the highest amplitude off of jumps, with an emphasis on performing different types of tricks instead of doing one great trick repeatedly?
Slopestyle    Unicycle basketball    Dodgeball    Unicycling

What is a variant of baseball played with a larger ball on a smaller field. It was invented in 1888 in Chicago as an indoor game, it was at various times called indoor baseball, mush ball, playground, softbund ball, kitten ball, and, because it was also played by women, ladies' baseball?
Slow Pitch    Kuk Sool Won    Jogo do Pau    Angling

Whattish English pronunciation: , American English ) is a cue sport that is typically played on a table covered with a green cloth or baize, with pockets situated in each of the four corners and a further two, commonly referred to as the middle, or side pockets, that sit in the middle of each of the long side cushions?
Snooker    Sport climbing    Lawn bowling    Rodeo

What is a cue sport based on snooker. The variant was created by Joe Davis, who added an orange ball (8 points) and a purple ball (10 points) to the set?
Snooker plus    Matball    Kuk Sool Won    Basketball

What is a winter sport that involves descending a slope that is covered with snow while standing on a board attached to a rider's feet, using a special boot set onto a mounted binding?
Snowboarding    Wakesurfing    Show Jumping    Pehlwani

What is an outdoor winter sport where people use kite power to glide on snow or ice?
Snowkiting    Balkline and straight rail    Wing Chun    Eventing

What is an ancient method of fishing that has been used throughout the world for millennia. Early civilizations were familiar with the custom of spearing fish from rivers and streams using sharpened sticks?
Spearfishing    Gungdo    Harrow Football    Road bicycle racing

What is a solitary pool game.  As its name suggests, one  all the pool balls on the table as quickly as possible?
Speed pool    Wing Chun    Cubbies    Bounceball

What is a form of rock climbing that relies on permanent anchors fixed to the rock, and possibly bolts, for protection?
Sport climbing    Subak    Xingyiquan    Sipa

Whatfishing, also called sport fishing, is fishing for pleasure or competition. It can be contrasted with commercial fishing, which is fishing for profit, or subsistence fishing, which is fishing for survival?
Sport fishing    Deaf basketball    Durango boot    Samoa Rules

What is a varsity sport played by United States colleges and universities, under rules similar to American football?
Sprint football    Bujinkan    Beach soccer    Egyptian stick fencing

What is a folk wrestling style and  traditional national sport of Korea?
Ssireum    Boxing    Novuss    Shoot boxing

Whatlise the requirements of a formal game of football, such as a large field, field markings, goal apparatus and corner flags, eleven players per team, or match officials (referee and assistant referees)?
Street football    Gliding    Snowboarding    Taekwondo

What is a variation of the sport of basketball, typically played on outdoor courts and featuring significantly less by way of formal structure and enforcement of the game's rules?
Streetball    Pehlwani    Marn Grook    Volleyball

What is a board that was invented in 1989 by James Fisher and Oliver Macleod Smith?
Streetboarding    Team penning    Swordfighting    Target archery

What is an extreme gravity-powered activity that involves riding a streetluge board (sometimes referred to as a sled) down a paved road or course?
Streetluge    Wingsuit flying    Kajukenbo    Powered hang glider

What is either a specific or generic ancient Korean martial art. Historically this term may have specified the old Korean martial art of taekkyeon, but it is unsure?
Subak    Pehlwani    Indoor cricket    Naginatajutsu

Whatis a competitive full-contact wrestling sport where a wrestler (rikishi) attempts to force another wrestler out of a circular ring (dohyō) or to touch the ground with anything other than the soles of the feet?
Sumo    Silambam    Pato    Eventing

What is the sport of catching fish standing on the shoreline or wading in the surf.  A general term, surf fishing may or may not include casting a lure or bait, and refers to all types of shore fishing - from sandy and rocky beaches, rock jetties, or even fishing piers?
Surf fishing    Kickboxing    Wakesurfing    Akroteri Punching

What is a surface water sport in which the wave rider, referred to as a "surfer", rides on the forward face of a wave, which is most often carrying the surfer towards shore?
Surfing    Silat    Rec footy    Kajukenbo

What is a form of association football that is played in bogs or swamps?
Swamp football    Dressage    Metro footy    Duckpin bowling

What is a physical activity that involves standing on a short board (typically a skateboard) which is suspended from a frame which allows the board to swing freely?
Swing boarding    Yukigassen    Hang gliding    Horse racing

What is modern, and as such was mainly used to refer to smallsword fencing, but by extension it can also be applied to any martial art involving the use of a sword?
Swordfighting    Ssireum    Skibobbing    Bicycle Motocross or BMX

What is a Russian martial art.  Training includes but not limited to: hand to hand combat, grappling, knife fighting and fire arms training as well?
Systema    Unicycle basketball    Road bicycle racing    Bowlliards

What is a traditional Korean military martial art with a dance-like appearance in some aspects.  is also frequently romanized informally as Taekkyon or Taekyun?
Taekkyeon    Hybrid codes    Sepak takraw    Sumo

What is a martial art originating in Korea. It combines combat and self-defense techniques with sport and exercise?
Taekwondo    Shurikenjutsu    Ball badminton    Fujian White Crane

What is a county in eastern Taiwan. While its name means "Eastern Taiwan", it is also known as "Houshan" () by many of the locals, meaning behind the mountains or the back mountains?
Taido    Duckpin bowling    Taekkyeon    Kendo

What is a Korean martial art "incorporating fighting principles from Soo Bahk Do (as described in the Kwon Bup Chong Do) and techniques from northern and southern Chinese kung fu."?
Tang Soo Do    Bartitsu    Modern Arnis    Ssireum

What is governed by the World Archery Federation, abbreviated WA (formerly FITA - Fédération Internationale de Tir à l'Arc)?
Target archery    Basketball    Harness racing    Jeet Kune Do

What is a western equestrian sport that evolved from the common ranch work of separating cattle into pens for branding, doctoring, or transport?
Team penning    Wing Tsun    Paralympic volleyball    Pradal Serey

What is a cavalry sport of ancient origin, and is one of only ten equestrian disciplines officially recognised by the International Equestrian Federation?
Tent pegging    Rock fishing    Muay Thai    Beach soccer

What is the longest form of the sport of cricket. Test matches are played between national representative teams with "Test status", as determined by the International Cricket Council (ICC)?
Test cricket		 	    Gymkhana    Gungdo    Xingyiquan

What is a variation of association football with three teams instead of the usual two?
Three sided football    Podex    Tent pegging    Jogo do Pau

What is a non-contact ball sport played across a net between two teams of seven players on a rectangular court?
Throwball    Jianzi    Bokator    Rock Climbing

What is a bicycle racing sport usually held on specially built banked tracks or velodromes (but many events are held at older velodromes where the track banking is relatively shallow) using track bicycles?
Track cycling    Lethwei    Shidokan    Shorinji Kempo

What is a form of cricket originally introduced in England and Wales for professional inter-county competition by the England and Wales Cricket Board (ECB), in 2003. A Twenty20 game involves two teams, each has a single innings, batting for a maximum of 20 overs?
Twenty20	    Indoor cricket    Flutterguts    Unicycle hockey

What is the flying of lightweight, 1 or 2 seat fixed-wing aircraft, ?
Ultralight aviation    International rules football    Shuffleboard    Systema

What is a team sport, the objective being to shoot a ball through a horizontally positioned basket to score points, while following a set of rules?
Unicycle basketball    Powerchair Football    Kelly pool    Sport fishing

What is a team sport, similar to roller or inline hockey, except that each player must be mounted on a unicycle (with both feet on the pedals) to play the ball?
Unicycle hockey    Woggabaliri    Bujinkan    Yubi lakpi

What is a form of unicycling which involves participants attempting to ride a unicycle over obstacles without any part of the rider touching the ground?
Unicycle trials    Ice Climbing    Team penning    Yubi lakpi

What is a human-powered, single-track vehicle with one wheel. Unicycles resemble bicycles, but are less complex?
Unicycling    Wheelchair basketball    Swamp football    Bobrun cycling

What was a proposed hybrid sport of Australian rules football and rugby league, trialled at the Sydney Showground in 1933. The game has not been played since that time?
Universal football    Iaijutsu    Chilean rodeo    Barrel Racing

What is an old outdoor game. The game dates back to the Viking Age and survived in Gotland together with several other medieval or Viking games?
Varpa    Arena football    Artistic billiards    Football tennis

What is a ball game that was developed in fascist Italy as a substitute for  association football and rugby union?
Volata    Swordfighting    Bar billiards    Capoeira

What is a team sport in which two teams of six players are separated by a net. Each team tries to score points by grounding a ball on the other team's court under organized rules?
Volleyball    Test cricket		 	    Snowboarding    Sanshou

What is a Vietnamese martial ar?
Vovinam    Slow Pitch    Kurash    Sumo

What is a surface water sport which involves riding a  over the surface of a body of water. It was developed from a combination of water skiing, snowboarding and surfing techniques?
Wakeboarding    Ball badminton    Pencak Silat    Baguazhang

What is a water sport in which a surfer trails behind a wakeboard boat, surfing the boat's wake without being directly attached to the boat?
Wakesurfing    kung fu    Kickball    Test cricket		 	

What is a fast-paced sport that was created by Bill Dejonghe at the Calabasas Racquetball Club (Calabasas, California), in 1979 ?
Wallyball    Spearfishing    American football    Beach basketball

What is a water sport which mixes the rules of basketball and water polo, played in a swimming pool?
Water basketball    Episkyros    Harrow Football    Cluster ballooning

What is a  western style competition at horse shows that evaluates horses on manners and suitability of the horse for a relaxed but collected gait cadence and relatively slow speed of gait, along with calm and responsive disposition?
Western Pleasure    Yukigassen    Cubbies    A Bracciuta

What is basketball played by people in wheelchairs and is considered one of the major disabled sports practiced?
Wheelchair basketball    Judo    Kendo    English billiards

What is a variation of the sport of baseball designed for indoor or outdoor play in confined areas?
Wiffleball    Medieval football    Beach soccer    Krav Maga

Whatnised as Ving Tsun or Wing Tsun, (and sometimes substituted with the characters 永春 " "); (also known as Snake-Crane style) ; is a concept-based Chinese martial art and form of self-defense utilising both striking and grappling while specialising in close-range combat?
Wing Chun    Pato    Harpastum    Endurance riding

What is a branch of Wing Chun, led by Leung Tin?
Wing Tsun    Metro footy    Mountain unicycling    Peteca

What is the sport of flying the human body through the air using a special jumpsuit, called a wingsuit, which adds surface area to the human body to enable a significant increase in lift?
Wingsuit flying    Powered paragliding    Skibobbing    Punchball

What is a street game related to baseball, usually formed as a pick-up game, in  urban areas of the United States?
Wireball	    Barrel Racing    Campdrafting    Northern Praying Mantis

What is the name given to a traditional Indigenous Australian "co-operative kicking volley game" similar to the games of keepie uppie and footbag?
Woggabaliri    Bokator    Fujian White Crane    Cuju

What is a form of combat sport involving grappling type techniques such as clinch fighting, throws and takedowns,  joint locks, pins and other grappling holds?
Wrestling    Unicycle hockey    Hopper ballooning    Footvolley

What is one of the major "internal" styles of Chinese martial arts. The word translates approximately to "Form/Intention Boxing", or "Shape/Will Boxing", and is characterized by aggressive, seemingly linear movements and explosive power?
Xingyiquan    Curling    Novuss    Bumper pool

What is a commonly known generic term for physical, mental, and spiritual disciplines which originated in ancient India?
Yoga    Wrestling    Show Jumping    Paintball

What is a seven-a-side traditional football game played in Manipur, India, using a coconut, which has some notable similarities to rugby?
Yubi lakpi    BoÃŸeln    Taekkyeon    Taekkyeon

Whatis a snowball fighting-competition from Japan. Today there are annual tournaments in Sobetsu, Hokkaidō in Japan, Kemijärvi in Finland, Vardø in Norway, Mount Buller, Victoria in Australia, Luleå in Sweden in Anchorage, Alaska, and Jasper, Alberta and Saskatoon, Saskatchewan in Canada?
Yukigassen    Canadian football    Hopper ballooning    Eskrima

What is literally Drunken Fist, also known as Drunken Boxing or Drunkard's Boxing) is a concept in traditional Chinese martial arts, as well as a classification of modern Wushu forms?
Zui Quan    Iaijutsu    Cubbies    Human powered aircraft

