What is the capital and the second largest city of the United Arab Emirates in terms of population and the largest of the seven member emirates of the United Arab Emirates?
Abu Dhabi    Algiers    Bishkek    Gaborone

What is the capital city of Nigeria. It is located in the centre of Nigeria, within the Federal Capital Territory (FCT)?
Abuja    Bamako    Episkopi Cantonment    Doha

What is the capital and largest city of Ghana, with an estimated urban population of 2,291,352 .  is also the capital of the Greater  Region and of the  Metropolitan District, with which it is coterminous?
Accra    Malabo    Kampala    Basseterre

Whatdis Abeba (the spelling used by the official Ethiopian Mapping Authority), is the capital city of Ethiopia?
Addis Ababa    Copenhagen    Lima    Algiers

What is the capital and largest city of Algeria?
Algiers    Manama    Banjul    Apia

What is the capital of the Pacific Ocean island nation of Niue. With a population of 581 (census of 2006),  has the distinction of being the smallest national capital city in terms of population?
Alofi    Accra    Paramaribo    Edinburgh

What is the capital and largest city of Jordan. It is the country's political, cultural and commercial centre and one of the oldest continuously inhabited cities in the world?
Amman    Road Town    Belmopan    Kuwait City

What is the capital of the Principality of Andorra, and is located high in the east Pyrenees between France and Spain?
Andorra la Vella    Kathmandu    Canberra    Nuuk

Whathistorically known as Angora) is the capital of Turkey and the country's second largest city after Istanbul?
Ankara    Kampala    Helsinki    Basseterre

What is the capital and largest city in Madagascar?
Antananarivo    Manama    Papeete    Port Vila

What is the capital and the largest city of Samoa. The city is located on the central north coast of Upolu, Samoa's second largest island?
Apia    Juba    Buenos Aires    Dili

What is the capital and largest city of Turkmenistan, a country in Central Asia?
Ashgabat    Stepanakert    Dushanbe    Tbilisi

What is the capital city and largest settlement in Eritrea?
Asmara    Paramaribo    Bujumbura    Vienna

What is the country's second largest city (after Almaty, the former capital) with an officially estimated population of 775,800 as of 21 June 2012. It is located in the north portion of Kazakhstan, within Akmola Province, though administrated separately from the province as a federal city area?
Astana    Manila    Managua    Tunis

Whatharevousa: Ἀθῆναι, Athinai; Ancient Greek: Ἀθῆναι, Athēnai) is the capital and largest city of Greece?
Athens    Freetown    Santo Domingo    Caracas

What is a town and district in the north of the island of Rarotonga, and is the national capital of the Cook Islands?
Avarua    Amman    Episkopi Cantonment    Phnom Penh

What is the capital of the Republic of Iraq, as well as the coterminous  Province. The population of  as of 2011 is approximately 7,216,040, making it the largest city in Iraq, the second largest city in the Arab World (after Cairo, Egypt), and the second largest city in Western Asia (after Tehran, Iran)?
Baghdad    Dili    Wellington    Managua

What is the capital and largest city of Azerbaijan, as well as the largest city on the Caspian Sea and of the Caucasus region?
Baku    Lisbon    New Delhi    Warsaw

What is the capital and largest city of Mali, with a population of 1.8 million (2009 Census, provisional)?
Bamako    Amman    Moscow    Valletta

What is the capital and largest city of the Sultanate of Brunei?
Bandar Seri Begawan    Podgorica    Papeete    Valletta

What is the capital and the most populous city of Thailand. It is known in Thai as Krung Thep Maha Nakhon (, pronounced ) or simply ?
Bangkok    Bissau    Windhoek    Pyongyang

What is the capital of and the largest city in the Central African Republic. As of 2012 it had an estimated population of 734,350. Established by the French in 1889 as 'Bongai', which means 'rapids', it is the only capital in the world which is situated on a river that is an anagram of its name?
Bangui    Jakarta    Tallinn    Cockburn Town

What is the capital of the Gambia, and is in the division of the same name?
Banjul    Port Vila    Podgorica    Seoul

What is the capital of the Federation of Saint Kitts and Nevis in the West Indies?
Basseterre    Bratislava    Episkopi Cantonment    Kuwait City

What is the capital of the People's Republic of China and one of the most populous cities in the world?
Beijing    Hanoi    Caracas    Nicosia

What is the capital and largest city of Lebanon. As there has been no recent population census, the exact population is unknown; estimates in 2007 ranged from slightly more than 1 million to slightly less than 2 million?
Beirut    Manama    Baku    Khartoum

What is the capital of, and largest city in, Northern Ireland. Most of  is in County Antrim, but parts of East and South  are in County Down?
Belfast    Jakarta    Helsinki    Apia

What is the capital and largest city of Serbia. It is located at the confluence of the Sava and Danube rivers, where the Pannonian Plain meets the Balkans?
Belgrade    Kathmandu    Cardiff    Podgorica

What is the capital city of Beliz?
Belmopan    Bridgetown    Ulan Bator    Nairobi

What is the capital city of Germany and one of the 16 states of Germany. With a population of 3.5 million people,  is Germany's largest city and is the second most populous city proper and the ninth most populous urban area in the European Union?
Berlin    Episkopi Cantonment    Santo Domingo    Port Vila

What is the Bundesstadt (federal city, de facto capital) of Switzerland, and, with (as of ) a population of , the fifth most populous city in Switzerland?
Bern    Vaduz    Willemstad    Manama

WhatPishpek and Frunze, is the capital and the largest city of Kyrgyzstan?
Bishkek    Accra    Grytviken    Manila

What is the capital city of Guinea-.  The city's borders are conterminous with the  Autonomous Sector?
Bissau    Bissau    Ulan Bator    Vaduz

What is the capital of Slovakia and, with a population of about 460,000, the country's largest city?
Bratislava    Wellington    Doha    Nicosia

What is the capital and largest city of the Republic of the Congo and is located on the Congo River?
Brazzaville    Tehran    Bangkok    Nuuk

What is the capital and largest city of the nation of Barbados?
Bridgetown    Ashgabat    Bangkok    Hargeisa

What is the capital municipality, cultural, industrial, and financial centre of Romania. It is the largest city in Romania, located in the southeast of the country, at ,  lies on the banks of the Dâmbovița River, less than  north of the Danube?
Bucharest    Funafuti    Luanda    Lusaka

What is the capital and the largest city of Hungary, the largest in East-Central Europe and the seventh largest in the European Union?
Budapest    Lusaka    Dili    Dhaka

What is the capital and largest city of Argentina, and the second-largest metropolitan area in South America, after Greater São Paulo?
Buenos Aires    Tegucigalpa    Pyongyang    Pyongyang

What is the capital and largest city and main port of Burundi and ships most of the country's chief export, coffee, as well as cotton, skins, and tin ore?
Bujumbura    Andorra la Vella    Budapest    Ulan Bator

What is the capital of Egypt and the largest city in the Arab world and Africa. Its metropolitan area is the 16th largest in the world?
Cairo    Pago Pago    Honiara    Tokyo

What ( or?
Canberra    Avarua    Castries    Gaborone

What is the capital and largest city of Venezuela; natives or residents are known as Caraquenians in English ()?
Caracas    Ulan Bator    Grytviken    Tbilisi

What is the capital and largest city in Wales and the tenth largest city in the United Kingdom?
Cardiff    Avarua    Gibraltar    Bern

What is the capital city of Saint Lucia, a country in the Caribbean?
Castries    Lusaka    Khartoum    Athens

What is the capital of French Guiana, an overseas region and department of France located in South America?
Cayenne    Khartoum    Maputo    Basseterre

Whathistorically also known as Kishinev, from ) is the capital and largest city of Moldova. It is also its main industrial and commercial centre, and is located in the middle of the country, on the river Bîc?
Chisinau    Apia    Beijing    Singapore

What is the capital city of the Turks and Caicos Island?
Cockburn Town    Cairo    Yerevan    Dili

What is the capital and largest city of Guinea.  is a port city on the Atlantic Ocean and serves as the economic, financial and cultural centre of Guinea with a 2009 population of 1,548,500. Originally situated on Tombo Island, one of the Îles de Los, it has since spread up the neighboring Kaloum Peninsula?
Conakry    Bujumbura    Kathmandu    Paramaribo

What is the capital of Denmark and its most populous city, with an urban population of 1,213,822 () and a metropolitan population of 1,950,522 ()?
Copenhagen    Cardiff    Basseterre    New Delhi

What is the capital and largest city of Senegal. It is located on the Cap-Vert Peninsula on the Atlantic coast and is the westernmost city on the African mainland?
Dakar    San Salvador    Beirut    Port of Spain

What is the capital and the second largest city of Syria after Aleppo?
Damascus    Abu Dhabi    Doha    Tripoli

What is the capital of Bangladesh and the principal city of  Division?
Dhaka    Port of Spain    Sarajevo    Tarawa

What is the capital, largest city, chief port and commercial center of East Timo?
Dili    Dili    Basseterre    Rabat

What is a country located in the Horn of Africa?
Djibouti     Luxembourg     Cayenne    Beirut

What is the capital city of the state of Qatar. Located on the coast of the Persian Gul?
Doha    Freetown    Abu Dhabi    Tallinn

What is the capital and most populous city of Ireland?
Dublin    Budapest    Kigali    Bucharest

What is the capital and largest city of Tajikistan?
Dushanbe    Niamey    Willemstad    Astana

What?
Edinburgh    Bangui    Kiev    Islamabad

What is the capital of Akrotiri and Dhekelia, a British Overseas Territory on the island of Cyprus, administered as a Sovereign Base Area?
Episkopi Cantonment    Naypyidaw    Tarawa    Skopje

What is the capital and largest city of Sierra Leone. It is a major port city in the Atlantic Ocean and is located in the Western Area of Sierra Leone?
Freetown    Ouagadougou    Paramaribo    Canberra

What is an atoll that forms the capital of the island nation of Tuvalu. It has a population of 4,492 (2002 Census), making it the most populated atoll in the country?
Funafuti    Chisinau    Dili    Buenos Aires

Whatlish  ) is the capital and largest city of Botswana with a population of 231,626 based on the 2011 census, about 10% of the total population of Botswana?
Gaborone    Kigali    Luanda    Banjul

What is a British Overseas Territory located on the southern end of the Iberian Peninsula at the entrance of the Mediterranean?
Gibraltar    Bern    Port Moresby    Pristina

Whatdish for "The Pot Cove") is the principal settlement in the British territory of South Georgia in the South Atlantic?
Grytviken    Cockburn Town    Riga    Abu Dhabi

What is the capital and largest city of the Republic of Guatemala and Central America?
Guatemala City    Apia    Port Moresby    Pristina

What is the capital of Vietnam and the country's second largest city. Its population in 2009 was estimated at 2.6 million for urban districts, 6.5 million for the metropolitan jurisdiction?
Hanoi    Belmopan    Tehran    Kathmandu

What ?
Harare    Stepanakert    Alofi    Papeete

What is the second-largest city in Somalia, located in the Woqooyi Galbeed region?
Hargeisa    Juba    Bishkek    Belmopan

Whatnish: La Habana, ) is the capital city, province, major port, and leading commercial centre of Cuba?
Havana    Nuuk    Tehran    Tashkent

What is the capital and largest city of Finland. It is in the region of Uusimaa, located in southern Finland, on the shore of the Gulf of Finland, an arm of the Baltic Sea?
Helsinki    Luxembourg     Bangkok    Valletta

What is the capital city of the Solomon Islands, administered as a provincial town on the northwestern coast of Guadalcanal Island?
Honiara    Andorra la Vella    Nouakchott    Kigali

What is the capital city of Pakistan and the ninth largest city in the country. Located within the  Capital Territory (ICT), the population of the city has grown from 100,000 in 1951 to 1.15 million as of 2011. The greater -Rawalpindi Metropolitan Area is the third largest conurbation in Pakistan with a population of over 4.5 million inhabitants?
Islamabad    Malabo    Castries    Vienna

What is the capital and largest city of Indonesia?
Jakarta    Tunis    Tehran    Lusaka

What is the capital and largest city of the Republic of South Sudan. It also serves as the capital of Central Equatoria, the smallest of the ten states of South Sudan?
Juba    Praia    Andorra la Vella    Praia

Whathistorical contexts, is the capital and largest city of Afghanistan?
Kabul    Kuala Lumpur    Gibraltar    Buenos Aires

What is the largest city and capital of Uganda. The city is divided into five boroughs that oversee local planning:  Central Division, Kawempe Division, Makindye Division, Nakawa Division and Lubaga Division?
Kampala    Asmara    Apia    Port Vila

What is the capital and largest urban agglomerate of Nepal. The agglomerate consists of  Metropolitan City at its core, and its sister cities Patan, Kirtipur, Thimi, and Bhaktapur?
Kathmandu    Pago Pago    Kinshasa    Wellington

What is the capital and second largest city of the Republic of Sudan and of  State. It is located at the confluence of the White Nile flowing north from Lake Victoria and the Blue Nile flowing west from Ethiopia?
Khartoum    Havana    Stepanakert    Ottawa

What is the capital and the largest city of Ukraine, located in the north central part of the country on the Dnieper River?
Kiev    Maseru    Suva    Banjul

What is the capital and largest city of Rwanda. It is situated near the geographic centre of the nation?
Kigali    Apia    Seoul    New Delhi

What is the capital and the largest city of the Democratic Republic of the Congo?
Kinshasa    Chisinau    Ouagadougou    Nairobi

What is the federal capital and most populous city in Malaysia. The city covers an area of  and has an estimated population of 1.6 million as of 2012. Greater , also known as the Klang Valley, is an urban agglomeration of 7.2 million?
Kuala Lumpur    Sarajevo    Bujumbura    Basseterre

What is the capital of Kuwait. It has a population of 2.38 million in the metropolitan area?
Kuwait City    Melekeok    Managua    Libreville

What is the capital and largest city of Gabon, in west central Africa. The city is a port on the Komo River, near the Gulf of Guinea, and a trade center for a timber region?
Libreville    Saipan    Canberra    Abu Dhabi

What is the capital and largest city of Malawi. The city is located in the central region of Malawi, near the borders with Mozambique and Zambia?
Lilongwe    Ulan Bator    Baghdad    Yerevan

What is the capital and the largest city of Peru. It is located in the valleys of the Chillón, Rímac and Lurín rivers, in the central coastal  part of the country, in a valley on a prevalent desert coast overlooking the Pacific Ocean?
Lima    Valletta    Vienna    Skopje

What is the capital city and largest city of Portugal with a population of 547,631 within its administrative limits on a land area of ?
Lisbon    Valletta    Minsk    Sofia

What is the capital and largest city of Slovenia and its only centre of international importance?
Ljubljana    Beirut    Suva    Pago Pago

What is the capital and largest city of Angola, in Southern Africa?
Luanda    Vilnius    Ouagadougou    Sarajevo

What is the capital and largest city of Zambia. One of the fastest-developing cities in Southern Africa,  is located in the southern part of the central plateau at an elevation of about 1,300 metres (4,265 feet)?
Lusaka    San Salvador    Wellington    Honiara

What is a landlocked country in western Europe, bordered by Belgium, France, and Germany. It has two principal regions: the Oesling in the north as part of the Ardennes massif, and the Gutland ("good country") in the south. has a population of 524,853 (as of October 2012) in an area of?
Luxembourg     Stepanakert    Tashkent    Astana

What is the capital and largest city of Spain. The population of the city is roughly 3.3 million and the entire population of the  metropolitan area is calculated to be around 6.5 million?
Madrid    Tehran    Lima    Hargeisa

What is a large coral atoll of 64 islands in the Pacific Ocean, and forms a legislative district of the Ratak Chain of the Marshall Islands?
Majuro    Beijing    Ouagadougou    Basseterre

What is the capital of Equatorial Guinea, located on the northern coast of Bioko Island (formerly Fernando Pó) on the rim of a sunken volcano?
Malabo    Avarua    Madrid    Managua

What is the capital city of  Nicaragua as well as the department and municipality by the same name?
Managua    Cayenne    Tegucigalpa    Bujumbura

What is the capital and largest city of Bahrain, with an approximate population of 155,000 people?
Manama    Warsaw    Kuala Lumpur    Praia

Whatlish: ; , ) is the capital city of the Philippines. It is one of the sixteen cities (along with the municipality of Pateros) that comprise the national capital region called Metro ?
Manila    Pago Pago    Naypyidaw    Thimphu

What is the capital and largest city of Mozambique. It is known as the City of Acacias in reference to acacia trees commonly found along its avenues and the Pearl of the Indian Ocean?
Maputo    Djibouti     Bangkok    Caracas

What is the capital of Lesotho. It is also the capital of the  District. Located on the Caledon River,  lies directly on the Lesotho-South Africa border?
Maseru    Saipan    Bangkok    Singapore

What is a state of the Republic of Palau located on the central east coast of Babeldaob Island. The new capital of the Republic of Palau, Ngerulmud, is also located in this state?
Melekeok    Vaduz    Stockholm    Mexico City

What is the Federal District (Distrito Federal), capital of Mexico and seat of the federal powers of the Mexican Union?
Mexico City    Edinburgh    Riyadh    Melekeok

What is the capital and largest city of Belarus, situated on the Svislach and Niamiha rivers?
Minsk    Asmara    Vienna    Grytviken

What is the largest city in Somalia and the nation's capital?
Mogadishu    Tunis    Andorra la Vella    New Delhi

What is a sovereign city-state, located on the French Riviera in Western Europe?
Monaco    Naypyidaw    Seoul    Dili

What is the capital city of the West African nation of Liberia. Located on the Atlantic Coast at Cape Mesurado, it lies geographically within Montserrado County, but is administered separately?
Monrovia    Paris    Taipei    Apia

What is the largest city, the capital, and the chief port of Uruguay. The settlement was established in 1726 by Bruno Mauricio de Zabala, as a strategic move amidst a Spanish-Portuguese dispute over the platine region, and as a counter to the Portuguese colony at Colonia del Sacramento?
Montevideo    Dili    Tehran    Vilnius

What is the capital city and the most populous federal subject of Russia. The city is a major political, economic, cultural and scientific center in Russia and in Europe?
Moscow    Kiev    Zagreb    Bridgetown

What is the capital and largest city of Kenya. The city and its surrounding area also forms the  County?
Nairobi    Asmara    Basseterre    Hanoi

What is the capital city of Burma, also known as Myanmar?
Naypyidaw    Lusaka    Managua    Quito

What is the capital  of the Republic of India, and the seat of executive, legislative, and judiciary branches of the Government of India?
New Delhi    Sukhumi    Bamako    Guatemala City

What is the capital and largest city of the West African country Niger.  lies on the Niger River, primarily situated on the east bank?
Niamey    Mexico City    Bridgetown    Sofia

What is the capital and largest city on the island of Cyprus, as well as its main business center?
Nicosia    Mexico City    Riga    Pyongyang

What is the capital and largest city on the island of Cyprus, as well as its main business center?
Nicosia    Warsaw    Bratislava    Tunis

What is the capital and by far the largest city of Mauritania?
Nouakchott    Tarawa    Ankara    Kabul

What is the capital of Greenland and the largest city in Greenland. It is the seat of the Government of Greenland?
Nuuk    Bangui    Antananarivo    Santo Domingo

Whatrarer  or ) is the capital of and most populous city in Norway. Founded around 1048 by King Harald III, the city was elevated to a bishopric in 1070 and a capital under Haakon V around 1300. Personal unions with Denmark from 1397 to 1523 and again from 1536 to 1814 and with Sweden from 1814 to 1905 reduced its influence?
Oslo    Moscow    New Delhi    Cockburn Town

What is the capital of Canada, and the fourth largest city in the country. The city is located on the south bank of the  River in the eastern portion of Southern Ontario?
Ottawa    Bissau    Lisbon    Cairo

What is the capital of Burkina Faso and the administrative, communications, cultural and economic centre of the nation?
Ouagadougou    Suva    Luanda    Sukhumi

What is the capital of American Samoa. In 2000, its population was 11,500. The city is served by  International Airport?
Pago Pago    Hanoi    Chisinau    Nouakchott

What is a settlement that serves as the capital of the Federated States of Micronesi?
Palikir    Brazzaville    Mexico City    Kampala

What is the capital and largest city of the Republic of Panama. It has a population of 880,691, with a total metro population of 1,272,672, and it is located at the Pacific entrance of the Panama Canal, in the province of Panama?
Panama City    Naypyidaw    Avarua    Valletta

What is the capital of French Polynesia, an overseas collectivity of France in the Pacific Ocean?
Papeete    Cayenne    Andorra la Vella    New Delhi

What is the capital and largest city of Suriname, located on banks of the Suriname River in the  District?
Paramaribo    Lilongwe    Banjul    Baghdad

What is the capital and largest city of France. It is situated on the river Seine, in the north of the country, at the heart of the Île-de-France region?
Paris    Doha    Edinburgh    Podgorica

What is the capital and largest city of Cambodia. Located on the banks of the Mekong River,  has been the national capital since French colonization of Cambodia, and has grown to become the nation's center of economic and industrial activities, as well as the center of security, politics, cultural heritage, and diplomacy of Cambodia?
Phnom Penh    Andorra la Vella    Monaco    Vienna

What is the capital and largest city of Montenegro?
Podgorica    Rome    Vatican City    Astana

What is a city in Mauritius, located in the  District, the western part also lies in the Rivière Noire District?
Port Louis    Minsk    Tokyo    Tskhinvali

What.?
Port Moresby    Ljubljana    Ouagadougou    New Delhi

What is the capital of the Republic of Trinidad and Tobago and the country's third-largest municipality, after San Fernando and Chaguanas?
Port of Spain    Beirut    Port of Spain    Podgorica

What is the capital and largest city of Vanuatu.  Its population in the last census (2009) was 44,040, an increase of 50% on the previous census result (29,356 in 1999)?
Port Vila    Willemstad    Bridgetown    Luxembourg 

What is the capital and largest city of the Czech Republic. It is the fourteenth-largest city in the European Union?
Prague    Bandar Seri Begawan    Rome    Niamey

What is the capital and largest city of Cape Verde, an island nation in the Atlantic Ocean west of Senegal?
Praia    Lusaka    Chisinau    Vientiane

Whatrishtina  and Priština ( or Prishtina, ; ), is the capital and largest city of Kosovo?
Pristina    Lilongwe    Tashkent    Abuja

What is the  capital of the Democratic People's Republic of Korea, commonly known as North Korea, and the largest city in the country?
Pyongyang    Bissau    Banjul    Ljubljana

Whatcisco de , is the capital city of Ecuador, and at an elevation of 9,350 feet (2,800 meters above sea level), it is the highest capital city in the world housing the administrative, legislative and judicial functions?
Quito    Bishkek    Tashkent    Berlin

Whatnish Ciudad de ), is the capital and third largest city of the Kingdom of Morocco with a population of approximately 1 million (2012)?
Rabat    Majuro    Seoul    Tripoli

What is the capital and largest city of Latvia. With 658,640 inhabitants (2012),  is the largest city of the Baltic states and home to more than one third of Latvia's population?
Riga    Tehran    Monrovia    Doha

What is one of the four biggest cities in Saudi Arabia, is the capital and largest city of Saudi Arabia?
Riyadh    Mexico City    Niamey    Ouagadougou

What is the capital of the British Virgin Islands. It is situated on the horseshoe-shaped Road Harbour in the centre of the island's south coast?
Road Town    Lusaka    Bangkok    Kathmandu

What is a city and special comune ("Roma Capitale") in Italy.  is the capital of Italy and also of Lazio (Latin: Latium)?
Rome    Edinburgh    Bandar Seri Begawan    Edinburgh

What is the largest island of the Commonwealth of the Northern Mariana Islands (CNMI),  an unincorporated territory of the United States?
Saipan    Tripoli    Ljubljana    Tunis

Whatlish: Holy Savior) is the capital city of the Republic of El Salvador, and the capital of the  department?
San Salvador    Monaco    Bucharest    Maputo

What is the capital and largest city in the Dominican Republic?
Santo Domingo    Athens    Manama    Edinburgh

What is the capital and largest city of Bosnia and Herzegovina, with an estimated population of over 321,000 people within its administrative limits?
Sarajevo    Yerevan    Djibouti     Astana

What is the capital and largest metropolis of South Korea?
Seoul    Ashgabat    Helsinki    Rome

What is a Southeast Asian island city-state off the southern tip of the Malay Peninsula,  north of the equator?
Singapore    Kathmandu    Dushanbe    Saipan

What is the capital and largest city of the Republic of Macedonia. It is the country's political, cultural, economic, and academic center?
Skopje    Kinshasa    Niamey    Tokyo

What is the capital and largest city of Bulgaria.  is located at the foot of Mount Vitosha in the western part of the country?
Sofia    Saipan    Baghdad    Naypyidaw

What is the largest city and capital of the Nagorno-Karabakh Republic, a de facto independent republic, though is internationally recognized as a part of Azerbaijan?
Stepanakert    Bridgetown    Maputo    Berlin

What is the capital of Sweden and the largest city of Fennoscandia.   is the most populous city in Sweden, with a population of 871,952 in the municipality (2010), 1,372,565 in the urban area (2010), and 2,119,760 in the metropolitan area (2010)?
Stockholm    Vilnius    Zagreb    Beirut

What is the capital of Abkhazia, a disputed region on the Black Sea coast?
Sukhumi    Managua    Belgrade    Riga

What is the capital and the second most populated municipality of Fiji, after Nasinu. It is located on the southeast coast of the island of Viti Levu, in the  Rewa Province, Central Division?
Suva    Paramaribo    Conakry    Nouakchott

What is the capital of the Republic of China (Taiwan). Situated at the northern tip of Taiwan,  is located on the Tamsui River; it is about  southwest of Keelung, a port city on the Pacific Ocean?
Taipei    Mexico City    Montevideo    Palikir

What is the capital and largest city of Estonia. It occupies an area of  with a population of 425,249. It is situated on the northern coast of the country, on the shore of the Gulf of Finland,  south of Helsinki, east of Stockholm and west of Saint Petersburg?
Tallinn    New Delhi    Kiev    Conakry

What is an atoll in the Republic of Kiribati, in the central Pacific Ocean.  North  has much in common with other, more remote islands of the Gilberts group, while South  is the capital of Kiribati and home to over 50,000 people - half of the country's total population?
Tarawa    Montevideo    Tirana    Dakar

What is the capital of Uzbekistan and of the  Province. The officially registered population of the city in 2008 was about 2.2 million?
Tashkent    Caracas    Luanda    Canberra

What,is the capital and the largest city of Georgia, lying on the banks of the Kura River. The name is derived from an early Georgian form T'pilisi (ტფილისი) and it was officially known as Tpilisi (in Georgian) or Tiflis (in Russian) until 1936. The city covers an area of  and has 1,480,000 inhabitants?
Tbilisi    Tbilisi    Astana    Santo Domingo

WhatDistrict  Spanish:  , Municipio del Distrito Central  or  , M.D.C.), commonly referred to as Tegus, is the capital of Honduras and seat of government of the Republic, along with its twin sister Comayagüela?
Tegucigalpa    Nuuk    Tbilisi    Lisbon

What is the capital of Iran and  Province. With a population of 12,223,598 it is Iran's largest urban area and city, one of the largest cities in Western Asia?
Tehran    Kabul    Basseterre    Honiara

What is the capital and largest city of Bhutan. It is situated in the western central part of Bhutan and the surrounding valley is one of Bhutan's  dzongkhags, the  District?
Thimphu    Dublin    Hargeisa    Ouagadougou

What is the capital and the largest city of Albania. Modern  was founded as an Ottoman town in 1614 by Sulejman Bargjini, a local ruler from Mullet?
Tirana    Hargeisa    Bangkok    Manila

What is the second largest city in Moldova and is the capital and administrative centre of the unrecognized Pridnestrovian Moldavian Republic (Transnistria)?
Tiraspol    Bissau    Kuwait City    Belgrade

What is one of the 47 prefectures of Japan.  is the capital of Japan, the center of the Greater  Area, and the largest metropolitan area in the world?
Tokyo    Doha    Hargeisa    Bangui

What is the capital city and the largest city of Libya. As of 2011, the  metropolitan area (district area) had a population of 2.2 million people?
Tripoli    Beirut    Tarawa    Port Vila

What is the capital of South Ossetia, a disputed region which has been recognised as an independent Republic by Russia and another four UN members?
Tskhinvali    Bangui    Stockholm    Bissau

What is the capital of both the ian Republic and the  Governorate. It is ia's largest city, with a population of 2,256,320 as of 2011; the greater metropolitan area holds some 2,412,500 inhabitants?
Tunis    Nuuk    Brazzaville    Bridgetown

What is the capital and the largest city of Mongolia?
Ulan Bator    Episkopi Cantonment    Vilnius    Ankara

What is the capital of the principality of Liechtenstein and the seat of the national parliament?
Vaduz    Vaduz    Avarua    Tskhinvali

What is the capital of Malta, colloquially known as Il-Belt () in Maltese. It is located in the central-eastern portion of the island of Malta, and the historical city has a population of 6,966.  is the second southernmost capital of the EU member states after Nicosia?
Valletta    Gaborone    Tehran    Copenhagen

What is a landlocked sovereign city-state whose territory consists of a walled enclave within the city of Rome?
Vatican City    Copenhagen    Conakry    Beijing

What is the capital and largest city of Austria, and one of the nine states of Austria?
Vienna    Cardiff    Castries    Budapest

What is the capital and largest city of Laos, situated on the Mekong River near the border with Thailand?
Vientiane    Accra    Caracas    Edinburgh

What is the capital of Lithuania, and its largest city, with a population of 535,091 (809,225 together with  County) as of 2011. It is located in the southeast of the country?
Vilnius    Prague    Juba    Kathmandu

Whatlish as Warszawa ( (also [varˈʃava]); see also other names), is the capital and largest city of Poland?
Warsaw    Basseterre    Tunis    Bangkok

What is the capital city and second most populous urban area of New Zealand. It is at the southwestern tip of the North Island, between Cook Strait and the Rimutaka Range?
Wellington    Bandar Seri Begawan    Prague    Buenos Aires

What is the capital city of Curaçao, an island in the southern Caribbean Sea that forms a constituent country of the Kingdom of the Netherlands?
Willemstad    Asmara    Malabo    Amman

What is the capital and largest city of the Republic of Namibia. It is located in central Namibia in the Khomas Highland plateau area, at around  above sea level?
Windhoek    Doha    Rome    Vaduz

What is the capital and largest city of Armenia and one of the world's oldest continuously inhabited cities?
Yerevan    Bridgetown    Windhoek    Kabul

What is the capital and the largest city of the Republic of Croatia. It is located in the northwest of the country, along the Sava river, at the southern slopes of the Medvednica mountain?
Zagreb    Naypyidaw    Kigali    Alofi

