Whatliss, Jr. was born on August 8, 1853. His father, Abel Bliss, Sr., was a native of Wilbraham, Mass, and was born on February 9, 1810. His mother was Lucinda Blake, a native of the Bay State and born in Springfield, October 14, 1816.  He was the sixth of the seven children born into his family, and attended high school at Englewood, and afterward was a student of engineering at Illinois University at Champaign?
Abel Bliss Professorship    Gibbs Brothers Medal    Saltire Prize    Queen Elizabeth Prize for Engineering

What is an award presented by the combined engineering societies of the United States, given each year to a person not over thirty-five for a paper published in one of the journals of the participating societies?
Alfred Noble Prize    Joan Hodges Queneau Award    Harold Pender Award    Intel Outstanding Researcher Award

What is awarded by the International Association of Bridge and Structural Engineers (IABSE) Foundation to honour a Laureate and support a Fellow of the Association?
Anton Tedesko Medal    James Watt International Medal    Ho Chi Minh Prize    Category:Wright Brothers Medal recipients

What is a Norwegian architecture and civil engineering award issued by the National Associations of Norwegian Architects and the Norwegian Concrete Association?
Betongtavlen    Category:Draper Prize winners    Dick Volz Award    Niels Bohr International Gold Medal

WhatPrimary article Charles Stark Draper Pri?
Category:Draper Prize winners    Igor I. Sikorsky Human Powered Helicopter Competition    Dick Volz Award    Betongtavlen

WhatArticles about or referencing awards in the field of electrical engineerin?
Category:Electrical engineering awards    Ho Chi Minh Prize    IEEE Charles LeGeyt Fortescue Graduate Scholarship    Charles Stark Draper Prize

What?
Category:Elliott Cresson Medal recipients    IEEE Ernst Weber Engineering Leadership Recognition    Category:Occupational safety and health awards    IEEE Richard M. Emberson Award

What?
Category:Industrial design awards    Queen Elizabeth Prize for Engineering    Steel bridge competition    Harold Brown Award

What?
Category:John Fritz Medal recipients    Elmer A. Sperry Award    IEEE Richard M. Emberson Award    Saltire Prize

WhatArticles about or referencing awards in the field of mechanical engineerin?
Category:Mechanical engineering awards    Queen Elizabeth Prize for Engineering    Sainsbury Management Fellowship    IEEE Corporate Innovation Recognition

What?
Category:Occupational safety and health awards    Category:Mechanical engineering awards    Niels Bohr International Gold Medal    Federal Engineer of the Year Award

What?
Category:Wright Brothers Medal recipients    Gibbs Brothers Medal    Category:Electrical engineering awards    IEEE Richard M. Emberson Award

What is given for the advancement of engineering and the education of the public about engineering?
Charles Stark Draper Prize    Wright Brothers Medal    Betongtavlen    IEEE Andrew S. Grove Award

What is a prestigious award presented annually to the "Fleet Engineer of the Year" by the American Society of Naval Engineers (ASNE) since 1987. The award recognizes the efforts of United States fleet or field engineers who have made significant contributions to improving operational engineering or material readiness of the United States maritime forces during the past three years prior to nomination?
Claud A. Jones Award    Willem P.C. Stemmer    Percy Nicholls Award    TEC Awards

What is an American engineering award, established by Daniel and Harry Guggenheim?
Daniel Guggenheim Medal    Sainsbury Management Fellowship    David W. Taylor Medal    Joan Hodges Queneau Award

What is a medal presented by the Society of Naval Architects and Marine Engineers for "notable achievement in naval architecture and/or marine engineering?
David W. Taylor Medal    President's Medal    Kelvin Gold Medal    Gordon Prize

Whatsis in Robotics and Automation is a yearly award to recognize outstanding Ph.D?
Dick Volz Award    Russ Prize    Elliott Cresson Medal    Saltire Prize

WhatThe , also known as the Elliott Cresson Gold Medal, was the highest award given by the Franklin Institute?
Elliott Cresson Medal    Niels Bohr International Gold Medal    Steel bridge competition    SPIE Gold Medal

What is an American transportation engineering priz?
Elmer A. Sperry Award    Sugden Award    IEEE Haraden Pratt Award    Washington Award

Whatdistributes up to thirty s each year?
Engineering Leadership Award    Hoover Medal    Harold Brown Award    Russ Prize

What is an annual award sponsored by the National Society of Professional Engineers and the Professional Engineers in Government advocacy group of the NSPE?
Federal Engineer of the Year Award    Nitro Nobel Gold Medal    Queen Elizabeth Prize for Engineering    IEEE Simon Ramo Medal

What is NASA's premier quality and performance award for NASA's prime and sub contractors?
George M. Low award    Kremer prize    TEC Awards    IEEE Donald G. Fink Prize Paper Award

What is awarded by the U.S. National Academy of Sciences for "outstanding contributions in the field of naval architecture and marine engineering"?
Gibbs Brothers Medal    IEEE Andrew S. Grove Award    Elmer A. Sperry Award    Category:Occupational safety and health awards

What is a national award given annually by the Society of American Military Engineers (SAME) to a registered engineer who is also a member of SAME prior to nomination?
Goethals Medal    IEEE Donald G. Fink Prize Paper Award    Ho-Am Prize in Engineering    Ho Chi Minh Prize

What is to recognize leaders in academia for the development of new educational approaches to engineering?
Gordon Prize    Niels Bohr International Gold Medal    IEEE Life Member Graduate Study Fellowship in Electrical Engineering    Harold Pender Award

What is the highest award given by the United States Air Force to a scientist or engineer who applies scientific research to solve a problem critical to the needs of the Air Force?
Harold Brown Award    Joan Hodges Queneau Award    Washington Award    Kremer prize

What is given by the Faculty of the School of Engineering and Applied Science of the University of Pennsylvania to an outstanding member of the engineering profession who has achieved distinction by significant contributions to society?
Harold Pender Award    Niels Bohr International Gold Medal    IEEE Donald G. Fink Prize Paper Award    SPIE Gold Medal

What is given annually to the paper appearing in Fire Technology journal that best represents excellence in the communication of fire protection concepts?
Harry C. Bigglestone Award    IEEE Ernst Weber Engineering Leadership Recognition    Willem P.C. Stemmer    Inducement prize contest

What is an honorary award given by the government of Vietnam in recognition of cultural and/or scientific achievement?
Ho Chi Minh Prize    James Watt International Medal    Ho Chi Minh Prize    Sainsbury Management Fellowship

WhatWinners of the?
Ho-Am Prize in Engineering    Ho Chi Minh Prize    Ho-Am Prize in Engineering    IEEE Richard M. Emberson Award

What is an American engineering priz?
Hoover Medal    Inducement prize contest    IEEE Richard M. Emberson Award    Kremer prize

What is a Technical Field Award presented  by the IEEE for outstanding contributions to solid-state devices and technology?
IEEE Andrew S. Grove Award    James Watt International Medal    David W. Taylor Medal    Washington Award

What is a  professional association headquartered in New York City that is dedicated to advancing technological innovation and excellence?
IEEE Charles LeGeyt Fortescue Graduate Scholarship    Gordon Prize    Category:Occupational safety and health awards    Federal Engineer of the Year Award

Whatlished by the IEEE Board of Directors in 1985.  This award is presented for outstanding and exemplary contributions by an industrial entity, governmental, or academic organization, or other corporate body?
IEEE Corporate Innovation Recognition    Category:Mechanical engineering awards    Gibbs Brothers Medal    Ho Chi Minh Prize

Whatlished by the Board of Directors of the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE) to honor Donald G?
IEEE Donald G. Fink Prize Paper Award    Claud A. Jones Award    Gibbs Brothers Medal    Russ Prize

Whatlished by the Board of Directors of the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE) in 1985.  This award is presented "for exceptional managerial leadership in the fields of interest to the IEEE"?
IEEE Ernst Weber Engineering Leadership Recognition    IEEE Andrew S. Grove Award    Abel Bliss Professorship    Harold Brown Award

Whatlished by the IEEE Board of Directors in 1971.  This award is presented to recognize individuals who have rendered outstanding service to the IEEE?
IEEE Haraden Pratt Award    IEEE Ernst Weber Engineering Leadership Recognition    Engineering Leadership Award    IEEE Simon Ramo Medal

What is a  professional association headquartered in New York City that is dedicated to advancing technological innovation and excellence?
IEEE Life Member Graduate Study Fellowship in Electrical Engineering    Federal Engineer of the Year Award    MacRobert Award    SPIE Gold Medal

Whatlished by the IEEE Board of Directors in 1986. It is presented to an IEEE member for distinguished service to the development, viability, advancement, and pursuit of the technical objectives of the IEEE?
IEEE Richard M. Emberson Award    Telford Medal    Elliott Cresson Medal    Sainsbury Management Fellowship

What is an award for exceptional achievement in systems engineering and systems science, and was established by the IEEE Board of Directors in 1982. The medal is named for Simon Ramo, one of the founders of the TRW corporation?
IEEE Simon Ramo Medal    Willem P.C. Stemmer    Category:Draper Prize winners    IEEE Ernst Weber Engineering Leadership Recognition

Whatlished in 1980 by the American Helicopter Society (AHS) International to develop the first controlled flight of a human powered helicopter that meets a set of extremely challenging requirements?
Igor I. Sikorsky Human Powered Helicopter Competition    John Fritz Medal    Anton Tedesko Medal    Saltire Prize

What is a competition that awards a cash prize for the accomplishment of a feat, usually of engineering?
Inducement prize contest    Inducement prize contest    Sugden Award    SPIE Gold Medal

What is presented by Intel Corporation for outstanding contributions to the development of advanced nanoelectronic and manufacturing technologies?
Intel Outstanding Researcher Award    Max Jakob Memorial Award    Category:Industrial design awards    George M. Low award

What is the name of two awards named after Scottish engineer James Watt, both awarded for excellence in engineerin?
James Watt International Medal    Ho-Am Prize in Engineering    Engineering Leadership Award    Queen Elizabeth Prize for Engineering

What is an American engineering award for the field of environmental conservation?
Joan Hodges Queneau Award    Harold Pender Award    Inducement prize contest    Category:Wright Brothers Medal recipients

What is since 1902 yearly awarded by the American Association of Engineering Societies for "outstanding scientific or industrial achievements"?
John Fritz Medal    IEEE Corporate Innovation Recognition    George M. Low award    John Fritz Medal

What is a British engineering priz?
Kelvin Gold Medal    Percy Nicholls Award    Category:Wright Brothers Medal recipients    Ho Chi Minh Prize

What are a series of monetary awards, established in 1959 by the industrialist Henry Kremer, that are given to pioneers of human-powered flight?
Kremer prize    IEEE Corporate Innovation Recognition    Sugden Award    Category:Mechanical engineering awards

Whathis is a list of Fellows of the Engineering Institute of Canada (EIC?
List of Fellows of the Engineering Institute of Canada    Wright Brothers Medal    George M. Low award    Saltire Prize

WhatThe  has been presented every year since 1969 by the Royal Academy of Engineerin?
MacRobert Award    Queen Elizabeth Prize for Engineering    Kremer prize    Willem P.C. Stemmer

Whatdistinguished leadership in the field of heat transfer?
Max Jakob Memorial Award    Category:John Fritz Medal recipients    Harold Pender Award    Category:Elliott Cresson Medal recipients

What is an international engineering awar?
Niels Bohr International Gold Medal    Prince Philip Medal    IEEE Donald G. Fink Prize Paper Award    Engineering Leadership Award

What is an explosives industry award given by the Nitro Nobel Company of Sweden (now part of Dyno Nobel)?
Nitro Nobel Gold Medal    IEEE Simon Ramo Medal    Intel Outstanding Researcher Award    Ho-Am Prize in Engineering

What is an American engineering priz?
Percy Nicholls Award    Theodore von Karman Medal    Max Jakob Memorial Award    Steel bridge competition

What is an award given by the President of the Royal Academy of Engineering?
President's Medal    Category:Draper Prize winners    Category:Electrical engineering awards    Abel Bliss Professorship

What is named after HRH The Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh, who is the Senior Fellow of the Royal Academy of Engineering (RAE)?
Prince Philip Medal    Nitro Nobel Gold Medal    Sugden Award    Category:Industrial design awards

What is a global engineering prize that rewards and celebrates individual (or a team of up to three individuals) responsible for a ground-breaking innovation in engineering which has been of global benefit to humanity?
Queen Elizabeth Prize for Engineering    MacRobert Award    IEEE Charles LeGeyt Fortescue Graduate Scholarship    Telford Medal

What is an American national and international award established by the United States National Academy of Engineering (NAE) in October 1999 in Athens, Ohio?
Russ Prize    Charles Stark Draper Prize    David W. Taylor Medal    Steel bridge competition

Whatnisation was established in 1987 by David Sainsbury (now Lord Sainsbury of Turville) to develop UK engineers into industry leaders, thereby raising UK competitiveness in engineering, manufacturing and construction businesses?
Sainsbury Management Fellowship    Category:Industrial design awards    Charles Stark Draper Prize    Category:Mechanical engineering awards

What is the national award for advances in the commercial development of marine energy?
Saltire Prize    MacRobert Award    Intel Outstanding Researcher Award    Intel Outstanding Researcher Award

What is awarded annually by the Royal Academy of Engineering to an enginee?
Sir Frank Whittle Medal    Alfred Noble Prize    TEC Awards    Hoover Medal

What is the highest honor of SPIE (the international society for optics and photonics), and is considered as one of the highest award in the fields of photonic and optical engineering and related instrumental sciences?
SPIE Gold Medal    Gibbs Brothers Medal    Federal Engineer of the Year Award    Steel bridge competition

What is a student contest that tests the knowledge and practicality of teams of university students from American Society of Civil Engineers (ASCE) Student Chapters in the field of structural engineering?
Steel bridge competition    Max Jakob Memorial Award    Inducement prize contest    Category:Industrial design awards

What is an annual award for contributions to combustion research. The prize is awarded by the British Section of The Combustion Institute for the published paper with at least one British Section member as author and is named after Sir Morris Sugden?
Sugden Award    SPIE Gold Medal    TEC Awards    MacRobert Award

What is an annual program recognizing the achievements of audio professionals. The awards are given to honor technically innovative products as well as companies and individuals who have excelled in sound for television, film, recordings, and concerts?
TEC Awards    Dick Volz Award    Queen Elizabeth Prize for Engineering    IEEE Andrew S. Grove Award

What is the highest prize awarded by the British Institution of Civil Engineers (ICE) for a paper, or series of papers; it was introduced in 1835 following a bequest made by Thomas Telford, the ICE's first president?
Telford Medal    IEEE Haraden Pratt Award    Ho Chi Minh Prize    Russ Prize

What is awarded annually to an individual in recognition of his distinguished achievement in engineering mechanics, applicable to any branch of civil engineering?
Theodore von Karman Medal    Category:Mechanical engineering awards    Dick Volz Award    Harry C. Bigglestone Award

What is an American engineering awar?
Washington Award    Niels Bohr International Gold Medal    Category:Elliott Cresson Medal recipients    David W. Taylor Medal

What is a scientist and entrepreneur who has invented numerous biotechnologies that have led to successful products and business ventures?
Willem P.C. Stemmer    Anton Tedesko Medal    Theodore von Karman Medal    Category:Wright Brothers Medal recipients

Whatlished  in 1927 to recognize individuals who have made notable contributions in the engineering design, development, or operation of air and space vehicles?
Wright Brothers Medal    Claud A. Jones Award    Kremer prize    George M. Low award

