What is the Association for Computing Machinery's Special Interest Group on programming language?
ACM SIGPLAN Programming Languages Software Award    Konrad Zuse Medal    ACM Software System Award    Harry H. Goode Memorial Award

What is an annual award that honors people or an organization "for developing a software system that has had a lasting influence, reflected in contributions to concepts, in commercial acceptance, or both"?
ACM Software System Award    J. H. Wilkinson Prize for Numerical Software    Category:The Benjamin Franklin Medal in Computer and Cognitive Science laureates    Ken Kennedy Award

What is a class of data compression algorithms that allows the exact original data to be reconstructed from the compressed data?
Calgary Challenge    Seymour Cray Computer Engineering Award    Kleene award    Nevanlinna Prize

What?
Category:Computer scientists by award    Machtey Award    John von Neumann Theory Prize    Herbrand Award

What?
Category:Dijkstra Prize laureates    Chatterbox Challenge    Nevanlinna Prize    Paris Kanellakis Award

What?
Category:Elliott Cresson Medal recipients    Category:Nevanlinna Prize laureates    Jon Postel    Category:Nevanlinna Prize laureates

What?
Category:Gödel Prize laureates    Pirelli Internetional Award    Gerard Salton Award    Harlan D. Mills Award

What?
Category:Information science awards    Category:Information science awards    Category:The Benjamin Franklin Medal in Computer and Cognitive Science laureates    Category:Elliott Cresson Medal recipients

What?
Category:Knuth Prize laureates    Seymour Cray Computer Engineering Award    IJCAI Award for Research Excellence    Category:Information science awards

What?
Category:Nevanlinna Prize laureates    Category:Turing Award laureates    ACM SIGPLAN Programming Languages Software Award    Loebner Prize

Whatlist of articles on people who have won the Seymour Cray Computer Engineering Awar?
Category:Seymour Cray Computer Engineering Award recipients    J.W. Graham Medal    Nevanlinna Prize    Sloan Fellowship

What is a category of the Benjamin Franklin Medal laureates in Computer and Cognitive Scienc?
Category:The Benjamin Franklin Medal in Computer and Cognitive Science laureates    Nevanlinna Prize    Eckert–Mauchly Award    Computer Pioneer Award

What?
Category:Turing Award laureates    Category:The Benjamin Franklin Medal in Computer and Cognitive Science laureates    Gerard Salton Award    Stevens Award

What is a computer program designed to simulate an intelligent conversation with one or more human users via auditory or textual methods, primarily for engaging in small talk?
Chatterbox Challenge    Dijkstra Prize    Eckert–Mauchly Award    Turing Award

What is a group of researchers honored by SIGCHI, the Special Interest Group in Computer–Human Interaction of the Association for Computing Machinery?
CHI Academy    Chatterbox Challenge    Nevanlinna Prize    Category:The Benjamin Franklin Medal in Computer and Cognitive Science laureates

Whatlished in 1981 by the Board of Governors of the IEEE Computer Society to recognize and honor the vision of those people whose efforts resulted in the creation and continued vitality of the computer industry?
Computer Pioneer Award    Category:Elliott Cresson Medal recipients    Dahl-Nygaard Prize    Pirelli Internetional Award

What is awarded annually to a senior researcher with outstanding career contributions and a younger researcher who has demonstrated great potential?
Dahl-Nygaard Prize    Machtey Award    J. H. Wilkinson Prize for Numerical Software    Category:Elliott Cresson Medal recipients

What is an academic conference in the field of theoretical computer science?
Danny Lewin Best Student Paper Award    Pirelli Internetional Award    Paris Kanellakis Award    Calgary Challenge

What is an international award sponsored by the Digital Preservation Coalition?
Digital Preservation Award    Loebner Prize    J. H. Wilkinson Prize for Numerical Software    SIGCOMM Award

WhatDistributed Computing is given for outstanding papers on the principles of distributed computing, whose significance and impact on the theory and/or practice of distributed computing has been evident for at least a decade?
Dijkstra Prize    Gödel Prize    Microsoft Award    Jonathan B. Postel Service Award

What is an international organization with a European focus, founded in 1972. Its aim is to facilitate the exchange of ideas and results among theoretical computer scientists as well as to stimulate cooperation between the theoretical and the practical community in computer science?
EATCS Award    IEEE John von Neumann Medal    Jonathan B. Postel Service Award    Ken Kennedy Award

WhatThe  recognizes contributions to digital systems and computer architecture. First awarded in 1979, it was named for John Presper Eckert and John William Mauchly, who between 1943 and 1946 collaborated on the design and construction of the first large scale electronic computing machine, known as ENIAC, the Electronic Numerical Integrator and Computer?
Eckert–Mauchly Award    Category:Computer scientists by award    Category:Nevanlinna Prize laureates    Seymour Cray Computer Engineering Award

WhatThe , also known as the Elliott Cresson Gold Medal, was the highest award given by the Franklin Institute?
Elliott Cresson Medal    John von Neumann Theory Prize    Gordon Bell Prize    Grace Murray Hopper Award

Whattist, a professor of computer science at the University of California, Berkeley?
Eugene L. Lawler Award    IEEE Richard W. Hamming Medal    Van Wijngaarden Award    Computer Pioneer Award

What area of discrete mathematics is sponsored jointly by the Mathematical Programming Society (MPS)  and the American Mathematical Society (AMS)?
Fulkerson Prize    Dahl-Nygaard Prize    Hutter Prize    Category:Dijkstra Prize laureates

What is presented by the Association for Computing Machinery (ACM) Special Interest Group on Information Retrieval (SIGIR) every three years to an individual who has made "significant, sustained and continuing contributions to research in information retrieval"?
Gerard Salton Award    Hutter Prize    Stevens Award    Google–O'Reilly Open Source Award

What is a prize for outstanding papers in theoretical computer science, named after Kurt Gödel and awarded jointly by the European Association for Theoretical Computer Science (EATCS) and the Association for Computing Machinery Special Interest Group on Algorithms and Computation Theory (ACM SIGACT)?
Gödel Prize    Tony Kent Strix award    Machtey Award    Dijkstra Prize

WhatThe  was presented from 2005 to 2009 to individuals for dedication, innovation, leadership and outstanding contribution to open source?
Google–O'Reilly Open Source Award    Eckert–Mauchly Award    Harlan D. Mills Award    Grace Murray Hopper Award

What is an award presented by the Association for Computing Machinery each year in conjunction with the SC Conference series (formerly known as the Supercomputing Conference)?
Gordon Bell Prize    Jon Postel    Pirelli Internetional Award    White Camel award

WhatThe s (named for computer pioneer RADM Grace Hopper) has been awarded by the Association for Computing Machinery (ACM) since 1971. The award goes to a computer professional of age 35 or less who makes a single, significant technical or service contribution?
Grace Murray Hopper Award    SIGCOMM Award    Category:Dijkstra Prize laureates    Microsoft Award

Whatware Engineering Technology, Inc?
Harlan D. Mills Award    Gerard Salton Award    Paris Kanellakis Award    Ken Kennedy Award

WhatHarry H. Goode (30 June 1909 – 30 October 1960) was an American computer engineer and systems engineer and professor at the University of Michigan?
Harry H. Goode Memorial Award    Digital Preservation Award    Nevanlinna Prize    Konrad Zuse Medal

WhatDistinguished Contributions to Automated Deduction is an award given by CADE Inc?
Herbrand Award    Dijkstra Prize    Category:Nevanlinna Prize laureates    Jon Postel

What is a cash prize funded by Marcus Hutter which rewards data compression improvements on a specific 100 MB English text file?
Hutter Prize    Elliott Cresson Medal    Herbrand Award    Seymour Cray Computer Engineering Award

Whatlished by the IEEE Board of Directors in 1990 and may be presented annually "for outstanding  achievements in computer-related science and technology." The achievements may be theoretical, technological, or entrepreneurial, and need not have been made immediately prior to the date of the award?
IEEE John von Neumann Medal    Elliott Cresson Medal    Category:Turing Award laureates    John von Neumann Theory Prize

What is presented annually to up to three persons, for outstanding achievements in information sciences, information systems and information technology?
IEEE Richard W. Hamming Medal    SIGCOMM Award    IEEE Richard W. Hamming Medal    Digital Preservation Award

What is a biannual award given at the IJCAI conference to researcher in artificial intelligence as a recognition of excellence of their career?
IJCAI Award for Research Excellence    White Camel award    Category:Turing Award laureates    Kleene award

What is awarded every four years to honor outstanding contributions to the field of numerical software?
J. H. Wilkinson Prize for Numerical Software    Grace Murray Hopper Award    Harry H. Goode Memorial Award    ACM SIGPLAN Programming Languages Software Award

What is an award given annually by the University of Waterloo and the University of Waterloo Faculty of Mathematics  to "recognize the leadership and many innovative contributions made to the University of Waterloo, and to the Canadian computer industry?
J.W. Graham Medal    Eckert–Mauchly Award    Category:Turing Award laureates    Category:The Benjamin Franklin Medal in Computer and Cognitive Science laureates

WhatThe  of the Institute for Operations Research and the Management Scienc?
John von Neumann Theory Prize    Chatterbox Challenge    Grace Murray Hopper Award    Elliott Cresson Medal

Whattist who made many significant contributions to the development of the Internet, particularly with respect to standards?
Jon Postel    SIGCOMM Award    Microsoft Award    Eugene L. Lawler Award

What is an award named after Jon Postel. The award has been presented every year since 1999 by the Internet Society to "honor a person who has made outstanding contributions in service to the data communications community?
Jonathan B. Postel Service Award    Konrad Zuse Medal    Category:Nevanlinna Prize laureates    Category:Turing Award laureates

Whatlished in 2009 by the Association of Computing Machinery and the IEEE Computer Society in memory of Ken Kennedy, is awarded annually and recognizes substantial contributions to programmability and productivity in computing and substantial community service or mentoring contributions?
Ken Kennedy Award    J.W. Graham Medal    White Camel award    Microsoft Award

WhatThe Kleene Awa?
Kleene award    Gerard Salton Award    Chatterbox Challenge    Nevanlinna Prize

What is a prize for outstanding contributions to the foundations of computer science, named after Donald E?
Knuth Prize    Pirelli Internetional Award    J. H. Wilkinson Prize for Numerical Software    Dahl-Nygaard Prize

What is the highest award of the Gesellschaft für Informatik (the German Computer Science Society), given every two years to one or sometimes two leading German computer scientists?
Konrad Zuse Medal    Harry H. Goode Memorial Award    William C. Carter Award    Danny Lewin Best Student Paper Award

What is an annual competition in artificial intelligence that awards prizes to the chatterbot considered by the judges to be the most human-like?
Loebner Prize    Sidney Fernbach Award    Nevanlinna Prize    Danny Lewin Best Student Paper Award

Whatlished by the British Computer Society in 1998, is presented to individuals who have advanced Information Systems or added significantly to their understanding?
Lovelace Medal    Loebner Prize    SIGMOD Edgar F. Codd Innovations Award    SIGMOD Edgar F. Codd Innovations Award

WhatTh?
Machtey Award    Category:Gödel Prize laureates    Turing Award    Dijkstra Prize

Whattists working in Europe who had made a major contribution to the advancement of science through the use of computational methods?
Microsoft Award    Jonathan B. Postel Service Award    Turing Award    J. H. Wilkinson Prize for Numerical Software

What is awarded once every 4 years at the International Congress of Mathematicians, for outstanding contributions in Mathematical Aspects of Information Sciences includin?
Nevanlinna Prize    Hutter Prize    Category:Gödel Prize laureates    Loebner Prize

Whatris Kanellakis Theory and Practice Award is granted yearly by the Association for Computing Machinery (ACM) to honor "specific theoretical accomplishments that have had a significant and demonstrable effect on the practice of computing"?
Paris Kanellakis Award    Digital Preservation Award    Herbrand Award    Microsoft Award

WhatThe  was first offered in 1996, as the first international multimedia competition for the communication of science & technology conducted entirely on the internet?
Pirelli Internetional Award    Harlan D. Mills Award    Ken Kennedy Award    Category:Computer scientists by award

What is awarded each year by the European Association for Theoretical Computer Science (EATCS) to "a young scientist for outstanding contributions in theoretical computer science, documented by a published paper or a series of published papers." The award is named after Mojzesz Presburger who accomplished his path-breaking work on decidability of the theory of addition (which today is called Presburger arithmetic) as a student in 192?
Presburger Award    Google–O'Reilly Open Source Award    Danny Lewin Best Student Paper Award    IJCAI Award for Research Excellence

What is an award given by the IEEE Computer Society, to recognize significant and innovative contributions in the field of high-performance computing?
Seymour Cray Computer Engineering Award    IEEE Richard W. Hamming Medal    John von Neumann Theory Prize    William C. Carter Award

Whatlished in 1992 by the IEEE Computer Society, in memory of Sidney Fernbach, one of the pioneers in the development and application of high performance computers for the solution of large computational problems as the Division Chief for the Computation Division at Lawrence Livermore Laboratory from the late 1950s through the 1970s?
Sidney Fernbach Award    Stevens Award    Kleene award    Tony Kent Strix award

WhatThe  recognizes lifetime contribution to the field of communication network?
SIGCOMM Award    Nevanlinna Prize    Sidney Fernbach Award    Chatterbox Challenge

What is a lifetime research achievement award given by the ACM Special Interest Group on Management of Data, at its yearly flagship conference (also called SIGMOD)?
SIGMOD Edgar F. Codd Innovations Award    Stevens Award    Fulkerson Prize    Knuth Prize

What are awarded annually by the Alfred P. Sloan Foundation since 1955 to "provide support and recognition to early-career scientists and scholars"?
Sloan Fellowship    Category:Elliott Cresson Medal recipients    Category:Seymour Cray Computer Engineering Award recipients    SIGMOD Edgar F. Codd Innovations Award

What is a software engineering award given in memory of Wayne Stevens. The international  was created to recognize outstanding contributions to the literature or practice of methods for software and systems development?
Stevens Award    Herbrand Award    John von Neumann Theory Prize    Chatterbox Challenge

What is an annual award for outstanding contributions to the field of information retrieval and is presented in memory of Dr Tony Kent, a past Fellow of the Institute of Information Scientists (IIS), who died in 1997. Tony Kent made a major contribution to the development of information science and information services both in the UK and internationally, particularly in the field of chemistry?
Tony Kent Strix award    Sloan Fellowship    Van Wijngaarden Award    ACM Software System Award

Whatlished in 1997 by a generous endowment from Hitachi Ltd., and named in honor of Dr?
Tsutomu Kanai Award    Category:The Benjamin Franklin Medal in Computer and Cognitive Science laureates    SIGMOD Edgar F. Codd Innovations Award    Category:Information science awards

What is an annual prize given by the Association for Computing Machinery (ACM) to "an individual selected for contributions of a technical nature made to the computing community"?
Turing Award    Category:Computer scientists by award    Hutter Prize    Category:Elliott Cresson Medal recipients

Whattist who is considered by many to have been the founding father of informatica (computer science) in the Netherlands?
Van Wijngaarden Award    Hutter Prize    ACM SIGPLAN Programming Languages Software Award    Elliott Cresson Medal

What is given to important contributors to the Perl Programming Language community?
White Camel award    CHI Academy    Google–O'Reilly Open Source Award    Hutter Prize

What is a technical award presented annually since 1997 for individuals whose graduate dissertation research has made an important contribution to the field of dependable computing?
William C. Carter Award    Loebner Prize    Category:Seymour Cray Computer Engineering Award recipients    Digital Preservation Award

