What is an American professional basketball team based in Atlanta, Georgia. They are part of the Southeast Division of the Eastern Conference in the National Basketball Association (NBA)?
Atlanta Hawks    Charlotte Bobcats    Charlotte Bobcats    Philadelphia 76ers

What is a National Basketball Association (NBA) team based in Boston, Massachusetts. They play in the Atlantic Division  of the Eastern Conference?
Boston Celtics    Brooklyn Nets    Utah Jazz    Boston Celtics

What is a professional basketball team based in the New York City borough of Brooklyn. They are members of the Atlantic Division of the Eastern Conference in the National Basketball Association (NBA)?
Brooklyn Nets    New York Knicks    Toronto Raptors    Dallas Mavericks

What is a professional basketball team based in Charlotte, North Carolina. They play American basketball in the Southeast Division of the Eastern Conference in the National Basketball Association?
Charlotte Bobcats    Miami Heat    New Orleans Hornets    Toronto Raptors

What is a professional basketball team based in Chicago, Illinois, playing in the Central Division of the Eastern Conference in the National Basketball Association (NBA)?
Chicago Bulls    Minnesota Timberwolves    Miami Heat    Boston Celtics

What is an American professional basketball team based in Cleveland, Ohio?
Cleveland Cavaliers    Dallas Mavericks    Toronto Raptors    Chicago Bulls

What is a professional basketball team based in Dallas, Texas?
Dallas Mavericks    Orlando Magic    Orlando Magic    San Antonio Spurs

What is a professional basketball team based in Denver, Colorado that plays in the National Basketball Association?
Denver Nuggets    Milwaukee Bucks    Cleveland Cavaliers    Golden State Warriors

What is a franchise of the National Basketball Association (NBA) based in Auburn Hills, Michigan in Metro Detroit?
Detroit Pistons    Los Angeles Lakers    Minnesota Timberwolves    Philadelphia 76ers

What is an American professional basketball team based in Oakland, California. They are part of the Pacific Division of the Western Conference in the National Basketball Association (NBA)?
Golden State Warriors    Oklahoma City Thunder    Philadelphia 76ers    Houston Rockets

What is an American professional basketball team based in Houston, Texas. The team plays in the Southwest Division of the Western Conference in the National Basketball Association (NBA)?
Houston Rockets    Dallas Mavericks    Los Angeles Clippers    Washington Wizards

What is a professional basketball team based in Indianapolis, Indiana. They are members of the Central Division in the Eastern Conference of the National Basketball Association (NBA)?
Indiana Pacers    San Antonio Spurs    Oklahoma City Thunder    New York Knicks

What is a professional basketball team in the National Basketball Association, located in Los Angeles, California, United States of America?
Los Angeles Clippers    Utah Jazz    Houston Rockets    Utah Jazz

What is an American professional basketball team based in Los Angeles, California. They play in the Pacific Division of the Western Conference in the National Basketball Association (NBA)?
Los Angeles Lakers    Utah Jazz    Washington Wizards    Charlotte Bobcats

What is a professional basketball team based in Memphis, Tennessee, USA. The team is part of the Southwest Division of the Western Conference in the National Basketball Association (NBA)?
Memphis Grizzlies    Orlando Magic    Washington Wizards    Charlotte Bobcats

What is a professional basketball team based in Miami, Miami-Dade County, Florida, United States?
Miami Heat    New Orleans Hornets    Cleveland Cavaliers    Washington Wizards

What is a professional basketball team based in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, United States. They are part of the Central Division of the Eastern Conference in the National Basketball Association (NBA)?
Milwaukee Bucks    Memphis Grizzlies    Chicago Bulls    New Orleans Hornets

What is an American professional basketball team based in Minneapolis, Minnesota?
Minnesota Timberwolves    Milwaukee Bucks    San Antonio Spurs    Denver Nuggets

What is a professional basketball team based in New Orleans, Louisiana.  They play in the Southwest Division of the Western Conference of the National Basketball Association?
New Orleans Hornets    Los Angeles Lakers    Milwaukee Bucks    Toronto Raptors

What is a professional basketball team based in New York City, New York?
New York Knicks    Los Angeles Lakers    New York Knicks    Houston Rockets

What is a professional basketball franchise based in Oklahoma City, Oklahoma. They play in the Northwest Division of the Western Conference in the National Basketball Association (NBA); their home court is at Chesapeake Energy Arena?
Oklahoma City Thunder    Golden State Warriors    Utah Jazz    Chicago Bulls

What is an American professional basketball team based in Orlando, Florida. They are part of the Southeast Division of the Eastern Conference in the National Basketball Association (NBA)?
Orlando Magic    Sacramento Kings    Golden State Warriors    Dallas Mavericks

What is a professional basketball team based in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania?
Philadelphia 76ers    Toronto Raptors    Oklahoma City Thunder    Sacramento Kings

What is a professional basketball team based in Phoenix, Arizona. They are members of the Pacific Division of the Western Conference in the National Basketball Association (NBA), and the only team in their division not to be based in California?
Phoenix Suns    Indiana Pacers    Detroit Pistons    Minnesota Timberwolves

What is an American professional basketball team based in Portland, Oregon?
Portland Trail Blazers    Cleveland Cavaliers    Philadelphia 76ers    Orlando Magic

What is a professional basketball team based in Sacramento, California, United States?
Sacramento Kings    Phoenix Suns    Portland Trail Blazers    Dallas Mavericks

What is an American professional basketball team based in San Antonio, Texas. They are part of the Southwest Division of the Western Conference in the National Basketball Association (NBA)?
San Antonio Spurs    Cleveland Cavaliers    Portland Trail Blazers    Indiana Pacers

What is a professional basketball team based in Toronto, Ontario. They are part of the Atlantic Division of the Eastern Conference in the National Basketball Association (NBA)?
Toronto Raptors    Philadelphia 76ers    Dallas Mavericks    New Orleans Hornets

What is a professional basketball team based in Salt Lake City, Utah. They is a part of the Northwest Division in the Western Conference in the National Basketball Association (NBA)?
Utah Jazz    Philadelphia 76ers    New York Knicks    Milwaukee Bucks

What is a professional basketball franchise based in Washington, D.C. They are part of the Southeast Division of the Eastern Conference in the National Basketball Association?
Washington Wizards    Philadelphia 76ers    Los Angeles Clippers    Charlotte Bobcats

