What is Western Canada's largest outdoor family amusement park. The park is located in Springbank, Rocky View County, Alberta,  west of the city of Calgary on the Trans-Canada Highway?
Calaway Park
What is the world's second largest indoor amusement park, situated in the West Edmonton Mall in Edmonton, Alberta, Canada?
Galaxyland
What is an indoor amusement park inside the Crystal Palace Complex adjacent to the Champlain Place shopping mall in the city of Dieppe, New Brunswick, Canada near Moncton?
Crystal Palace Amusement Park
What is a water park located in Moncton, New Brunswick, Canada?
Magic Mountain Water Park
What is a seasonal attraction composed of two parks: Upper Clements Theme Park and Upper Clements Adventure Park?
Upper Clements Park
What is a family-owned safari park situated in Flamborough, Hamilton, Ontario, Canada, about  west of Toronto?
African Lion Safari
What is a theme waterpark located in Limoges, Ontario, Canada, about  east of Ottawa. It opened to the public on June 7, 2010. The park, built by Village Vacances Valcartier at about 45 million, is on a  site and is Canada’s largest waterpark?
Calypso Park
What is a chain of Lego-themed theme parks. They are not fully owned by Lego Group itself; rather they are owned and operated by the British theme park company Merlin Entertainment?
Legoland
What may refer to one of the following location?
Crystal Beach
What is a mixed-use district in Toronto, Ontario, Canada, by the shoreline of Lake Ontario, just west of downtown?
Exhibition Place
What is a small, family resort that offers a water park, par 71 golf course, RV Park & campground, Motel and 2 bedroom villa units in Ontario, Canada, located about 8 km (5 mi) east of Cobden along Highway 17. Built on the site of the Astrolabe's discovery,  features 5 water slides, a splash pad, large water trampolines, paddleboats, mini-golf, a petting farm and a representation of Noah's ark which contains the resort's reservations desk, gift shop and restaurant?
Logos Land
What is a themed amusement and animal exhibition park in the city of Niagara Falls, Ontario, Canada?
MarineLand
What is a Canadian company which operates a large Family Entertainment Centre in Mississauga, Ontario, Canada?
Playdium
What is a 140-hectare (300 acre) park located along a stretch of the Thames River in London, Ontario, Canada?
Storybook Gardens
Whatlished in 1955 to facilitate the building of the Metro Toronto Gardiner Expressway project?
Sunnyside Amusement Park
What is located in Brampton, Ontario, and was Canada's largest water-based fun park until Calypso Park  was built in 2010. Opened in 1986, the  park is located next to the Clairville Reservoir, Clairville Conservation Area and the Humber River (Ontario)?
Wild Water Kingdom
What is a term for a region in the Carina Nebula imaged by the Hubble Space Telescope. The view was captured by the then new Wide Field Camera 3, though the region was also viewed by the previous generation instrument?
Mystic Mountain
What is a historic and recreational complex located in the city of Aguascalientes, Aguascalientes, in the Mexican state of Aguascalientes?
La Estacion Theme Park
What is a Mexican zoo park that was established in 1972 by Captain Carlos Camacho Espíritu. It is located about  from the city of Puebla?
Africam Safari
What is the practice of raising turtles and tortoises of various species commercially. Raised animals are sold for use as gourmet food, traditional medicine ingredients, or as pets?
Turtle Farm
What is a privately owned and operated theme park, resort and self-described ecotourism development located in the Riviera Maya, a portion of the Caribbean coastline of Mexico's state of Quintana Roo that has been designated as a zone for tourism development?
Xcaret Park
Whater may refer t?
Xplor
What is an amusement park in Huntsville, Alabam?
Southern Adventures
What is a  water and amusement park located a quarter-mile from the Gulf of Mexico in the city of Gulf Shores, Alabama, on Gulf Shores Parkway (Alabama State Route 59)?
Waterville USA
What is a Water park located in Arkadelphia, Arkansas. [http://lasr.net/pages/city.php?Arkadelphia&AR&Arkadelphia+Aquatic+Park&City_ID=AR0401001&Attraction_ID=AR0401001a003&VA=Y]  During the 2006 season, nearly 25,000 individuals visited the park?
Arkadelphia Aquatic Park
What is a small amusement park located in Burns Park, North Little Rock, Arkansas. The park features several small family rides including a ferris wheel and a train?
Funland Amusement Park
What is an amusement park and water park located in Hot Springs, Arkansas, about 50 miles from Little Rock?
Magic Springs and Crystal Falls
What is an outdoor water park located in North Little Rock, Arkansas, United States. It is the largest water park in the state of Arkansas?
Wild River Country
What is a Water park located in Little Rock, Arkansas.[http://lasr.net/pages/city.php?Little%20Rock&Arkansas&City_ID=AR0203012&VA=Y&Attraction_ID=AR0203012a01?
Willow Springs Water Park
What is a garden-themed family theme park in Gilroy, California, United States, and the current location of the world-famous Circus Trees created by Axel Erlandson?
Gilroy Gardens
What is the name of three water theme parks located in Sacramento, San Dimas, and San Jose, California?
Raging Waters
What is an oceanfront amusement park in Santa Cruz, California. Founded in 1907, it is California's oldest surviving amusement park  and one of the few seaside parks on the West Coast of the United States?
Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk
What is a reggae music festival first staged in 1978 in the northern part of Jamaica. In 1985 it expanded with the addition of an international touring festival?
Sunsplash
What is a  zoo located in southeastern Oakland, California, United States?
Oakland Zoo
What is the name of three water theme parks located in Sacramento, San Dimas, and San Jose, California?
Raging Waters
What is a  animal theme park located in Vallejo, California?
Six Flags Discovery Kingdom
What is a water park located in Concord, California. It was developed, owned and operated by Premier Parks, and now it is under the management of Palace Entertainment?
Waterworld California
What is a water park located in Central Park in Fremont, Californi?
Aqua Adventure
What is the name of several parks containing a splash pad. The original is in Oakland, California, along Lake Park Ave, between Grand Ave and Lakeshore Ave, and north of the 580 Freeway?
Splash Pad Park
What is an oceanfront amusement park located in Santa Monica, Californi?
Pacific Park
What is the name of three water theme parks located in Sacramento, San Dimas, and San Jose, California?
Raging Waters
What is the name of a chain of water parks that are part of the Six Flags amusement park chain?
Six Flags Hurricane Harbor
What is a 260-acre theme park located in Valencia, Santa Clarita, California, north of Los Angeles?
Six Flags Magic Mountain
What is a movie studio and theme park in the unincorporated Universal City community of Los Angeles County, California, United States?
Universal Studios Hollywood
What is an oceanfront amusement park located in Santa Monica, Californi?
Pacific Park
What is a water park operated by the city of Palmdale, California, opened in 2006. It is located on the grounds of the Palmdale Oasis Park & Recreation Center in the southeast portion of the city?
Dry Town Water Park
What is a theme park located in Anaheim, California near the city of Stanton. The park's slogan is "The Little Theme Park that's BIG on Family Fun"?
Adventure City
WhatDisney California Adventure is a theme park located in Anaheim, California, it is owned and operated by The Walt Disney Company through its Parks and Resorts division?
Disney California Adventure Park
What is a theme park located in Anaheim, California, owned and operated by the Walt Disney Parks and Resorts division of The Walt Disney Company?
Disneyland
What is a chain of water parks owned and operated by SeaWorld Parks & Entertainment. Aquatica parks are operating in Orlando, Florida and San Antonio, Texas, with a third location set to open in Chula Vista, California in 201?
Aquatica San Diego
What is a theme park and miniature park located in Carlsbad, California, based around the Lego toy brand?
Legoland California
What is an animal theme park, oceanarium, and marine mammal park, located in San Diego, California, United States?
SeaWorld San Diego
What is an amusement park in Denver, Colorado.  It is owned by CNL Lifestyle Properties and operated by Herschend Family Entertainment?
Elitch Gardens Theme Park
What is a family-owned amusement park in Lakeside, Colorado near Denver. Originally named White City, it was opened in 1908 as a popular amusement resort adjacent to Lake Rhoda spearheaded by prominent Denver brewer Adolph Zang?
Lakeside Amusement Park
What is an amusement park located in Bristol, Connecticut, United States and a part of the neighboring town of Southington; the lake itself lies completely in Southington?
Lake Compounce
What is a beachfront neighborhood of San Diego, Californi?
Ocean Beach Park
What, which was once called Lake Quassapaug Amusement Park, was founded as an amusement park in 1908 and sits on the south shore of Lake Quassapaug in Middlebury, Connecticut, United States?
Quassy Amusement Park
What is a group of amusement parks located in Florida, New York, North Carolina and Texas?
Adventure Landing
What is a water park located at the Walt Disney World Resort in Bay Lake, Florid?
Blizzard Beach
What is a  19th century African-themed animal theme park located in the city of Tampa, Florida?
Busch Gardens Tampa Bay
What is a waterpark and family entertainment center located in Daytona Beach which is open year round for its dry attractions and March through October for the waterpark?
Daytona Lagoon
What is a theme park owned and operated by SeaWorld Parks & Entertainment, a subsidiary of The Blackstone Group, and located in Orlando, Florida?
Discovery Cove
What is an "indoor interactive theme park" located in Downtown Disney at the Walt Disney World Resort in Florida?
DisneyQuest
What is the second of four theme parks built at Walt Disney World in Bay Lake, Florida?
Epcot
What is a  theme park and wildlife preserve located along South Orange Blossom Trail in Orlando, Florida?
Gatorland
What is a Christian theme park in Orlando, Florida and registered non-profit corporation?
Holy Land Experience
What is a theme park in Winter Haven, Florida.  It opened October 15, 2011. The park encompasses , making  the world's largest Legoland park?
Legoland Florida
What is a drive-through safari park located in Loxahatchee (near West Palm Beach), in Palm Beach County, Florida?
Lion Country Safari
What is the first of four theme parks built at the Walt Disney World Resort in Bay Lake, Florida?
Magic Kingdom
What is a  oceanarium located on the island of Virginia Key in Biscayne Bay, Miami-Dade County, Florida, United States and is located near downtown Miami?
Miami Seaquarium
What is a water park in West Palm Beach, Florida, that occupies 30 acres near I-9?
Rapids Water Park
What is a theme park, and marine-life based zoological park, in Orlando, Florida. It is owned and operated by SeaWorld Parks & Entertainment, a subsidiary of The Blackstone Group?
SeaWorld Orlando
Whathis is a complete list of islands and other locations in the Pirates of the Caribbean films series. Some locations in the series of films are real, others are fictional?
Shipwreck Island
What is a zoological park located in Silver Springs, Florida, USA, east of Ocala?
Silver Springs Nature Theme Park
What is a water park located at the Walt Disney World Resort in Lake Buena Vista, Florida, United States?
Typhoon Lagoon
What is an American theme park located in Orlando, Florida. Opened on June 7, 1990, the park's theme is the entertainment industry, in particular movies and television?
Universal Studios Florida
What is a natural tourist attraction located in Weeki Wachee, Florida, where underwater performances by "mermaids", women dressed with fins about their legs as well as other fancy outfits, can be viewed in an aquarium-like setting in the spring of the Weeki Wachee River?
Weeki Wachee Springs
What is a water park in Silver Springs, Florida. It is the sister park of Silver Springs Theme Park in Silver Springs?
Wild Waters
What is an amusement park located on Lakeview Drive in Lakeview, Georgia (mailing address Rossville, Georgia) near Chattanooga, Tennessee?
Lake Winnepesaukah
What is a  theme park located west of Atlanta, in Austell, Georgia, United States. Opened in 1967, it is the second park in the Six Flags chain, after the original opening in 1961 in Texas?
Six Flags Over Georgia
What is a  water park located northwest of Atlanta, in unincorporated Cobb County. Originally opening in 1984 as White Water Atlanta, the park became part of the Six Flags family of parks in 1999. Today, it is marketed as a second gate to Six Flags Over Georgia, and the two parks often cross-promote each other?
Six Flags White Water
What is located  from Valdosta, Georgia, United States. It is owned by Herschend Family Entertainment?
Wild Adventures
What is an Association of Zoos and Aquariums (AZA) accredited zoological park in Atlanta, Georgia?
Zoo Atlanta
What is a marine mammal park, bird sanctuary and aquarium near Makapuʻu Point, north of Hanauma Bay on the island of Oahu in Hawaii, United States?
Sea Life Park
What is an amusement park located in northern Idaho, United States, near the town of Coeur d'Alene, and just 47 miles from Spokane, Washington on U.S?
Silverwood Theme Park
What is a Rockford Park District waterpark in Cherry Valley, Winnebago County, Illinois.  It is located next to the interchange between Interstate 39/U.S?
Magic Waters
What is a Six Flags theme park in the Chicago metropolitan area, located in Gurnee, Illinois?
Six Flags Great America
What is the name of a chain of water parks that are part of the Six Flags amusement park chain?
Six Flags Hurricane Harbor
What is an amusement park and resort located on Lake Shafer in Monticello, Indian?
Indiana Beach
What is a city in Dickinson County, Iowa, United States. The population was 1,126 in the 2010 census, a decline from the 1,162 population in the 2000 census?
Arnolds Park
What is a family-owned and operated company based in New Braunfels, Texas, USA.  began its first park,  Waterpark Resort, in 1979. Since then,  has developed three waterparks located in Texas and one in Kansas City, Kansas?
Schlitterbahn
What is an amusement park, campground and automobile race track located in Warren County, Kentucky, just outside the limits of the city of Bowling Green?
Beech Bend Park
What is a family-owned amusement park located in Saco, Maine, in the United States?
Funtown Splashtown USA
What is a seasonal amusement park located in Old Orchard Beach, Maine.  It has operated on the same site since 190?
Palace Playland
What is a theme park located in Upper Marlboro, Maryland. It is situated  east of Washington D.C?
Six Flags America
What is the name of a chain of water parks that are part of the Six Flags amusement park chain?
Six Flags Hurricane Harbor
What is a Six Flags theme park, named for the New England region, in which it is located?
Six Flags New England
What is a water park located in East Wareham, Massachusetts?
Water Wizz
What is a township in Marshall County, Minnesota, United States. The population was 52 at the 2000 census?
Como Town
What is the seven-acre (28,000 m²) indoor amusement park located in the center of the Mall of America (MOA), in Bloomington, Minnesota, USA?
Nickelodeon Universe
What is an amusement park located in Brainerd, Minnesota, on This Old Farm. Its trademark is the  animated and talking statue of Paul Bunyan?
Paul Bunyan Land
What is a 125 acre (0.5 km²) amusement park located in Shakopee, Minnesota, USA and is currently the largest amusement park in the Upper Midwest United States?
Valleyfair
What is a tropically-themed water park that opened on May 31, 1982 in Kansas City, Missouri to celebrate Worlds of Fun's 10th year anniversary?
Oceans of Fun
What is a theme park in the state of Missouri. Opened on May 1, 1960, the park is located between Branson and Branson West on Missouri Route 76. The park is an 1880's-themed experience that fits Branson's vision as a family-friendly vacation destination with down-home charm?
Silver Dollar City
What is the name of a chain of water parks that are part of the Six Flags amusement park chain?
Six Flags Hurricane Harbor
What is located in Branson, Missouri and is known by most in the area as just White Water?
White Water Branson
What is a 235-acre amusement park in Kansas City, Missouri, United States. The park opened in 1973 and was originally built by Mid-America Enterprises, owned by Lamar Hunt?
Worlds of Fun
What is a  indoor amusement park (formerly known as Grand Slam Canyon) located at Circus Circus in Winchester, Nevada on the Las Vegas Strip?
Adventuredome
What is a tower, hotel, and casino located on Las Vegas Boulevard just north of the Las Vegas Strip in Las Vegas, Nevada, United States?
Stratosphere Tower
What is an amusement park located in Salem, New Hampshire, United States, about  north of Boston, Massachusetts?
Canobie Lake Park
What is a theme park located in Glen, New Hampshir?
Story Land
What is located in Portsmouth, New Hampshire, United States?
Water Country
What is an amusement park situated on a pier, in Seaside Heights, New Jersey, United States.   was partially destroyed, and indefinitely closed, on October 29, 2012, after part of the pier collapsed into the Atlantic Ocean due to the extreme natural forces generated by Hurricane Sandy?
Casino Pier
What is a small amusement park located in Clementon, New Jersey in Camden County, New Jersey, United States right on Clementon Lake and close to the Pine Valley Golf Club?
Clementon Amusement Park
What is a theme park in Jackson Township, Ocean County, New Jersey, United States, owned by Six Flags Entertainment Corp.?
Six Flags Great Adventure
What is a  amusement pier in Atlantic City, New Jersey, located across The Boardwalk from Trump Taj Mahal?
Steel Pier
What is a  amusement park located in Sunland Park, New Mexico. It was located in Ascarate Park in El Paso, Texas from 1960 until 2006, but after conflicts with the county of El Paso, owner Pat Thomson decided to move it across the Rio Grande to Sunland Park where the owner of Sunland Park Casino donated land right across from his casino?
Western Playland
What is a theme park resort located between Buffalo and Rochester in Corfu, New York, United States, south of the New York State Thruway (I-90) on State Highway 77. It is owned by CNL Lifestyle Properties and operated by Herschend Family Entertainment?
Darien Lake
What is an amusement park in Old Forge, New York?
Enchanted Forest Water Safari
What is a name shared by dozens of currently operating and defunct amusement parks that have opened on every continent except Antarctica since 190?
Luna Park
Whatlished in 1898 by the Jamestown & Lake Erie Railway as a picnic ground?
Midway State Park
What is an historic amusement park in Irondequoit, a suburb of Rochester, New York, United States?
Seabreeze Amusement Park
What is a seasonal traditional-style amusement park, which is located in the Wollman Rink of Central Park in Manhattan, New York City?
Victorian Gardens
What is a  amusement park, located adjacent to Interstate 77 on the border between North and South Carolina, in Charlotte and Fort Mill, respectively?
Carowinds
What is a  amusement park located on a Lake Erie peninsula in Sandusky, Ohio, United States. Opened in 1870, it is the second-oldest operating amusement park in the United States behind Lake Compounce?
Cedar Point
What is a peninsula and beach on the Atlantic Ocean in southern Brooklyn, New York City, New York, United States?
Coney Island
What is a  amusement park located  northeast of Cincinnati in Mason, Ohio. It is owned and operated by Cedar Fair Entertainment Company?
Kings Island
What is an 11-ride amusement park located in Brooklyn, Ohio, designed specifically for children and families?
Memphis Kiddie Park
What is a western-themed amusement park in Oklahoma City.  It is owned by CNL Lifestyle Properties and operated by Premier Attractions Management?
Frontier City
What is a water park in Oklahoma City, Oklahoma built in 1981. Originally built by the Herschend Family Entertainment Corporation,  was picked up by Premier Parks (then known as Tierco) in 1991 and its name was changed from White Water to ?
White Water Bay
What is a small amusement park located  south of downtown Portland, Oregon USA, near the Sellwood Bridge?
Oaks Amusement Park
What is a water park located in the Pocono Mountains, in Tannersville, Pennsylvania at Big Pocono State Park?
Camelbeach Waterpark
What is a summer amusement resort, located in Conneaut Lake, Pennsylvania, USA. It has long served as a regional tourist destination, and is loved by roller coaster enthusiasts for its classic Blue Streak coaster, which was recently classified as "historic" by the group American Coaster Enthusiasts?
Conneaut Lake Park
What is a  amusement park just east of Lancaster, Pennsylvania, appealing primarily to families with small children?
Dutch Wonderland
What is a family theme park situated in Hershey, Derry Township, Pennsylvania, United States, about  east of Harrisburg, and  west of Philadelphia?
Hersheypark
What is a family amusement park situated in the Laurel Highlands near Ligonier, Pennsylvania, United States, about  east of Pittsburgh,  along US Route 30. Founded in 1878 as a campground along the Ligonier Valley Railroad by Thomas Mellon, Idlewild is the oldest amusement park in Pennsylvania and the third oldest operating amusement park in the United States behind Lake Compounce and Cedar Point?
Idlewild and Soak Zone
What is an amusement park located in West Mifflin, Pennsylvania, a suburb of Pittsburgh. The park first opened in 1898 as a "trolley park" attraction at the end of the Mellon family's Monongahela Street Railway?
Kennywood
What is a family-owned and -operated amusement park, picnic grove, and campground in Elysburg, Pennsylvania?
Knoebels Amusement Resort
What, located in Altoona, Pennsylvania, houses the world's oldest-surviving roller coaster, the Leap-The-Dips?
Lakemont Park
What is a theme park in Langhorne, Pennsylvania based on the Sesame Street television program?
Sesame Place
What is an amusement / water park in Erie, Pennsylvania located at the base of Presque Isle?
Waldameer Park
What is a water park located in East Wareham, Massachusetts?
Water Wizz
What is Myrtle Beach, South Carolina's only seaside amusement park and oceanfront waterpark?
Family Kingdom Amusement Park
What is a theme park owned by entertainer Dolly Parton and Herschend Family Entertainment. It is located in Pigeon Forge, Tennessee?
Dollywood
What is an amusement park and ski area, located in the mountains overlooking Gatlinburg, Tennessee, USA?
Ober Gatlinburg
What is a resort located in New Caney, Texas, approximately  north of Houston that is scheduled to open to the public in 2014 or 2015. Contour Entertainment is the resort's master planner and lead designer?
Earth Quest Adventures
What is a Pleasure pier in Galveston, Texas, United States. Opened in Summer 2012, it has 1 roller coaster, 15 rides, carnival games and souvenir shops?
Galveston Island Historic Pleasure Pier
What is a small family-owned traditional amusement park, located in Lubbock, Texas, USA within Lubbock's Mackenzie Park?
Joyland Amusement Park
What is a hotel and restaurant destination in Kemah, Texas, USA. The main attractions of the  complex, which opened in 1997, are its many restaurants overlooking Galveston Bay?
Kemah Boardwalk
What is a small amusement park located in Carrollton, Texas, Dallas County, Texas?
Sandy Lake Amusement Park
What is a family-owned and operated company based in New Braunfels, Texas, USA.  began its first park,  Waterpark Resort, in 1979. Since then,  has developed three waterparks located in Texas and one in Kansas City, Kansas?
Schlitterbahn
What is a  marine mammal park, oceanarium, and animal theme park, located in the Westover Hills District of San Antonio, Texas?
SeaWorld San Antonio
What is a theme park located on approximately  of land in San Antonio, Texas, USA. It is owned by Six Flags?
Six Flags Fiesta Texas
What is the name of a chain of water parks that are part of the Six Flags amusement park chain?
Six Flags Hurricane Harbor
What is a 212-acre theme park located in Arlington, Texas, east of Fort Worth and about  west of Dallas?
Six Flags Over Texas
What is an amusement park in Farmington, Utah, United States located about seventeen miles (27 km) north of Salt Lake City?
Lagoon Amusement Park
What is a  theme park located in James City County, Virginia, about 3 miles (5 km) southeast of Williamsburg, originally developed by Anheuser-Busch (A-B) and currently owned by SeaWorld Parks & Entertainment, a division of The Blackstone Group?
Busch Gardens Williamsburg
What is an amusement park in Doswell, Virginia  north of Richmond and  south of Washington, DC, off Interstate 9?
Kings Dominion
What is a water theme park in York County, Virginia, about 3 miles (5 km) southeast of Williamsburg, Virginia, USA?
Water Country USA
What is an amusement park in Federal Way, Washington. Opened in 1977, the park is a popular summer destination in the Pacific Northwest and is the largest of its kind in the area?
Wild Waves Theme Park
What is a water park resort chain with locations in Wisconsin Dells, Wisconsin and Sandusky, Ohio?
Kalahari Resorts
What is an amusement park located in Marshall, Wisconsin, USA.  features The Whisky River Railway, a 1/3 size railroad operating an array of steam and diesel engines and proto-typical freight and passenger cars with over 3 miles of track on the ground?
Little Amerricka
Whatuis A. Ferré Bayamón, Puerto Rico (Luis A. Ferré Science Park) is an educational and recreational park located in Bayamón, Puerto Rico focused on science-related exhibitions?
Parque de las Ciencias
What is a Brazilian theme park located at Km 72 of Bandeirantes Highway, Vinhedo in the state of São Paulo?
Hopi Hari
What was a park in Rio de Janeiro which designed to be one of the most modern amusement parks in Latin America?
Terra Encantada
What is a Chilean amusement park. The park opened in 1978 and is located in a corner of the O'Higgins Park in Santiago, Chile?
Fantasilandia
What is a theme park located in the department of Quindío, Colombia, 4 km south-west of the town of Montenegro and 11 km west of the departmental capital city Armenia?
Colombian National Coffee Park
What?
Mundo Aventura
What is a farming theme park that promotes contact between humans and nature, intended for those who live in the city and to create awareness about nature?
PANACA
What is a greenspace and entertainment and sports complex located in the middle of the city of Bogotá, Colombia?
Salitre Magico
What is an amusement park in Quito, Ecuador. The park is part of a much larger entertainment complex named the TelefériQo?
Vulqano Park
What is a theme park located near Mérida, Venezuela. It depicts a typical Andean town in the 1930s?
Los Aleros
What is a theme park in Guatemala. It is located in the Retalhuleu Department in the southwest of the country?
Xetulul Theme Park
What is a water park in Guatemala. It is located in the Retalhuleu Department in the southwest of the country?
Xocomil
