Whathis is a list of mammals found in Indonesia. made  by Quinton Tarlton and Morgan Tarlto?
List of mammals of Indonesia    Pardofelis    Large treeshrew    Neriad horseshoe bat

WhatThe mammal species of Borneo include 288 species of terrestrial and 91 species of marine mammals recorded within the territorial boundaries of Brunei, Indonesia and Malaysia?
Mammals of Borneo    Spectacled flying fox    Andrew's hill rat    Javan tiger

Whatlis), also known as the black-handed gibbon, is an Old World primate in the gibbon family?
Agile gibbon    Small-eared rat    Sumatran water shrew    Halmahera naked-backed fruit bat

What is a species of rodent in the family Murida?
Andrew's hill rat    Homo floresiensis    Dusky fruit bat    Peters's myotis

What are a subgenus of Bubalus comprising two species native to Indonesia: the mountain anoa (Bubalus quarlesi) and the lowland anoa (Bubalus depressicornis)?
Anoa    Greenish naked-backed fruit bat    Common treeshrew    Mountain treeshrew

What is a species of rodent in the Sciuridae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Arrow flying squirrel    Javan lutung    Painted bat    Moluccan flying fox

What is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Ashy-headed flying fox    Mentawai long-tailed giant rat    North Sulawesi babirusa    Sody's tree-rat

What is a widespread, adaptable species of shrew found mainly in South Asia but introduced widely throughout Asia?
Asian house shrew    Sulawesi shrew    Sulawesi naked-backed fruit bat    Proboscis monkey

What is a proposed species of babirusa from the Indonesian island of Sulawesi?
Babyrousa bolabatuensis    Spectral tarsier    Short-tailed gymnure    Common blossom bat

Whatris balica), harimau Bali in Indonesian, or referred to as samong in archaic Balinese language, was a subspecies of tiger which was found solely on the small Indonesian island of Bali?
Bali tiger    Sulawesi soft-furred rat    Buru babirusa    Sunda stink badger

What is a linsang found in South Asia. It is considered widespread throughout its range, but due to its small size and semi-arboreal nature, it has been infrequently recorded, and thus its population status is difficult to assess?
Banded linsang    Bornean yellow muntjac    Sulawesi bear cuscus    Tarsius fuscus

What is a civet found in the tall forests of Burma, Indonesia, Malaysia, and Thailand?
Banded palm civet    Greater mouse-deer    Malayan civet    Painted bat

Whattis femoralis) is a species of primate in the Cercopithecidae family. It is endemic to the Thai-Malay Peninsula and the Indonesia island of Sumatra?
Banded surili    Sulawesi flying fox    Long-tailed pygmy possum    Javan tailless fruit bat

Whatsis) is a species of marsupial in the Phalangeridae famil?
Banggai cuscus    Sumatran surili    Pygmy treeshrew    Wild water buffalo

Whatnister's Rat, or Great Key Island Mosaic-tailed Rat, or Great Key Island Melomys or Great Kai Island Melomys (Melomys bannisteri) is a species of rodent of the genus Melomys?
Bannister's rat    Malayan civet    Sulawesi shrew    Sunda porcupine

What is a species of wild cattle found in Southeast Asia?
Banteng    Striped treeshrew    Long-tongued fruit bat    Sulawesi naked-backed fruit bat

Whatbare-backed rousette (Rousettus spinalatus) is a species of megaba?
Bare-backed rousette    Sunda pangolin    Minahassa Ranee Mouse    Pagai Island macaque

What is a species of rodent in the Sciuridae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Bartel's flying squirrel    Indonesian short-nosed fruit bat    Sumatran long-tailed shrew    Neriad horseshoe bat

What is a bat found in South Asia and Southeast Asia from Sri Lanka and India in the west to Indonesia and the Philippines in the east?
Lesser false vampire bat    Dayak fruit bat    Sulawesi naked-backed fruit bat    Pen-tailed treeshrew

Whatxis kuhlii, also known as Kuhl's hog deer or Bawean hog deer, is a highly threatened species of deer found only in the island of Bawean (Gresik Regency) in Indonesia?
Bawean deer    Thomas's langur    Category:Rodents of Indonesia    Heavenly hill rat

Whatlis badia), also known as the Bornean cat, Bornean bay cat, or Bornean marbled cat, is a wild cat endemic to the island of Borneo that appears relatively rare compared to sympatric felids, based on the paucity of historical as well as recent records?
Bay cat    Crested roundleaf bat    Timor roundleaf bat    Nobkirelch

What is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Beaufort's naked-backed fruit bat    Large treeshrew    Crested roundleaf bat    Lowland long-nosed squirrel

What is a species of mammal in the Soricidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Beccari's shrew    Siau Island tarsier    Mammals of Borneo    Manusela mosaic-tailed rat

What is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Biak naked-backed fruit bat    Timor shrew    Painted bat    Celebes crested macaque

What is a species of bat in the family Hipposideridae?
Biak roundleaf bat    Bornean yellow muntjac    Pig-tailed langur    Sumatran tiger

Whateared Roundleaf Bat (Hipposideros macrobullatus) is a species of bat in the family Hipposideridae?
Big-eared roundleaf bat    Spotted-winged fruit bat    Hose's langur    Category:Rodents of Indonesia

Whattis binturong), also known as bearcat and Palawan binturong, is a viverrid found in South and Southeast Asia?
Binturong    Small-toothed palm civet    Category:Mammals of New Guinea    Flores shrew

What is a megabat in the family Pteropodidae. Members of the genus Pteropus include the largest bats in the world?
Black flying fox    Javan tailless fruit bat    Sumatran tiger    Pig-tailed langur

What is an endangered species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Black-bearded flying fox    Halmahera blossom bat    Sulawesi free-tailed bat    Timor roundleaf bat

What is a species of megabat in the monotypic genus Chironax?
Black-capped fruit bat    Java warty pig    Beaufort's naked-backed fruit bat    Linduan rousette

What is a species of mammal in the Soricidae family. It is endemic to Indonesi?
Black-footed shrew    Wild boar    Sumatran serow    Long-tongued nectar bat

What is a species of marsupial in the family Phalangeridae. It is endemic to the two small islands of Ternate and Tidore, west of the island of Halmahera in North Maluku province, Indonesi?
Blue-eyed cuscus    Bay cat    Sulawesi rousette    Siberut flying squirrel

What is a species of pig. It can be recognized by its prominent beard?
Bornean bearded pig    Lesser mouse-deer    Bannister's rat    Papillose woolly bat

What is a member of the Mustelidae family?
Bornean ferret-badger    Long-footed treeshrew    Bare-backed rousette    Long-tailed porcupine

What is a species of orangutan native to the island of Borneo. Together with the Sumatran orangutan, it belongs to the only genus of great apes native to Asia?
Bornean orangutan    Hipposideros sorenseni    Water buffalo    Tarsius fuscus

Whatbis), also known as the Bornean agile gibbon or southern gibbon, is an endangered species of gibbon endemic to southern Borneo, between the Kapuas and Barito rivers?
Bornean white-bearded gibbon    Long-tailed porcupine    Irrawaddy dolphin    Irrawaddy dolphin

What is restricted to the moist forests of Borneo where it lives alongside the common muntjac?
Bornean yellow muntjac    Pig-tailed langur    Long-tongued nectar bat    Mainland serow

WhatThe  also called the Borneo pygmy elephant inhabits northeastern Borneo. Its origin remains the subject of debate?
Borneo elephant    Peter's trumpet-eared bat    Clear-winged woolly bat    Mammals of Borneo

What is a species of bat in the family Hipposideridae. It is found in Borneo, Sumatra and Peninsular Malaysia?
Borneo roundleaf bat    Bawean deer    Sulawesi stripe-faced fruit bat    Mammals of Borneo

What is a wild pig-like animal native to the island of Buru and the two Sula Islands of Mangole and Taliabu, all belonging to Indonesia?
Buru babirusa    Timor shrew    Black-capped fruit bat    Lariang tarsier

What is a species of bat in the Rhinolophidae family. It is endemic to Indonesi?
Canut's horseshoe bat    Mountain treeshrew    Indonesian short-nosed fruit bat    Timor roundleaf bat

What is a possible new species of carnivoran discovered on the Indonesian part of the island of Borneo?
Cat-fox    Sulawesi tiny shrew    Tufted ground squirrel    Small-toothed palm civet

What is an Old World monkey that lives in the northeast of the Indonesian island of Sulawesi (Celebes) as well as on smaller neighboring islands?
Celebes crested macaque    Short-tailed mongoose    Banteng    White-collared fruit bat

What is a species of rodent in the Sciuridae family. It is endemic to Indonesi?
Celebes dwarf squirrel    Dayak fruit bat    Horsfield's fruit bat    Groove-toothed bat

Whatsis) is a species of rodent in the family Murida?
Celebes shrew rat    Javan tiger    Halmahera blossom bat    Timor shrew

Whatsis), Sulawesi warty pig or Sulawesi Pig, lives on Sulawesi in Indonesia?
Celebes warty pig    Sulawesi shrew    Lesser false vampire bat    White-fronted surili

What is a species of rodent in the family Muridae?
Central Sulawesi spiny rat    Silvery flying fox    Sumba roundleaf bat    North Sulawesi babirusa

Whatris) is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Ceram fruit bat    Siau Island tarsier    Small-eared rat    Phalanger matabiru

What is a civet species native to the Indian Subcontinent and Southeast Asia?
Masked palm civet    Crested roundleaf bat    Javan leopard    Sangihe tarsier

What is a civet found in South and Southeast Asia. It is listed as Least Concern by IUCN because of its widespread geographical distribution, widespread habitat use and healthy populations living in agricultural and secondary landscapes of many range states?
Small Indian civet    Long-tongued fruit bat    Mammals of Borneo    Sumatran mastiff bat

What is a large and little known species of carnivore endemic to the Indonesian island of Sulawesi, where it is found particularly in the North and Central regions?
Sulawesi palm civet    Siau Island tarsier    Mentawai long-tailed giant rat    Tufted ground squirrel

What is a species of vesper bat in the Vespertilionidae family?
Clear-winged woolly bat    Collared mongoose    Tailless fruit bat    Siau Island tarsier

Whatlared mongoose (Herpestes semitorquatus) is a species of mongoose in the Herpestidae family. It is found in Brunei, Indonesia, and Malaysi?
Collared mongoose    Minute shrew    Mentawi flying squirrel    Mammals of Borneo

Whatris australis, also known as the southern blossom bat or Queensland blossom bat, is a megabat in the family Pteropodidae?
Common blossom bat    Small Indian civet    Small-toothed palm civet    Celebes warty pig

What is a cuscus, a marsupial that lives in the Cape York region of Australia, New Guinea, and nearby smaller islands?
Common spotted cuscus    Flores shrew    Lariang tarsier    Bornean ferret-badger

Whatris) is a cercopithecine primate native to Southeast Asia. It is also called the long-tailed macaque, and is referred to as the cynomolgus monkey in laboratories?
Crab-eating macaque    Ceram fruit bat    Dusky fruit bat    Sun bear

Whatnis) is a large tree squirrel in the genus Ratufa found in Brunei, Indonesia, Malaysia, and Thailand?
Cream-coloured giant squirrel    Bay cat    Gebe cuscus    Southern pig-tailed macaque

What is a species of bat in the family Hipposideridae?
Crested roundleaf bat    Bali tiger    Irrawaddy dolphin    Eonycteris major

What is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Dark tube-nosed fruit bat    Sumatran porcupine    Sulawesi tiny shrew    Pen-tailed treeshrew

What is a relatively rare frugivorous megabat species found only on the Sunda Shelf of southeast Asia, specifically the Malay Peninsula south of the Isthmus of Kra, and the islands of Borneo and Sumatra?
Dayak fruit bat    Hairy-nosed otter    Pen-tailed treeshrew    Oriental shrew

What is a nocturnal primate found and endemic to central Sulawesi, Indonesia?
Dian's tarsier    Lesser false vampire bat    Flores woolly bat    Bannister's rat

Whatris, is a euryhaline species of oceanic dolphin found in discontinuous subpopulations near sea coasts and in estuaries and rivers in parts of the Bay of Bengal and Southeast Asia?
Irrawaddy dolphin    Bornean ferret-badger    Mentawai Three-striped Squirrel    Sumatran giant shrew

What is a large marine mammal which, together with the manatees, is one of four living species of the order Sirenia?
Dugong    Indonesian short-nosed fruit bat    Dark tube-nosed fruit bat    Komodo rat

WhatThe dusky fruit bat (Penthetor lucasi Dobson, 1880), the only member of the genus Penthetor, a genus of megabat?
Dusky fruit bat    Dugong    Greater mouse-deer    Nobkirelch

What is a species of rodent in the family Murida?
Dusky mosaic-tailed rat    Western naked-backed fruit bat    Natuna Island surili    Bornean white-bearded gibbon

What is a gymnure found only at Mount Kerinci, Sumatra, Indonesia. It is listed by the International Union for Conservation of Nature as a critically endangered species due to a restricted range?
Dwarf gymnure    Komodo rat    Malayan civet    Heavenly hill rat

What is a species of mammal in the Soricidae family. It is endemic to Indonesi?
Elongated shrew    Minahassa Ranee Mouse    Bali tiger    Canut's horseshoe bat

What is a species of megabat within the genus Eonycteris?
Eonycteris major    Sulawesi shrew    Javan mastiff bat    Small-toothed palm civet

What is a small wild cat patchily distributed in the Thai-Malay Peninsula, Borneo and Sumatra?
Flat-headed cat    Black flying fox    Sanghir squirrel    Silvery gibbon

What is a species of rodent endemic to Flores Island, Indonesia?
Flores long-nosed rat    Siamang    Homo floresiensis    Biak roundleaf bat

What is a white-toothed shrew found only on Flores Island, Indonesia. It is listed as a critically endangered species due to habitat loss and a restricted rang?
Flores shrew    Black flying fox    Dian's tarsier    Sunda porcupine

What is a species of vesper bat in the Vespertilionidae famil?
Flores woolly bat    Lesser tube-nosed bat    Blue-eyed cuscus    Mentawai langur

Whatriscus) form a taxon of squirrels under the subfamily Callosciurinae?
Four-striped Ground Squirrel    Blue-eyed cuscus    Borneo elephant    Thick-spined porcupine

What is a species of rodent in the family Murida?
Fraternal hill rat    Silvery gibbon    Sulawesi tiny shrew    Arrow flying squirrel

What is a species of rodent in the Sciuridae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Fraternal squirrel    Malayan weasel    Sumatran muntjac    Whitehead's woolly bat

What is a species of marsupial in the family Phalangeridae. It is endemic to the island of Gebe Umera, North Maluku province, Indonesia, where it lives at elevations from sea level to 300 ?
Gebe cuscus    Common blossom bat    Bay cat    Sanghir squirrel

What is a primate in the Hylobatidae or gibbon family?
Kloss's gibbon    Bornean bearded pig    Long-tongued nectar bat    Java mouse-deer

What is a primate in the Hylobatidae or gibbon family?
Müller's Bornean gibbon    Hagen's flying squirrel    Sulawesi montane rat    Ornate cuscus

What is a primate in the Hylobatidae or gibbon family. Its coat is bluish-grey in colour, with a dark grey or black cap?
Silvery gibbon    Long-footed treeshrew    Fraternal hill rat    Sunda clouded leopard

What is a species of treeshrew in the Tupaiidae family?
Golden-bellied treeshrew    Halmahera naked-backed fruit bat    Arrow flying squirrel    Sulawesi yellow bat

What is a species of primate in the Cercopithecidae family?
Gorontalo macaque    Nobkirelch    Pygmy treeshrew    Sunda clouded leopard

What is a species of even-toed ungulate in the Tragulidae family?
Greater mouse-deer    Hipposideros madurae    Bornean white-bearded gibbon    Beaufort's naked-backed fruit bat

Whatnish Naked-backed Fruit Bat (Dobsonia viridis) is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Greenish naked-backed fruit bat    Sanghir squirrel    Muntjac    Lombok flying fox

Whatniscus atrox) is a species of vesper bat in the Vespertilionidae famil?
Groove-toothed bat    Proboscis monkey    Greenish naked-backed fruit bat    Homo floresiensis

What is a species of rodent in the Sciuridae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Hagen's flying squirrel    Kloss Squirrel    Dwarf gymnure    Dian's tarsier

What is a species of rodent in the family Muridae. It is found only on Flores Island in Indonesia?
Hainald's rat    Bornean white-bearded gibbon    Horsfield's fruit bat    Montane long-nosed squirrel

What is one of the rarest otter species on earth. Until 1998, it was thought to have been extinct, but small populations have been discovered since then?
Hairy-nosed otter    Striped possum    Talaud flying fox    Painted treeshrew

Whatris carolinae) is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Halmahera blossom bat    Papillose woolly bat    Otter civet    Sunda flying fox

What is a common and widespread species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Halmahera naked-backed fruit bat    Slender treeshrew    Sulawesi montane rat    Large treeshrew

Whattis) is a species of rodent in the family Murida?
Heavenly hill rat    Halmahera blossom bat    Category:Rodents of Indonesia    Sumatran muntjac

What is a species of bat in the family Hipposideridae. It is endemic to Indonesi?
Hipposideros madurae    Peter's trumpet-eared bat    Sulawesi naked-backed fruit bat    Blue-eyed cuscus

What is a species of bat in the family Hipposideridae. It is endemic to Indonesi?
Hipposideros sorenseni    Big-eared roundleaf bat    Silvery flying fox    Sulawesi palm civet

Whatris) is a terrestrial mustelid that is widespread in Central and Southeast Asia?
Hog badger    Canut's horseshoe bat    Celebes dwarf squirrel    Slender treeshrew

What is a possible species, now extinct, in the genus Homo?
Homo floresiensis    Sunda stink badger    Minute fruit bat    Indian muntjac

What is a species of megabat native to South East Asia. It is named for Thomas Horsfield, an American naturalist who presented the type specimen to the British Museum?
Horsfield's fruit bat    Flat-headed cat    Marbled cat    Celebes warty pig

What is a species of tarsier?
Horsfield's tarsier    Asian house shrew    Sunda slow loris    Northern common cuscus

What is a species of treeshrew in the Tupaiidae family?
Horsfield's treeshrew    Javan leopard    Halmahera blossom bat    Timor roundleaf bat

Whattis hosei) is a species of primate in the Cercopithecidae family. It is endemic to the island of Borneo, including Brunei, Kalimantan (Indonesia), and East Malaysia?
Hose's langur    Inland hill rat    Neofelis    Black-footed shrew

What is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Indonesian short-nosed fruit bat    Dusky mosaic-tailed rat    Indonesian mountain weasel    Bannister's rat

What is a species of rodent in the family Murida?
Inland hill rat    Category:Mammals of Western New Guinea    Otter civet    Hog badger

Whatsis) is a species of bat in the Rhinolophidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Insular horseshoe bat    Linduan rousette    Javan ferret-badger    Natuna Island surili

What is a species of even-toed ungulate in the Tragulidae family?
Java mouse-deer    Oriental shrew    Anoa    Mentawai langur

What is a species of even-toed ungulate in the Suidae family?
Java warty pig    Dugong    Halmahera naked-backed fruit bat    Minute fruit bat

Whatlis) is a species of mammal in the Mustelidae family. It is endemic to Java and Bali in Indonesia?
Javan ferret-badger    Banded linsang    Wild boar    Clear-winged woolly bat

What is a leopard subspecies confined to the Indonesian island of Java and classified as critically endangered by IUCN since 2008. The population is estimated at less than 250 mature individuals, with a decreasing population trend?
Javan leopard    Sulawesi montane rat    Sumatran surili    Javanese shrew

What is an Old World monkey from the Colobinae subfamily?
Javan lutung    Lesser false vampire bat    Java warty pig    Black-footed shrew

What is a species of bat in the family Molossidae. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Javan mastiff bat    Silvery flying fox    Sumatran water shrew    Tailless fruit bat

Whatcisely Sunda rhinoceros) or lesser one-horned rhinoceros (Rhinoceros sondaicus) is a member of the family Rhinocerotidae and one of five extant rhinoceroses?
Javan rhinoceros    Sumatran mastiff bat    Tonkean macaque    Secretive dwarf squirrel

Whatsis) is a deer native to the islands of Java, Bali and Timor (shared with East Timor) in Indonesia?
Javan rusa    Sumatran tiger    Gebe cuscus    Flores woolly bat

What is a strepsirrhine primate and a species of slow loris native to the western and central portions of the island of Java, in Indonesia?
Javan slow loris    List of mammals of Indonesia    Sumatran striped rabbit    Spotted-winged fruit bat

What is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Javan tailless fruit bat    Bornean white-bearded gibbon    Canut's horseshoe bat    Nobkirelch

Whatris sondaica) is an extinct tiger subspecies that inhabited the Indonesian island of Java until the mid-1970s?
Javan tiger    Komodo rat    Eonycteris major    Cat-fox

What is a species of mammal in the Soricidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Javanese shrew    Category:Mammals of Western New Guinea    Sulawesi rousette    Malayan tapir

What is a genus of squirrels collectively referred to as the "Beautiful squirrels". They are found mainly in Southeast Asia, though a few species also occur in Nepal, northeastern India, Bangladesh and southern China?
Kloss Squirrel    Sambar deer    Sulawesi soft-furred rat    Ornate cuscus

What is a species of rodent in the family Murida?
Komodo rat    Banteng    Homo floresiensis    Hog badger

What is a species of rodent in the family Muridae?
Koopman's pencil-tailed tree mouse    Sody's tree-rat    Nesolagus    Sarawak surili

What is a primate in the Hylobatidae or gibbon family?
Lar gibbon    Siberut flying squirrel    Celebes warty pig    Painted bat

What is a mammal species of the family Tupaiidae. It is found on Sumatra and adjacent small islands, as well as in the lowlands and hills of Borneo?
Large treeshrew    Tufted ground squirrel    Gorontalo macaque    Sunda porcupine

What is a recently described tarsier occurring in the western part of the central core of Sulawesi?
Lariang tarsier    Lesser mouse-deer    Sulawesi stripe-faced fruit bat    Lesser tube-nosed bat

Whatsis) is a small wild cat of South and East Asia. Since 2002 it has been listed as Least Concern by IUCN as it is widely distributed but threatened by habitat loss and hunting in parts of its range?
Leopard cat    Sumatran serow    Rothschild's cuscus    Spectacled flying fox

What is a species of even-toed ungulate in the Tragulidae family?
Lesser mouse-deer    Eonycteris major    Irrawaddy dolphin    Long-tongued fruit bat

What is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family. It is endemic to the mountainous forests of two Indonesian islands, Buru and Seram, including the Manusela National Park on Seram, but is not found on the nearby Ambon Island?
Lesser tube-nosed bat    Spectacled flying fox    Tarsius fuscus    Sumatran long-tailed shrew

Whatsis) is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Lombok flying fox    Peter's trumpet-eared bat    Javan tiger    Pig-tailed langur

What is a species of treeshrew in the Tupaiidae family?
Long-footed treeshrew    Flores shrew    Lesser false vampire bat    Short-tailed mongoose

What is a species of rodent in the family Murida?
Long-headed hill rat    Pygmy treeshrew    Banded surili    Sunda shrew

What is a species of rodent in the Hystricidae family. It is monotypic within the genus Trichys?
Long-tailed porcupine    Hipposideros madurae    Sulawesi horseshoe bat    Peleng tarsier

What is a diprotodont marsupial found in the rainforests of northern Australia, Indonesia and New Guinea?
Long-tailed pygmy possum    Java warty pig    Sulawesi palm civet    Siau Island tarsier

What is a species of megaba?
Long-tongued fruit bat    Obi mosaic-tailed rat    Greenish naked-backed fruit bat    Sumatran water shrew

WhatThe long-tongued nectar bat (Macroglossus minimus), also known as the northern blossom bat,Honey nectar bat, least blossom-bat, dagger-toothed long-nosed fruit bat, and lesser long-tongued fruit bat, is a species of megabat. M?
Long-tongued nectar bat    Central Sulawesi spiny rat    Clear-winged woolly bat    Sumatran serow

What is a species of rodent in the Sciuridae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Lowland long-nosed squirrel    Sanghir squirrel    Whitish dwarf squirrel    Lesser mouse-deer

Whatnis milneedwardsii) is a species of goat antelope native to China and Southeast Asia?
Mainland serow    Silvery lutung    Canut's horseshoe bat    Mammals of Borneo

What is a civet found on the Malay Peninsula and the islands of Sumatra, Bangka, Borneo, the Rhio Archipelago, and the Philippines?
Malayan civet    Silvery flying fox    Lombok flying fox    Otter civet

What is the largest of the four species of tapir and the only one native to Asia?
Malayan tapir    Borneo roundleaf bat    Hainald's rat    Large treeshrew

What is a species of weasel. It lives in Brunei, Indonesia, Malaysia, and Thailand?
Malayan weasel    Marbled cat    Bornean yellow muntjac    Celebes warty pig

What is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Manado fruit bat    Banteng    Malayan civet    Black flying fox

What is a species of rodent in the family Muridae. It is found only in Indonesia?
Manusela mosaic-tailed rat    Sunda slow loris    Hainald's rat    Eonycteris major

Whatlis marmorata) is a small wild cat of South and Southeast Asia. Since 2002 it has been listed as vulnerable by IUCN as it occurs at low densities, and its total effective population size is suspected to be fewer than 10,000 mature individuals, with no single population numbering more than 1,00?
Marbled cat    Category:Rodents of Indonesia    Black-capped fruit bat    Arrow flying squirrel

Whattis rubicunda) is a species of primate in the Cercopithecidae family?
Maroon leaf monkey    Sulawesi stripe-faced fruit bat    Mentawai long-tailed giant rat    Marbled cat

What is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Masked flying fox    Banded palm civet    Ruddy treeshrew    Timor roundleaf bat

Whattis potenziani) is a species of primate in the Cercopithecidae family. It is endemic to the Mentawai Islands in Indonesia?
Mentawai langur    Southern pig-tailed macaque    Otter civet    Small-eared rat

What is a species of rodent in the family Muridae?
Mentawai long-tailed giant rat    Wild boar    Tufted ground squirrel    Large treeshrew

What is a genus of squirrels collectively referred to as the "Beautiful squirrels". They are found mainly in Southeast Asia, though a few species also occur in Nepal, northeastern India, Bangladesh and southern China?
Mentawai Squirrel    Crested roundleaf bat    Moonrat    Sumatran tiger

Whatriscus) form a taxon of squirrels under the subfamily Callosciurinae?
Mentawai Three-striped Squirrel    Short-tailed gymnure    Timor roundleaf bat    Pen-tailed treeshrew

What is a species of rodent in the Sciuridae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Mentawi flying squirrel    Hairy-nosed otter    Collared mongoose    Mentawai langur

What is a species of rodent in the family Murida?
Minahassa Ranee Mouse    Crab-eating macaque    Sunda flying fox    Bannister's rat

What is a species of megabat within the Pteropodidae family. It is found in Sumatra, Java, Borneo and Sulawesi?
Minute fruit bat    Neofelis    Minute shrew    Sulawesian shrew rat

What is a species of mammal in the Soricidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Minute shrew    Papillose woolly bat    Kloss's gibbon    Sunda flying fox

What is a species of megabat in the genus Pteropus?
Moluccan flying fox    Peters's myotis    Sangihe tarsier    Sunda clouded leopard

What is a species of rodent in the Sciuridae family?
Montane long-nosed squirrel    Komodo rat    Talaud bear cuscus    Polynesian rat

What is a species of mammal in the Erinaceidae family. It is the only species in the genus Echinosorex?
Moonrat    Moonrat    Sanghir squirrel    Striped treeshrew

What is a species of treeshrew in the Tupaiidae family that is endemic to Borneo?
Mountain treeshrew    Sulawesi rousette    Javan slow loris    Siberut flying squirrel

What are small deer of the genus Muntiacus. s are the oldest known deer, appearing 15–35 million years ago, with remains found in Miocene deposits in France, Germany and Poland?
Muntjac    Sarawak surili    Mentawai Squirrel    Clear-winged woolly bat

What is the most numerous muntjac deer species?
Indian muntjac    Southern pig-tailed macaque    Sumatran muntjac    Togian babirusa

Whattis natunae) is a species of primate in the Cercopithecidae family. It is endemic to the Indonesian island of Natuna Besar?
Natuna Island surili    Masked palm civet    Crested roundleaf bat    Javan mastiff bat

What is a species of mammal in the Soricidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Neglected shrew    Phalanger matabiru    Short-headed roundleaf bat    Thomas's langur

What is a genus comprising two extant felid species from Southeast Asia: the clouded leopard ( nebulosa) of mainland Asia, and the Sunda clouded leopard ( diardi) of Sumatra and Borneo?
Neofelis    Mountain treeshrew    Peter's trumpet-eared bat    Peter's trumpet-eared bat

Whateis) is a species of bat in the Rhinolophidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Neriad horseshoe bat    Lombok flying fox    Mentawai long-tailed giant rat    Celebes crested macaque

What is a genus of rabbits containing three species of striped rabbit, the Annamite Striped Rabbit, the Sumatran Striped Rabbit, and that of the extinct species "sinensis"?
Nesolagus    Black-bearded flying fox    Canut's horseshoe bat    Hipposideros sorenseni

Whatriscus) form a taxon of squirrels under the subfamily Callosciurinae?
Niobe Ground Squirrel    Sumatran porcupine    Javan ferret-badger    Gebe cuscus

Whatlis larvatus) or long-nosed monkey, known as the bekantan in Malay, is a reddish-brown arboreal Old World monkey that is endemic to the south-east Asian island of Borneo?
Nobkirelch    Natuna Island surili    Sulawesi naked-backed fruit bat    Peters's myotis

Whatsis, is a pig-like animal native to northern Sulawesi and the nearby Lembeh Islands in Indonesia?
North Sulawesi babirusa    Golden-bellied treeshrew    Masked palm civet    Four-striped Ground Squirrel

Whatlis), also known as the Grey cuscus, is a species of marsupial in the Phalangeridae family?
Northern common cuscus    Sumatran mastiff bat    Pygmy tarsier    Sulawesi montane rat

Whatsis) is a species of rodent in the family Murida?
Obi mosaic-tailed rat    Sulawesi forest rat    Minute fruit bat    Javan rusa

What is one of the two species of orangutans.  Found only on the island of Sumatra, in Indonesia, it is rarer than the Bornean orangutan?
Sumatran orangutan    Sumba roundleaf bat    Sulawesi naked-backed fruit bat    Ruddy treeshrew

Whatlis) is a species of mammal in the Soricidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Oriental shrew    Sunda shrew    Long-footed treeshrew    Lesser false vampire bat

What is a species of marsupial in the family Phalangeridae?
Ornate cuscus    Mentawi flying squirrel    Category:Rodents of Indonesia    Wild water buffalo

What is a species of bat in the Molossidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Otomops johnstonei    Water buffalo    Sun bear    Greater mouse-deer

What is a semi-aquatic civet found in forests, primarily lowland, near rivers and swampy areas of the Thai-Malay Peninsula, Sumatra, and Borneo?
Otter civet    Babyrousa bolabatuensis    Binturong    Clear-winged woolly bat

Whatsis), also known as the Pagai macaque or Bokkoi, is an Old World monkey endemic to the Mentawai Islands off the west coast of Sumatra?
Pagai Island macaque    Pen-tailed treeshrew    North Sulawesi babirusa    Flat-headed cat

What is a species of vesper bat in the Vespertilionidae famil?
Painted bat    Javan tailless fruit bat    Sulawesian shrew rat    Borneo elephant

What is a species of treeshrew in the Tupaiidae family. It is found in Brunei, Indonesia, and Malaysia?
Painted treeshrew    Tarsius fuscus    Dark tube-nosed fruit bat    Banggai cuscus

What is a species of vesper bat in the Vespertilionidae family?
Papillose woolly bat    Heavenly hill rat    Sunda porcupine    Babyrousa bolabatuensis

What is a genus within the family of cats. At present, this genus is defined as including three species native to Southeast Asia: the marbled cat, the bay cat and the Asian golden cat?
Pardofelis    Bornean orangutan    Sulawesi forest rat    Bannister's rat

Whatsis), or the Peleng Island tarsier, is a nocturnal primate found on Peleng Island, Indonesia?
Peleng tarsier    Bornean white-bearded gibbon    Spectacled flying fox    Black-footed shrew

What is a species of treeshrew in the Ptilocercidae family. It is found in Indonesia, Malaysia, and Thailand?
Pen-tailed treeshrew    Elongated shrew    Nobkirelch    Short-headed roundleaf bat

WhatEared Bat (Phoniscus jagorii) is a species of vesper bat in the Vespertilionidae family?
Peter's trumpet-eared bat    Maroon leaf monkey    Dark tube-nosed fruit bat    Siau Island tarsier

Whattis ater) is a species of vesper bat It is found in Indonesia, Papua New Guinea, the Philippines, and sometimes Australi?
Peters's myotis    Four-striped Ground Squirrel    Inland hill rat    Javan lutung

What is a species of marsupial in the Phalangeridae family. It is endemic to the two small islands of Ternate and Tidore, west of the island of Halmahera of Indonesi?
Phalanger matabiru    Golden-bellied treeshrew    Otomops johnstonei    Timor roundleaf bat

What is a large, rather heavily built Old World monkey, which is adapted to climbing with its long arms?
Pig-tailed langur    Horsfield's fruit bat    Flores woolly bat    Beaufort's naked-backed fruit bat

Whatcis monkey (Nasalis larvatus) or long-nosed monkey, known as the bekantan in Malay, is a reddish-brown arboreal Old World monkey that is endemic to the south-east Asian island of Borneo?
Proboscis monkey    Bay cat    Dwarf gymnure    Beaufort's naked-backed fruit bat

What is a species of megaba?
Pygmy fruit bat    Niobe Ground Squirrel    Javan tailless fruit bat    Secretive dwarf squirrel

What is a nocturnal primate found in central Sulawesi, Indonesia, in an area with lower vegetative species diversity than the lowland tropical forests?
Pygmy tarsier    Flores shrew    Water buffalo    Pagai Island macaque

What is a species of treeshrew in the family Tupaiidae. It is found in Indonesia, Malaysia, and Thailand?
Pygmy treeshrew    Peter's trumpet-eared bat    Oriental shrew    Neglected shrew

What is the third most widespread species of rat in the world behind the brown rat and black rat?
Polynesian rat    Banded linsang    Javan slow loris    Irrawaddy dolphin

Whatrisciurus rubriventer) is a species of squirrel. Until recently, it was described as a species in the genus Callosciurus, but since the 1990s it is generally placed in its own genus Rubrisciurus?
Red-bellied squirrel    Togian babirusa    Sulawesian shrew rat    Bornean orangutan

Whatsis) is a member of the family Rhinocerotidae and one of five extant rhinoceroses?
Sumatran rhinoceros    Clear-winged woolly bat    Sulawesi horseshoe bat    Muntjac

What is a species of marsupial in the family Phalangeridae?
Rothschild's cuscus    Masked flying fox    Borneo elephant    Java mouse-deer

Whatsis) is a species of megabat in the Rousettus genus of the Pteropodidae family?
Linduan rousette    Muntjac    Borneo roundleaf bat    Marbled cat

Whatsis) is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Sulawesi rousette    Striped possum    Pygmy fruit bat    Peters's myotis

What is a species of treeshrew in the Tupaiidae family. It is endemic to Indonesi?
Ruddy treeshrew    Bornean ferret-badger    Whitish dwarf squirrel    Pygmy tarsier

What is a large deer native to the Indian Subcontinent and Southeast Asia. Although it primarily refers to R?
Sambar deer    Indonesian mountain weasel    Banggai cuscus    Neofelis

What is a species of rodent in the Sciuridae family. It is endemic to the presently-dormant volcanic Sangir Island, which is one of the Sangir Islands in Indonesia, located just north of the equator in the Celebes Sea, between the Indonesian island of Sulawesi and the island of Mindanao in the Philippines?
Sanghir squirrel    White-thighed surili    Northern common cuscus    Java warty pig

Whatsis), also known as Sangihe Island tarsier, is a small primate found on Sangir Island, which is located about 200 kilometers north-east of the island of Sulawesi in Indonesia?
Sangihe tarsier    Leopard cat    Wild boar    Pardofelis

Whattis chrysomelas) is a species of primate in the Cercopithecidae family. It is endemic to the southeast Asian island of Borneo, where it is distributed north of the Kapuas River in Kalimantan, Indonesia, the Malaysia states of Sarawak and Sabah, and in Brunei?
Sarawak surili    Black-bearded flying fox    Sumba roundleaf bat    Phalanger matabiru

What is a species of rodent in the Sciuridae family?
Secretive dwarf squirrel    Central Sulawesi spiny rat    Dugong    Western naked-backed fruit bat

What is a member of the order Peramelemorphia?
Seram bandicoot    Celebes shrew rat    Hose's langur    Spotted-winged fruit bat

What is a species of bat in the family Hipposideridae?
Short-headed roundleaf bat    Sulawesi soft-furred rat    Celebes dwarf squirrel    Lowland long-nosed squirrel

What is a small erinaceomorph that is found in southeast Asia. This gymnure, which resembles a large mouse, grows to a length of 4-6 inches, and feeds on insects, worms and other small animals?
Short-tailed gymnure    Natuna Island surili    Otomops johnstonei    Black-bearded flying fox

What is a species of mongoose that lives in the rainforests of Southeast Asia?
Short-tailed mongoose    Silvery lutung    Ashy-headed flying fox    Flores woolly bat

What is a red-toothed shrew found only in the Padang highlands of western Sumatra, Indonesia?
Sumatran water shrew    Dark tube-nosed fruit bat    Masked flying fox    Hipposideros madurae

What is a tailless, arboreal, black-furred gibbon native to the forests of Malaysia, Thailand, and Sumatra?
Siamang    White-thighed surili    Mentawai Squirrel    Painted treeshrew

What is a species of tarsier from the tiny volcanic island of Sia?
Siau Island tarsier    Talaud bear cuscus    Beccari's shrew    Horsfield's tarsier

What is a species of rodent in the Sciuridae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Siberut flying squirrel    Ruddy treeshrew    Western naked-backed fruit bat    Fraternal squirrel

What is a megabat in the genus Pteropus from eastern Indonesia?
Silvery flying fox    Spotted-winged fruit bat    Spotted-winged fruit bat    Sulawesi soft-furred rat

Whatristatus), also known as the silvered leaf monkey or the silvery langur, is an Old World monkey?
Silvery lutung    Timor roundleaf bat    Javan tailless fruit bat    Gebe cuscus

What is a species of rodent in the Sciuridae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Sipora flying squirrel    Slow loris    Javan lutung    Thick-spined porcupine

Whatlis) is a species of treeshrew in the Tupaiidae family. It is found in Indonesia and Malaysi?
Slender treeshrew    Minute shrew    Pardofelis    Greenish naked-backed fruit bat

What are a group of several species of strepsirrhine primates which make up the genus Nycticebus?
Slow loris    Sumatran striped rabbit    Halmahera naked-backed fruit bat    Sulawesi yellow bat

Whateared Rat (Taeromys microbullatus), is an extant species of Old World rodent that inhabits the south-east of Sulawesi, an Indonesian island?
Small-eared rat    Clear-winged woolly bat    Large treeshrew    Malayan civet

What is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family. It is monotypic within the genus Neopteryx?
Small-toothed fruit bat    Long-tongued fruit bat    Four-striped Ground Squirrel    Neglected shrew

What is a civet?
Small-toothed palm civet    Blue-eyed cuscus    Irrawaddy dolphin    Mentawai Squirrel

What is a species of rodent in the family Murida?
Sody's tree-rat    Greater mouse-deer    Bornean white-bearded gibbon    Javan leopard

What is a medium-sized Old World monke?
Southern pig-tailed macaque    Asian house shrew    Fraternal hill rat    Buru babirusa

What is a megabat that lives in Australia's north-eastern regions of Queensland?
Spectacled flying fox    Pig-tailed langur    Masked flying fox    Javan rusa

What is a species of tarsier found in Indonesia. It is apparently less specialized than the Philippine tarsier or Horsfield's tarsier; for example, it lacks adhesive toes?
Spectral tarsier    Mentawai long-tailed giant rat    Banggai cuscus    Javanese shrew

Whatris maculata) is the smallest megabat in the world, and the only species in the genus Balionycteris?
Spotted-winged fruit bat    Red-bellied squirrel    Pen-tailed treeshrew    Crab-eating macaque

What is a member of the Petauridae family, one of the marsupial families?
Striped possum    Sumatran elephant    Wild water buffalo    Sumatran rhinoceros

Whatlis) is a species of treeshrew in the Tupaiidae family. It is found in Indonesia and Malaysi?
Striped treeshrew    Horsfield's tarsier    Short-headed roundleaf bat    Sunda flying lemur

What is a species of marsupial in the family Phalangeridae?
Sulawesi bear cuscus    Asian house shrew    Blue-eyed cuscus    Collared mongoose

Whatsis) is a species of marsupial in the family Phalangeridae?
Sulawesi dwarf cuscus    Sulawesi dwarf cuscus    Sipora flying squirrel    Sulawesi rousette

Whatsis') is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Sulawesi flying fox    Sunda clouded leopard    Dugong    Siamang

What is a species of rodent in the family Murida?
Sulawesi forest rat    Silvery flying fox    Red-bellied squirrel    Neglected shrew

What is a species of bat in the family Molossidae. It is found in Indonesia and the Philippines?
Sulawesi free-tailed bat    Halmahera naked-backed fruit bat    Pygmy tarsier    Gebe cuscus

What is a species of rodent in the family Muridae. It is monotypic in the genus Paruromys?
Sulawesi giant rat    Sunda slow loris    Siamang    Blue-eyed cuscus

Whatris celebensis) is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Sulawesi harpy fruit bat    Sulawesi flying fox    Sunda porcupine    Bornean orangutan

Whatsis) is a species of bat in the Rhinolophidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Sulawesi horseshoe bat    Talaud flying fox    Javan ferret-badger    Gebe cuscus

What is a species of rodent in the family Murida?
Sulawesi montane rat    Lombok flying fox    Muntjac    Sulawesi naked-backed fruit bat

What is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Sulawesi naked-backed fruit bat    Gebe cuscus    Pen-tailed treeshrew    Gebe cuscus

What is a species of mammal in the Soricidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Sulawesi shrew    Sunda porcupine    Sulawesi dwarf cuscus    Moonrat

What is a species of rodent in the family Muridae.  It is the only species in the genus Eropeplus?
Sulawesi soft-furred rat    Pen-tailed treeshrew    Fraternal squirrel    Andrew's hill rat

What is a species of rodent in the family Murida?
Sulawesi spiny rat    Clear-winged woolly bat    Flores woolly bat    Muntjac

What is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Sulawesi stripe-faced fruit bat    Manusela mosaic-tailed rat    Spectacled flying fox    Gebe cuscus

What is a species of mammal in the Soricidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Sulawesi tiny shrew    Sangihe tarsier    Sulawesi forest rat    Javanese shrew

Whattis) is a species of mammal in the Soricidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Sulawesi white-handed shrew    Sumatran muntjac    Horsfield's tarsier    Whitehead's woolly bat

Whatsis) is a species of vesper bat. It is found only in Indonesia?
Sulawesi yellow bat    Timor shrew    Tonkean macaque    Gorontalo macaque

What is a species of rodent in the family Muridae.  It is the only species in the genus Melasmothrix?
Sulawesian shrew rat    Natuna Island surili    Nobkirelch    Sulawesi naked-backed fruit bat

What is one of three recognized subspecies of the Asian elephant, and native to the Indonesia island of Sumatra?
Sumatran elephant    Striped possum    Bornean ferret-badger    Sody's tree-rat

What is a flying squirrel only found on the island of Sumatra?
Sumatran flying squirrel    Thick-spined porcupine    Hose's langur    Common blossom bat

What is a shrew of the genus Crocidura. It is native to the Indonesian island of Sumatra, where it is found both in the rainforests to the west of the island and in the hillsides in the south and east?
Sumatran giant shrew    Sumatran surili    Pardofelis    Pardofelis

What is a species of mammal in the Soricidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Sumatran long-tailed shrew    Long-headed hill rat    Sulawesi yellow bat    Sunda flying fox

What is a species of bat found in Indonesia. Synonyms include Tadarida and Micronomus?
Sumatran mastiff bat    Arrow flying squirrel    Short-tailed gymnure    Javan rhinoceros

What is a deer which can be the size of a large dog. The  was discovered in 1914, but had not been sighted since 1930, until one was snared and freed from a hunter's snare in Kerinci Seblat National Park, Sumatra, Indonesia in 2002. Two other  have since been photographed in the park?
Sumatran muntjac    Flores woolly bat    Siberut flying squirrel    Long-tongued nectar bat

What is a species of rodent in the Hystricidae family. It is endemic to the Indonesian island of Sumatra?
Sumatran porcupine    Oriental shrew    Hainald's rat    Borneo roundleaf bat

Whatnis sumatraensis), also known as the southern serow, is a species of goat-antelope native to mountain forests in the Thai-Malay Peninsula and on the Indonesian island of Sumatra?
Sumatran serow    Sumatran porcupine    Dwarf gymnure    Otomops johnstonei

Whateared rabbit or Sumatran rabbit, is a rabbit found only in forest in the Barisan Mountains in western Sumatra, Indonesia and surrounding areas?
Sumatran striped rabbit    Sun bear    Oriental shrew    Cream-coloured giant squirrel

Whattis melalophos) is a species of primate in the Cercopithecidae family. It is endemic to Sumatra in Indonesia?
Sumatran surili    Sulawesi yellow bat    Horsfield's tarsier    Sangihe tarsier

What is a species of bat in the family Hipposideridae. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Sumba roundleaf bat    Wild boar    Inland hill rat    Dian's tarsier

What is a bear found in tropical forest habitats of Southeast Asia. It is classified as Vulnerable by IUCN as the large-scale deforestation that has occurred throughout Southeast Asia over the past three decades has dramatically reduced suitable habitat for the sun bear?
Sun bear    Sipora flying squirrel    Sumatran porcupine    Canut's horseshoe bat

Whatlis diardi), also known as the Sundaland clouded leopard, is a medium-sized wild cat found in Borneo and Sumatra. In 2006, it was classified as a separate species, distinct from its continental relative Neofelis nebulos?
Sunda clouded leopard    Kloss's gibbon    Gebe cuscus    Talaud flying fox

What is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Sunda flying fox    Hose's langur    Pen-tailed treeshrew    Canut's horseshoe bat

What is a species of colugo (see below for notes on the common name "flying lemur")?
Sunda flying lemur    Rothschild's cuscus    Eonycteris major    Water buffalo

Whatnis javanica), also known as the Malayan or Javan pangolin, is a species of pangolin found in Southeast Asia, including Thailand, Indonesia (Java, Sumatra, Borneo and the Lesser Sunda Islands), the Philippines, Vietnam, Laos and Cambodia, and Malaysia and Singapore?
Sunda pangolin    Minute shrew    Sumatran elephant    Pygmy tarsier

What is a species of rodent in the Hystricidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Sunda porcupine    Painted treeshrew    Sarawak surili    Dusky fruit bat

What is a species of mammal in the Soricidae family. It is found in Indonesia and Malaysia?
Sunda shrew    Sumatran elephant    Western naked-backed fruit bat    Fraternal hill rat

Whatris is a strepsirrhine primate and a species of slow loris native to Indonesia, western Malaysia, southern Thailand and Singapore?
Sunda slow loris    Ruddy treeshrew    Talaud bear cuscus    Sunda pangolin

Whatsis, also called the Javan stink badger, teledu, Malay stink badger and Indonesian stink badger) is a mammal of Southeast Asia?
Sunda stink badger    Celebes warty pig    Banggai cuscus    Striped possum

What is a species of megaba?
Tailless fruit bat    Category:Mammals of New Guinea    Banded linsang    Müller's Bornean gibbon

Whattis) is a species of marsupial in the Phalangeridae family. It is endemic to  in the Talaud Islands, Indonesia?
Talaud bear cuscus    Timor shrew    Lowland long-nosed squirrel    Manusela mosaic-tailed rat

Whatlis) is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Talaud flying fox    Ruddy treeshrew    Groove-toothed bat    Sumatran long-tailed shrew

What is a species of tarsier. Its range is in Indonesia in the southwestern peninsula of the island of Sulawesi,  near Makassar?
Tarsius fuscus    Elongated shrew    Whitish dwarf squirrel    Long-tongued fruit bat

Whatsispinis) is a species of rodent in the Hystricidae family. It is found in Brunei, Indonesia, and Malaysia?
Thick-spined porcupine    Neglected shrew    Elongated shrew    Seram bandicoot

Whattis thomasi) is a species of primate in the Cercopithecidae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Thomas's langur    Category:Mammals of New Guinea    Crab-eating macaque    Category:Rodents of Indonesia

Whatris sumatrae) is a rare tiger subspecies that inhabits the Indonesian island of Sumatra?
Sumatran tiger    Pygmy fruit bat    Java mouse-deer    Sody's tree-rat

What is a species of bat in the family Hipposideridae. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Timor roundleaf bat    Nobkirelch    Dusky mosaic-tailed rat    Sumatran rhinoceros

Whatuis) is a species of mammal in the Soricidae family. It is endemic to Timor?
Timor shrew    Long-tongued nectar bat    Celebes dwarf squirrel    Javan slow loris

Whatsis), also known as the Malenge Babirusa, is the largest species of babirusa?
Togian babirusa    Water buffalo    Bare-backed rousette    Tufted ground squirrel

What is a species of primate in the Cercopithecidae family?
Tonkean macaque    Four-striped Ground Squirrel    Black-footed shrew    Irrawaddy dolphin

Whatlis) is a small mammal in the treeshrew family Tupaiidae, and is native to Thailand, Malaysia and Indonesia?
Common treeshrew    Cat-fox    Insular horseshoe bat    Sumatran orangutan

Whattis) is a species of rodent in the Sciuridae family. It is monotypic within the genus Rheithrosciurus?
Tufted ground squirrel    Sun bear    Slender treeshrew    Sulawesi forest rat

Whattis wallacii) is a member of the Dasyuromorphia order. This marsupial carnivore is found in Indonesia and Papua New Guinea?
Wallace's dasyure    Manado fruit bat    Sumatran muntjac    Natuna Island surili

Whatlis) is a large buffalo found on the Indian subcontinent to Vietnam and Peninsular Malaysia, in Sri Lanka and in Borneo?
Water buffalo    Sulawesi horseshoe bat    Javan ferret-badger    Short-tailed mongoose

What is a species of weasel that lives on the islands of Java and Sumatra in Indonesia at elevations over 1,000 metres (3,280 ft)?
Indonesian mountain weasel    Sulawesi dwarf cuscus    Greater mouse-deer    Slow loris

What is a species of rodent in the Sciuridae family. It is endemic to Indonesia?
Weber's dwarf squirrel    Obi mosaic-tailed rat    Sanghir squirrel    Siau Island tarsier

What is a species of megabat in the Pteropodidae family?
Western naked-backed fruit bat    Sunda shrew    Montane long-nosed squirrel    Short-headed roundleaf bat

Whatlared Fruit Bat (Megaerops wetmorei) is a species of megabat found in Southeast Asi?
White-collared fruit bat    Anoa    Lombok flying fox    Sulawesi spiny rat

Whattis frontata) is a species of primate in the Cercopithecidae family. It is found in Indonesia, Malaysia, and possibly Brunei?
White-fronted surili    Peter's trumpet-eared bat    Manusela mosaic-tailed rat    Hainald's rat

Whattis siamensis) is a species of primate in the Cercopithecidae family. It is endemic to the Thai-Malay Peninsula, the Riau Archipelago and Sumatra?
White-thighed surili    Binturong    Siberut flying squirrel    Eonycteris major

What is a species of vesper bat in the Vespertilionidae family?
Whitehead's woolly bat    Sunda slow loris    Whitish dwarf squirrel    Sun bear

Whattish Dwarf Squirrel (Prosciurillus leucomus) is a species of rodent in the Sciuridae family. It is endemic to Indonesi?
Whitish dwarf squirrel    Dwarf gymnure    Javanese shrew    Sunda flying fox

What is a species of the pig genus Sus, part of the biological family Suidae?
Wild boar    Blue-eyed cuscus    Bornean orangutan    Malayan weasel

What is a large bovine native to Southeast Asia?
Wild water buffalo    Dian's tarsier    Celebes warty pig    Mentawi flying squirrel

Whathis is a category for mammals found on the island of New Guinea, both Western New Guinea, Indonesia (western) and Papua New Guinea (eastern?
Category:Mammals of New Guinea    Dark tube-nosed fruit bat    Striped treeshrew    Sumatran striped rabbit

What?
Category:Rodents of Indonesia    Indonesian mountain weasel    Sarawak surili    Sumatran surili

WhatMammals of Western New Guine?
Category:Mammals of Western New Guinea    Rothschild's cuscus    Javan rhinoceros    Javan rusa

